<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game id="279266">
		<path>./BioShock.bat</path>
		<name>BioShock</name>
		<desc>In the year 1960, a plane crashes in the middle of the Atlantic Ocean with a man named Jack as the only survivor. He has the apparent luck of resurfacing in front of what looks like a door to an underwater complex. Without hesitating, Jack enters the door and is greeted by slogans that praise the city of Rapture, a paradise of free will built in the 1940s by a business magnate named Andrew Ryan. However, even before he assimilates all this new information, the descent to this supposed paradise ends and he can only see ruins and chaos. Learning about the destiny of Rapture will be now Jack's main motivation while he tries to survive the horrors that free will can create.</desc>
		<image>./images/BioShock-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/BioShock-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/BioShock-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/BioShock-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/BioShock-boxback.png</boxback>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20070821T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>2K Australia</developer>
		<publisher>2K Games</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / 1st person</genre>
		<family>Bioshock</family>
		<lastplayed>20230222T000000</lastplayed>
		<md5>0e23e1fd175d25342abe4eebd75ea994</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230222T112635" />
	</game>
	<game id="279288">
		<path>./BioShock Remastered.bat</path>
		<name>BioShock: Remastered</name>
		<desc>BioShock: Remastered is a remastered version of BioShock. Released as a part of BioShock: The Collection, for PC it is also available separately. It includes:
BioShock (original version)
BioShock: Remastered (remastered version)
Bioshock: PS3 Challenge Rooms (DLC integrated into the remastered version)
BioShock: Museum of Orphaned Concepts (in-game gallery of abandoned development concepts, previously exclusive to BioShock: Ultimate Rapture Edition) for the remastered version
Imagining BioShock, an unlockable director's commentary video series for the remastered version of BioShock featuring Ken Levine and Shawn Robertson, activated through hidden film reels. The remastered version has achievements, full controller support, high resolution textures, models and interface, and 4K resolution support.</desc>
		<image>./images/BioShock Remastered-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/BioShock Remastered-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/BioShock Remastered-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/BioShock Remastered-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/BioShock Remastered-boxback.png</boxback>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20160915T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>2K Australia</developer>
		<publisher>2K Games</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / 1st person</genre>
		<family>Bioshock</family>
		<lastplayed>20230222T000000</lastplayed>
		<md5>195472f4dd984aab95da40b181d8659a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230222T112638" />
	</game>
	<game id="282276">
		<path>./Call of Duty 4 Modern Warfare.bat</path>
		<name>Call of Duty 4: Modern Warfare</name>
		<desc>A fresh approach in the long-running Call of Duty franchise with the original developers back behind the wheel, chapter 4 has the player assume the role of a British S.A.S. squad member in various missions over Europe, as well as a U.S. Marine in the Middle East, fighting against fictive global terrorism driving persona.

Without breaking the traditions of its heritage, Call of Duty 4 is a true military-based FPS, only this time it has the player fight in a fictive setting and in a modern-day world, against modern enemies and ditto weapons. There are various campaign-based missions that enable the player to take the role of two different soldiers, from two different kinds of military enforcement disciplines. As usual, multiplayer is also available with different game modes.</desc>
		<image>./images/Call of Duty 4 Modern Warfare-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Call of Duty 4 Modern Warfare-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Call of Duty 4 Modern Warfare-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Call of Duty 4 Modern Warfare-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Call of Duty 4 Modern Warfare-boxback.png</boxback>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20071105T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Infinity Ward</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / 1st person</genre>
		<family>Call Of Duty</family>
		<lastplayed>20230222T000000</lastplayed>
		<md5>03ec0b7184792ee0397bdf9f1358f21f</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230222T112640" />
	</game>
	<game id="286486">
		<path>./Counter-Strike.bat</path>
		<name>Counter-Strike</name>
		<desc>A tactical FPS game, in which players assume the roles of members of combating teams of the governmental counter-terrorist forces, or various terrorist militants opposing them.

The game of Counter-Strike deals with two sides, the Counter Terrorists and the Terrorists, consisting of a Team Deathmatch style game play in 2 game modes. In Defuse game play, the Terrorists can either kill the opposing team (Same for the Counter-Terrorists), or plant the bomb at point A &amp; B, and then guard the bomb until it explodes - the Counter Terrorists can win by defusing the bomb. In the the CS game mode the Counter Terrorists must rescue 4 hostages. The Terrorists can win by defending the hostages.

The Steam release of Counter-Strike is commercial standalone version of the game, updated with a newer GoldSrc engine build. However, they omit the extra modifications which were available in the Half-Life: Counter-Strike retail releases that are not Counter-Strike itself.</desc>
		<image>./images/Counter-Strike-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Counter-Strike-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Counter-Strike-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Counter-Strike-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Counter-Strike-boxback.png</boxback>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20030912T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Valve</developer>
		<publisher>Valve</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<lastplayed>20230222T000000</lastplayed>
		<md5>212c0a1356cbcdaa948f9b2a6594f5b9</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230222T112642" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Counter-Strike Condition Zero Deleted Scenes.bat</path>
		<name>Counter-Strike Condition Zero Deleted Scenes</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20230222T000000</releasedate>
		<players>0</players>
		<lastplayed>20230222T000000</lastplayed>
		<md5>d128906da8dfbd3db768b0e4b1840e90</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230222T112645" />
	</game>
	<game id="286492">
		<path>./Counter-Strike Condition Zero.bat</path>
		<name>Counter-Strike: Condition Zero</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<lastplayed>20230222T000000</lastplayed>
		<md5>a7dfdbe0b3ceaf5d30504f7c41cf6944</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230222T112647" />
	</game>
	<game id="286526">
		<path>./Counter-Strike Source.bat</path>
		<name>Counter-Strike: Source</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<lastplayed>20230222T000000</lastplayed>
		<md5>c6fbd8d2f60a0c9a75297c0bf3929a25</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230222T112650" />
	</game>
	<game id="289226">
		<path>./Day of Defeat.bat</path>
		<name>Day of Defeat</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<lastplayed>20230222T000000</lastplayed>
		<md5>ca38ac36903db0452383d1815d9475aa</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230222T112652" />
	</game>
	<game id="289228">
		<path>./Day of Defeat Source.bat</path>
		<name>Day of Defeat: Source</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<lastplayed>20230222T000000</lastplayed>
		<md5>f40604d430b4b21487a01930093c9793</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230222T112655" />
	</game>
	<game id="289716">
		<path>./Deathmatch Classic.bat</path>
		<name>Deathmatch Classic</name>
		<desc>Deathmatch Classic is a pure multiplayer game, designed as a tribute to id Software and the multiplayer gameplay in its older games. While very similar to multiplayer Quake, some elements of the game are borrowed from Half-Life, such as player models and the melee weapon.

The game was originally developed as a mod for Half-Life, and continues to use the GoldSrc engine. The idea behind DMC was to allow Half-Life players to play deathmatch games in the style of Quake and Quake II, but with the enhancements of the GoldSrc engine.</desc>
		<image>./images/Deathmatch Classic-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Deathmatch Classic-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Deathmatch Classic-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Deathmatch Classic-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Deathmatch Classic-boxback.png</boxback>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20030912T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Valve</developer>
		<publisher>Valve</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / 1st person</genre>
		<family>Half-Life</family>
		<lastplayed>20230222T000000</lastplayed>
		<md5>68c5f6fbd1571947d8a37bdd64416ba8</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230222T112657" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dota 2.bat</path>
		<name>Dota 2</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20230222T000000</releasedate>
		<players>0</players>
		<lastplayed>20230222T000000</lastplayed>
		<md5>0d4e4f52076be6d5dff7b38415397aaa</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230222T112659" />
	</game>
	<game id="302442">
		<path>./Golden Rush.bat</path>
		<name>Golden Rush</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<lastplayed>20230222T000000</lastplayed>
		<md5>8e98c4371cb493e86174d6929b4206e6</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230222T112702" />
	</game>
	<game id="303390">
		<path>./Grimoire Manastorm.bat</path>
		<name>Grimoire: Manastorm</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<lastplayed>20230222T000000</lastplayed>
		<md5>657b7cd2b483b2f4bf63cc25c4d8f068</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230222T112704" />
	</game>
	<game id="304202">
		<path>./Half-Life.bat</path>
		<name>Half-Life</name>
		<desc>Black Mesa Research Facility is an ultra-secret laboratory under government contract, conducting top-secret and extremely volatile experiments. The scientist Gordon Freeman a Black Mesa employee. This morning, as usual, he pits his way to the research facility for a run-of-the-mill experiment. However, when the experiment initiates, Gordon realizes that it might not be as ordinary as he thought. Odd things begin to happen as he makes his way to one of the Black Mesa test chambers. Even weirder things happen when he starts to move the test sample towards the antimass-spectrometer.

At that moment everything goes horribly wrong. Aliens from the planet Xen have suddenly invaded the facility, injuring or killing many of the employees. The Marines have come to the facility to kill off the aliens and the surviving witnesses of the accident. Gordon understands what that means: he will have to fight his way through aliens and Marines to get to the top of the Black Mesa complex and much beyond.

The story of Half-Life is told entirely in-game: everything is seen through the eyes of the protagonist. Most story elements unfold via scripted sequences, triggered by the player reaching a certain area. If other characters have information to reveal, they address the player directly. The Black Mesa complex in the game is not made up of distinct levels, but is mostly a continuous world, where it is possible to backtrack through large parts of the game.

The game's weapon arsenal is, to a large part, made up of realistic weapons like pistols, machine guns and explosives, but there are also futuristic energy weapons developed at Black Mesa as well as organic weapons acquired from the invading aliens. Most weapons feature an alternate firing mode.

Enemies fall into two categories: aliens and human soldiers. While most of the aliens are not very bright, the humans display some relatively advanced artificial intelligence: they seek cover, retreat when hit and try to drive the player from his cover by throwing grenades. Some of the alien enemies can not be killed by normal means. The environment must be used against them instead, going with a general tendency of the game to alternate the combat with environmental puzzles.</desc>
		<image>./images/Half-Life-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Half-Life-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Half-Life-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Half-Life-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Half-Life-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Half-Life-boxback.png</boxback>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19981119T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Valve</developer>
		<publisher>Sierra On-Line</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<family>Half-Life</family>
		<lastplayed>20230222T000000</lastplayed>
		<md5>fbe18a84d2cefdef27432ad6f75ba6c7</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230222T112707" />
	</game>
	<game id="304206">
		<path>./Half-Life 2.bat</path>
		<name>Half-Life 2</name>
		<desc>Following the period of instability caused by the events described in Half-Life, an interdimensional organization known as the Combine invades the Earth, defeating the human forces in the Seven Hour War. A Combine Citadel is erected in City 17, a town in Eastern Europe reminiscent of World War II ghettos. Dr. Wallace Breen, a human scientist, rules the city on behalf of his new masters. An energy field prevents humans from procreating, and no new children are born. Earth is turning into a grim, oppressive police state.

Meanwhile, Gordon Freeman, the man who was at the center of the events that took place shortly before the rise of the Combine, awakens from his stasis and is inserted into a train to City 17 by the mysterious G-man. Gordon is soon brought into a resistance group, and makes a seemingly futile attempt to bring down the Combine and liberate the Earth.</desc>
		<image>./images/Half-Life 2-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Half-Life 2-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Half-Life 2-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Half-Life 2-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Half-Life 2-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Half-Life 2-boxback.png</boxback>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20041116T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Valve</developer>
		<publisher>Vivendi Universal Games</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<family>Half-Life</family>
		<lastplayed>20230222T000000</lastplayed>
		<md5>9b24db269f75bf4a81542d17c2650b8d</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230222T112710" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Half-Life 2 Lost Coast.bat</path>
		<name>Half-Life 2 Lost Coast</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20230222T000000</releasedate>
		<players>0</players>
		<lastplayed>20230222T000000</lastplayed>
		<md5>3dda3f2a9bd90070e34ac18b1e4b8b0d</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230222T112712" />
	</game>
	<game id="304212">
		<path>./Half-Life 2 Deathmatch.bat</path>
		<name>Half-Life 2: Deathmatch</name>
		<desc>Half-Life 2: Deathmatch is the stand-alone multiplayer version of Half-Life 2. The original game did not contain a multiplayer part, and it was released later. The main goal of the game is to annihilate your opponent(s) in a free-for-all multiplayer battle. 

The game features the famous HL2 gravity gun which turns random objects into deadly ammunition, making it the first online FPS game to heavily utilize physics simulation for gameplay. Besides the standard HL2 weaponry it adds the Stunstick and the Selectable Lightweight Attack Munition (SLAM). The game features a Deathmatch and a Team Deathmatch scenario (Combine vs. Rebel). This game is often included with various Half-Life packs, both offline and online.</desc>
		<image>./images/Half-Life 2 Deathmatch-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Half-Life 2 Deathmatch-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Half-Life 2 Deathmatch-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Half-Life 2 Deathmatch-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Half-Life 2 Deathmatch-boxback.png</boxback>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20041130T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Valve</developer>
		<publisher>Valve</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / 1st person</genre>
		<family>Half-Life</family>
		<lastplayed>20230222T000000</lastplayed>
		<md5>86d73e61fc54b932633e267fa58ba5f9</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230222T112715" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Half-Life Opposing Force.bat</path>
		<name>Half-Life Opposing Force</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20230222T000000</releasedate>
		<players>0</players>
		<lastplayed>20230222T000000</lastplayed>
		<md5>a734c7d8b8e6bef8511f666976c9f960</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230222T112717" />
	</game>
	<game id="304230">
		<path>./Half-Life Blue Shift.bat</path>
		<name>Half-Life: Blue Shift</name>
		<desc>Return to the Black Mesa complex in this additional Half-Life storyline. In this module, you play Barney Calhoun, a security officer working Blue Shift who is present at Black Mesa at the same time as Gordon Freeman.  Your goal is to try to get out of Black Mesa alive as all hell breaks loose and reality is altered around you.

This version can be played stand-alone and also includes the Half-Life High Definition Pack that replaces most of the Half-Life/Opposing Force/Blue Shift player and weapon models and textures with updated high-res models and textures.</desc>
		<image>./images/Half-Life Blue Shift-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Half-Life Blue Shift-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Half-Life Blue Shift-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Half-Life Blue Shift-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Half-Life Blue Shift-boxback.png</boxback>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20010601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Gearbox Software</developer>
		<publisher>Sierra On-Line</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / 1st person</genre>
		<family>Half-Life</family>
		<lastplayed>20230222T000000</lastplayed>
		<md5>c1733b14ea2af99be6afa4c496795e45</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230222T112720" />
	</game>
	<game id="304236">
		<path>./Half-Life Deathmatch Source.bat</path>
		<name>Half-Life: Deathmatch - Source</name>
		<desc>Half-Life Deathmatch: Source is a recreation of the first multiplayer game set in the Half-Life universe.

It features all the classic weapons and most-played maps, now running on the Source engine.

At first, it was released as a free download on Steam only to people who already owned Half-Life 1: Source. It is now available for free to Steam customers who buy the available Half-Life / Source packages.</desc>
		<image>./images/Half-Life Deathmatch Source-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Half-Life Deathmatch Source-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Half-Life Deathmatch Source-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Half-Life Deathmatch Source-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Half-Life Deathmatch Source-boxback.png</boxback>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20050120T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Valve</developer>
		<publisher>Valve</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / 1st person</genre>
		<family>Half-Life</family>
		<lastplayed>20230222T000000</lastplayed>
		<md5>7be2aaea1d0ab68024dfa316821ae4eb</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230222T112723" />
	</game>
	<game id="304246">
		<path>./Half-Life Source.bat</path>
		<name>Half-Life: Source</name>
		<desc>Half-Life: Source is a port of Valve's original acclaimed game  Half-Life  to their new Source engine used for Half-Life 2 .  It was initially only available in the Silver and Gold Edition Steam packages when buying Half-Life 2, and in the  Collector's Edition  retail disc package. Later, it could be bought separately through Valve's Steam game delivery system.

It takes advantage of vertex and pixel shaders to create realistic water effects, and can now portray realistic physics effects. It also has new menus, improved lighting and soft shadows, ragdoll character animations, and a 3D skybox replacing the old 16-bit color prerendered bitmap skies.</desc>
		<image>./images/Half-Life Source-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Half-Life Source-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Half-Life Source-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Half-Life Source-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Half-Life Source-boxback.png</boxback>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20050101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Valve</developer>
		<publisher>Valve</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / 1st person</genre>
		<family>Half-Life</family>
		<lastplayed>20230222T000000</lastplayed>
		<md5>c6dd3099a377ebc9b2ce8f4a0d4a4812</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230222T112725" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lineage II.bat</path>
		<name>Lineage II</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20230222T000000</releasedate>
		<players>0</players>
		<lastplayed>20230222T000000</lastplayed>
		<md5>07e0bf4962156d42f5982d65efd3774c</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230222T112728" />
	</game>
	<game id="316616">
		<path>./Maldita Castilla.win</path>
		<name>Maldita Castilla</name>
		<desc>The kingdom of Castile is cursed. Thou hath been sent forth by thy King to learn of the source of this evil and rid the land of it. God be with thee, Don Ramiro!

Maldita Castilla (Damn Castile) is a side scrolling action game that is, clearly, inspired by such games as Ghosts 'N Goblins, Rygar, Karnov, among others.

You, as Spanish knight Don Ramiro, must move to the right, killing enemies as you go. Along the way, you encounter treasure chests that will help you. At certain points, you must defeat a boss to advance. You are trying to get through all the bosses to find and defeat the source of all this evil plaguing Castile.</desc>
		<image>./images/Maldita Castilla-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Maldita Castilla-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Maldita Castilla-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Maldita Castilla-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<manual>./manuals/Maldita Castilla-manual.pdf</manual>
		<boxback>./images/Maldita Castilla-boxback.png</boxback>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20121212T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Locomalito</developer>
		<publisher>Locomalito</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20210612T000000</lastplayed>
		<gametime>98</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230222T112730" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pinball Arcade.bat</path>
		<name>Pinball Arcade</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20230222T000000</releasedate>
		<players>0</players>
		<lastplayed>20230222T000000</lastplayed>
		<md5>6a1369790a2aa794c54ff700e8c60e09</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230222T112732" />
	</game>
	<game id="326974">
		<path>./Pinball FX3.bat</path>
		<name>Pinball FX3</name>
		<image>./images/Pinball FX3-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Pinball FX3-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Pinball FX3-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Pinball FX3-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Pinball FX3-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Pinball FX3-boxback.png</boxback>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<genre>Pinball</genre>
		<lastplayed>20230222T000000</lastplayed>
		<md5>e58cfe428b9abe799a3f53c72f4d43ee</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230222T112735" />
	</game>
	<game id="332302">
		<path>./Ricochet.bat</path>
		<name>Ricochet</name>
		<desc>Ricochet is a futuristic multiplayer game where you're playing in team match or one-vs-one in battle arenas. Players are jumping on between neon-lit platforms suspended above an abyss, and shoot disks at one another. The main goal is to push the opponent out of the platform. Players can use the horizontal barriers for bouncing their disk, hence the name Ricochet.

The game is an official mod for Half-Life.</desc>
		<image>./images/Ricochet-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Ricochet-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Ricochet-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/Ricochet-boxback.png</boxback>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20001101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Valve</developer>
		<publisher>Valve</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / 3rd person</genre>
		<family>Half-Life</family>
		<lastplayed>20230222T000000</lastplayed>
		<md5>a4876d837f7a9b8cf17837ed417e4457</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230222T112738" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sphere 3 Enchanted World.bat</path>
		<name>Sphere 3 Enchanted World</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20230222T000000</releasedate>
		<players>0</players>
		<lastplayed>20230222T000000</lastplayed>
		<md5>fe58dc0298be105b4a74035a086853a4</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230222T112741" />
	</game>
	<game id="345596">
		<path>./Team Fortress Classic.bat</path>
		<name>Team Fortress Classic</name>
		<desc>Team Fortress Classic is a team-based, multiplayer first-person shooter with nine distinct classes, each with their own abilities and weapons. Most of the matches consist of Capture the Flag-type maps, along with variations such as Assassination/Escort, Territory Control, and more.

Each player is armed with a melee weapon, a couple of firearms and one or two types of grenades. The exact choice of weapons depends on the class chosen. The chosen class also affects walking speed, maximum armor and health, and some special abilities. 

The game started as a modification for Quake, but was later adapted to the engine of Half-Life, originally based on the first Quake engine. Later, it was offered as a stand-alone title.</desc>
		<image>./images/Team Fortress Classic-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Team Fortress Classic-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Team Fortress Classic-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Team Fortress Classic-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Team Fortress Classic-boxback.png</boxback>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19990101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Valve</developer>
		<publisher>Sierra On-Line</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / 1st person</genre>
		<family>Half-Life</family>
		<lastplayed>20230222T000000</lastplayed>
		<md5>4b155dfc541f4a7a5219ba39bd3cbe23</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230222T112744" />
	</game>
	<game id="352290">
		<path>./Warframe.bat</path>
		<name>Warframe</name>
		<desc>Warframe is an online-only third-person action game where the player controls ancient warriors called Tenno in a high-tech, futuristic environment. After centuries they wake up from a cryosleep in a war with the humanoid clones from the Grineer Empire, the Infested who are disfigured creatures affected by the Technocyte virus, and the Corpus, a corporation with robots. To fight back the Tenno are equipped with exo-armour called Warframes. The Tenno is the only playable faction in the game. Another group called Orokin also make an appearance for certain missions. They are soldiers from different factions grouped together. Many of the game elements are derived from the original concept of Dark Sector by the same developer, where they were scrapped before release.</desc>
		<image>./images/Warframe-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Warframe-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Warframe-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Warframe-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Warframe-boxback.png</boxback>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20130325T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Digital Extremes</developer>
		<publisher>Digital Extremes</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / 3rd person</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lastplayed>20230222T000000</lastplayed>
		<md5>5112c085b2553433f8faa16d7d5302c3</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230222T112747" />
	</game>
</gameList>
