<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./Arcana Heart 3.m3u</path>
		<name>Arcana Heart 3</name>
		<desc>A plucky cast of female fighters duke it out on a battlefield with the help of their "Arcana" spirit (who adds to the character's attacks and defense) in this third entry in the all-girls fighting franchise. Arcana Heart 3 combines fast-paced aerial action with a unique cast for an extraordinary fighting experience!


Chaos and disorder are threatening to rip apart the very fabric of Japanese society as planar rifts appear throughout the country. It is suspected that the Drexler Institute, the instigator of the Great War many years ago and creator of the Divine Celestial Weapon, is somehow involved. In the midst of this confusion, a mysterious rumor arises, claiming the existence of wish-granting "Celestial Stones" within the chaotic planar rifts. As a result of these rumors, a number of individuals have converged on Japan in the hopes of obtaining one of these fabled stones – either to seal them away or to see for themselves if rumor is true. Each person has their own reasons for seeking these rare and valuable stones, and they won't let anyone stand in their way, be they foe ... or friend.</desc>
		<image>./images/Arcana Heart 3-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Arcana Heart 3-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Arcana Heart 3-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Arcana Heart 3-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20110419T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Examu</developer>
		<publisher>Aksys Games</publisher>
		<genre>Combat</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<md5>ace2d3cc91c453b2fc48d110a979d252</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T023151" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T010247" />
	</game>
	<game id="25277">
		<path>./Army of TWO The Devils Cartel.m3u</path>
		<name>Army of Two: The Devil's Cartel</name>
		<desc>Army of Two: The Devil's Cartel is a third-person shooter video game developed by the Montreal branch of Visceral Games and released on March 26, 2013 by Electronic Arts for the Xbox 360 and PlayStation 3. It is the third game in the Army of Two series, following 2008's Army of Two and 2010's Army of Two: The 40th Day. The game takes place in Mexico and pits T.W.O. against a ruthless drug cartel known as La Guadaña (Spanish for "the Scythe"). It is the first game in the series to run on the Frostbite 2 game engine, whereas the previous two ran on Unreal Engine 3. The demo for the game was released on March 13, 2013.[3] It was the last game developed by Visceral Montreal.[4]</desc>
		<marquee>./images/Army of TWO The Devils Cartel-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Army of TWO The Devils Cartel-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Army of TWO The Devils Cartel-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20120326T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Electronic Arts</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / 3rd person</genre>
		<family>Army Of Two</family>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<md5>ed8dc4705bf255e54e8bbfb688df16e3</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T151547" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T010347" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Blazing Angels 2 Secret Missions of WWII.m3u</path>
		<name>Blazing Angels 2: Secret Missions of WWII</name>
		<desc>Blazing Angels 2: Secret Missions shows World War II from a different perspective - that of an elite pilot who is part of a secret team. In the game, the player undertakes some of the most dangerous missions in exotic locations all over the globe. As an elite pilot, the player goes from one great adventure to another, while battling the most lethal experimental weapons of the Third Reich.</desc>
		<video>./videos/Blazing Angels 2 Secret Missions of WWII-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Blazing Angels 2 Secret Missions of WWII-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Blazing Angels 2 Secret Missions of WWII-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Blazing Angels 2 Secret Missions of WWII-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20071106T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft Romania</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>0df9e203e4707cfcc7a553e093b6ff66</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T151548" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T010347" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BRAIN CHALLENGE.m3u</path>
		<name>Brain Challenge Deluxe</name>
		<desc>Released in Europe in 2008 and for the PSN in 2009.</desc>
		<marquee>./images/BRAIN CHALLENGE-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/BRAIN CHALLENGE-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>20081205T000000</releasedate>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<md5>33c55cf4430695487eb53ada321b6023</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T151550" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T010447" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Call Of Duty 4 Modern Warfare.m3u</path>
		<name>Call of Duty 4: Modern Warfare</name>
		<desc>A radical leader has executed the president of an unnamed country in the Middle East, and an "Ultranationalist" movement starts a civil war in Russia. The conflicts are seen from the perspectives of a U.S. Force Reconnaissance Marine and a British SAS commando in various locales around the world.</desc>
		<image>./images/Call Of Duty 4 Modern Warfare-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Call Of Duty 4 Modern Warfare-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Call Of Duty 4 Modern Warfare-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Call Of Duty 4 Modern Warfare-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<manual>./manuals/Call Of Duty 4 Modern Warfare-manual.pdf</manual>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20071106T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Infinity Ward</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<md5>78020723f11fe42c1b4a604b9eaef0ca</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T151626" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T010447" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Call of Duty Black Ops II NPUB31054.m3u</path>
		<name>Call of Duty Black Ops II NPUB31054</name>
		<md5>9f34f9b59a9a0b1412f730af84951d0a</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T151627" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T010448" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Call of Duty Black Ops.m3u</path>
		<name>Call of Duty: Black Ops</name>
		<desc>Call of Duty: Black Ops takes place during the Cold War, in The Sixties. The story focuses on CIA-backed clandestine black operations carried out behind enemy lines. These missions take place in various locations around the globe such as the Ural Mountains in central Russia, Cuba, Laos, and Vietnam. The single-player campaign revolves around an experimental Soviet chemical weapon codenamed "Nova-6".</desc>
		<image>./images/Call of Duty Black Ops-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Call of Duty Black Ops-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Call of Duty Black Ops-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Call of Duty Black Ops-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Call of Duty Black Ops-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20101109T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Treyarch</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<md5>39dbe6b656b811b375e041aec4f49811</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T151653" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T010549" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Call of Duty Ghosts.m3u</path>
		<name>Call of Duty: Ghosts</name>
		<desc>Outnumbered and outgunned, but not outmatched. Welcome to Call of Duty®: Ghosts, an extraordinary step forward for one of the largest entertainment franchises of all-time. This new chapter in the Call of Duty® franchise features a fresh dynamic where players are on the side of a crippled nation fighting not for freedom, or liberty, but simply to survive.

Fueling this all new Call of Duty universe, the franchise's ambitious new next-gen engine delivers stunning levels of immersion and performance all while maintaining the speed and fluidity of 60 frames-per-second across all platforms.

Ten years after a devastating mass event, the nation's borders and the balance of global power have been redrawn forever. As what's left of the nation's Special Operations forces, a mysterious group known only as "Ghosts" leads the fight back against a newly emerged, technologically-superior global power.</desc>
		<image>./images/Call of Duty Ghosts-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Call of Duty Ghosts-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Call of Duty Ghosts-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Call of Duty Ghosts-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>20131105T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Infinity Ward</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<md5>1f1c683e477cb7df46cadc9bde0e7882</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T151722" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T010550" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Carnival Island Digital.m3u</path>
		<name>Carnival Island Digital</name>
		<md5>11635a151d37e40f51f11e875ad12b42</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T151723" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T010648" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Cars 2.m3u</path>
		<name>Cars 2</name>
		<desc>Cars 2: The Video Game brings players inside the international training center CHROME (Command Headquarters for Recon Operations and Motorized Espionage), where they choose from more than 20 different characters and train to become world class spies. As part of their international training, they will participate in simulated hazardous missions using high-tech gadgets to evade and slow down adversaries.</desc>
		<image>./images/Cars 2-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Cars 2-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Cars 2-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Cars 2-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Cars 2-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20110621T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Avalanche Software (USA)</developer>
		<publisher>Disney Interactive Studios</publisher>
		<genre>Course</genre>
		<md5>ca3d066079a55a6b81e4d6b768723271</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T023234" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T010649" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Catherine.m3u</path>
		<name>Catherine</name>
		<desc>Vincent likes his girlfriend. Katherine's pretty, smart, and successful. Trouble is, she's starting to talk about long-term commitment, something Vincent's spent his entire life avoiding. Since romantic complications are the last thing he wants to deal with, Vincent meets his friends for their regular night of drinks. Little does he know that he's about to be blindsided by a beautiful, seductive, irresistible freight train named Catherine. Suddenly, he's hung over in bed next to the most beautiful woman he's ever seen, unsure about the previous night's events. Was it just making out, he wonders, or did something more serious happen between them? Should he tell Katherine? Will he ever see Catherine again? Vincent's about to find that a stumble on the staircase of love can turn into a horrific, fatal plummet...</desc>
		<image>./images/Catherine-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Catherine-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Catherine-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Catherine-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Catherine-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20120210T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Deep Silver</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus</publisher>
		<genre>Aventure</genre>
		<md5>c360b05f5d1e6602b4bdbf63f4f98bc2</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T023250" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T010650" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chariot.m3u</path>
		<name>Chariot</name>
		<desc>Chariot is a couch co-op platformer that can be played alone or with a friend. Players take the role of the brave Princess or her faithful Fiancé as they maneuver the departed king's coffin-on-wheels through 25 levels set in 5 vibrant underground environments, with his majesty's ghost giving them a piece of his mind every step of the way. Filled to the brim with emergent physics-based gameplay, Chariot offers hours of exciting exploration, fast-paced ride sequences and mountains upon mountains of loot! Notice: We highly recommend playing Chariot with a controller.</desc>
		<marquee>./images/Chariot-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Chariot-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Chariot-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20141112T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Frima Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Frima Studios</publisher>
		<genre>Aventure</genre>
		<md5>9c05ea238292e7998cdb9269cd645188</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T023258" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T010748" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./DiRT 3.m3u</path>
		<name>DiRT 3</name>
		<desc>The acclaimed off-road racing franchise returns in this third series entry. DiRT 3 delivers mud, sweat and gears the world over: from the intense weather-beaten rally stages of Europe, Africa and the US, to executing performance driving showcases and career challenges where car control is pushed to spectacular limits. The game boasts more cars, more locations, more routes and more events than any other game in the series, including over 50 rally cars representing the very best from five decades of the sport.</desc>
		<video>./videos/DiRT 3-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/DiRT 3-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/DiRT 3-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/DiRT 3-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20110524T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Codemasters</developer>
		<publisher>Codemasters</publisher>
		<genre>Course</genre>
		<md5>c2df009ea6f6148a322d3088ead81ffc</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T151725" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T010749" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./DiRT Showdown.m3u</path>
		<name>Dirt: Showdown</name>
		<desc>An expansion on the rough-riding racing action of Dirt 3's gymkhana competition, Dirt Showdown offers three modes focused on the wilder aspects of off-road driving: Race, Showdown and Demolition!</desc>
		<marquee>./images/DiRT Showdown-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/DiRT Showdown-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20120529T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Codemasters</developer>
		<publisher>Codemasters</publisher>
		<genre>Course</genre>
		<md5>683a507214a64af5c5b28d37234edb7c</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T023309" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T010749" />
	</game>
	<game id="25257">
		<path>./Disney Epic Mickey 2 The Power of Two.m3u</path>
		<name>Epic Mickey : Le Retour des Héros</name>
		<image>./images/Disney Epic Mickey 2 The Power of Two-image.jpg</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Disney Epic Mickey 2 The Power of Two-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Disney Epic Mickey 2 The Power of Two-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20121118T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Disney Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Junction Point</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<family>Mickey Mouse</family>
		<md5>a2924ec354081421dd539010e86c32a1</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T151746" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T010750" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Disney Universe.m3u</path>
		<name>Disney Universe</name>
		<desc>Disney Universe is an off-the-wall non-stop action adventure where Disney worlds and characters mix up for the first time. Suit up in iconic costumes and face challenges in legendary Disney worlds.  Defeat enemies, collect coins and powerups, unlock new costumes and explore with friends as you battle in a mix-up of worlds inspired by numerous Disney and Pixar films.</desc>
		<image>./images/Disney Universe-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Disney Universe-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Disney Universe-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20111025T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Eurocom</developer>
		<publisher>Disney Interactive Studios</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<md5>99223b99caec458a3cddadd848631233</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T023319" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T010850" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./DYNASTY WARRIORS 7 Empires.m3u</path>
		<name>Dynasty Warriors 7: Empires</name>
		<desc>Dynasty Warriors 7 Empires is a Beat-'Em-Up game, developed by Omega Force and published by TECMO KOEI GAMES CO., LTD., which was released in 2013.</desc>
		<thumbnail>./images/DYNASTY WARRIORS 7 Empires-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20130226T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>TECMO KOEI GAMES CO., LTD.</developer>
		<publisher>TECMO KOEI GAMES CO., LTD.</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<md5>e07c43ec66ea21170de5628b8cdea6d4</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T151748" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T010850" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./DYNASTY WARRIORS 8 Empires Free Alliances Version.m3u</path>
		<name>DYNASTY WARRIORS 8 Empires Free Alliances Version</name>
		<md5>80b710f108bdc1c5c074a0cbf1f5f9ec</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T151749" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T010949" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./DYNASTY WARRIORS 8 Empires.m3u</path>
		<name>Dynasty Warriors 8 Empires</name>
		<desc>Dynasty Warriors 8 (??????7 Shin Sangokumus? 7?, known in Japan as Shin Sangokumusou 7) is a hack and slash video game and the eighth official installment of the Dynasty Warriors series. It is developed by Omega Force and published by Tecmo Koei. The story is based on the Chinese writer Luo Guanzhong's historical novel Romance of the Three Kingdoms. The game was unveiled on October 30, 2012 via Jump Magazine and released on February 28, 2013 for the PlayStation 3 in Japan.[3] On April 3, 2013, it was confirmed by Tecmo Koei that there would be an overseas release for both North America and Europe in July 2013. It was released on both PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360 for both physical and digital release. The option of English and Japanese voice overs also return, where there is also an option to change the subtitles to English, French or German.

Having more than 82 characters featured in the game,[13][14] the game largely based its system from Dynasty Warriors 7 and instead focused on adding more content for replayability as well as several tweaks in the combat system.[15] The game is followed by two expansions. The first, Dynasty Warriors 8: Xtreme Legends was released for PlayStation 3 on November 28, 2013 in Japan and on 2014 in North America and Europe. Versions for PlayStation Vita and PlayStation 4 are developed as well, both of which package the expansion with the original version and are released under the title of Dynasty Warriors 8: Xtreme Legends Complete Edition.[7] The PlayStation Vita version was released on the same day as PlayStation 3, while the PlayStation 4 version was released as a launch title for the console in Japan, on March 25, 2014 in North America, and on April 4, 2014 for Europe.[16] The PC port for Complete Edition released on May 13, 2014. The second expansion, Dynasty Warriors 8: Empires was released for the PlayStation 3, PlayStation 4, and Xbox One on November 20, 2014 in Japan,[1] with North American and European versions released in February 2015 for PlayStation 4, PlayStation 3, Xbox One and Microsoft Windows (via Steam).</desc>
		<marquee>./images/DYNASTY WARRIORS 8 Empires-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/DYNASTY WARRIORS 8 Empires-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>20141120T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Omega Force</developer>
		<publisher>Koei Tecmo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<md5>0c585dc173f89c449d9cb7e83cb482be</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T151751" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T010950" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./DYNASTY WARRIORS GUNDAM Reborn.m3u</path>
		<name>Dynasty Warriors: Gundam Reborn</name>
		<desc>Gundam comes to life in the classic Dynasty Warriors series like never before! Experience the thrill of reliving your favorite epic battles from the Gundam Universe in epic battlefields with hundreds of opponents! Play as your favorite Mobile Suits from series such as Gundam Seed and Gundam Unicorn for the first time ever! Features over 100 playable Mobile Suits and thrilling story episodes for each series represented!</desc>
		<marquee>./images/DYNASTY WARRIORS GUNDAM Reborn-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/DYNASTY WARRIORS GUNDAM Reborn-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/DYNASTY WARRIORS GUNDAM Reborn-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20140701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Omega Force</developer>
		<publisher>Namco Bandai Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<md5>c9f45eea37ccd78a2a5595c85423c8fd</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T151753" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T011051" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./EA SPORTS MMA.m3u</path>
		<name>EA Sports MMA</name>
		<desc>EA Sports MMA is a fighting video game which was published by EA Sports and developed by EA Tiburon from 2008 to 2010. It was released for the PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360[3] on October 19, 2010 in North America and October 22, 2010 everywhere else. Online services have been shut down since April 13, 2012[4] for the PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360.[5]

EA SPORTS MMA brings the authenticity of the world's most intense combat sport home like never before. Choose from the world's top fighters or climb the ranks of the worldwide circuit with your created prodigy to become the ultimate MMA champion. Travel the globe and learn a multitude of fighting techniques and skills from masters in each discipline. Select from various weight classes, rule sets, and take on all challengers in multiple cage types or a ring. The challenge continues online with the most robust offering for any MMA videogame, including the ability to create and share custom fighters, prize fights, and more. Are you ready? Let's get it on!</desc>
		<image>./images/EA SPORTS MMA-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/EA SPORTS MMA-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/EA SPORTS MMA-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/EA SPORTS MMA-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/EA SPORTS MMA-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20101019T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>EA Tiburon</developer>
		<publisher>EA Sports</publisher>
		<genre>Combat</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<md5>6fc4bbbf7dfca42db76c4e39ee7e1996</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T151754" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T011052" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Family Guy Back To The Multiverse.m3u</path>
		<name>Family Guy: Back to the Multiverse</name>
		<desc>Family Guy: Back to the Multiverse is a third-person cooperative gameplay video game set to be released on November 20, 2012 in North America for Xbox 360, PlayStation 3 and PC. It's based on the Family Guy television series, most notably the episode Road to the Multiverse, and is also a continuation of The Big Bang Theory. It is rated M for Mature for blood, violence, drug use, mature humor, and sexual content/themes. This game also features the return of Stewie's evil half-brother Bertram, who was killed in the show.</desc>
		<image>./images/Family Guy Back To The Multiverse-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Family Guy Back To The Multiverse-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Family Guy Back To The Multiverse-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20121120T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Heavy Iron Studio</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<md5>1ab697e9800c9a260b5ff4fee2688dc3</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T151803" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T011150" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Fast  Furious Showdown.m3u</path>
		<name>Fast &amp; Furious: Showdown</name>
		<marquee>./images/Fast  Furious Showdown-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Fast  Furious Showdown-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>20130521T000000</releasedate>
		<genre>Course</genre>
		<md5>7f9af60c004f70f241573c318e993610</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T151804" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T011151" />
	</game>
	<game id="25255">
		<path>./Fist of the North Star Kens Rage 2.m3u</path>
		<name>Fist of the North Star : Ken's Rage 2</name>
		<desc>Fist of the North Star: Ken's Rage 2 is a beat'em all on PS3 adapted from the manga Ken the survivor. Through battles including an impressive number of enemies, the player relives the entire adventure of the heir of Hokuto Shinken.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20121220T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tecmo</developer>
		<publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<md5>67a89661ba262bdc0a6a2860187339c7</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T151806" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T011152" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./HEAVY FIRE SHATTERED SPEAR.m3u</path>
		<name>Heavy Fire: Shattered Spear</name>
		<thumbnail>./images/HEAVY FIRE SHATTERED SPEAR-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<developer>Teyon</developer>
		<publisher>Mastiff</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<md5>b677642e3ae4281264a1e3afabf60a09</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T151808" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T011252" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Hot Shots Golf Out of Bounds.m3u</path>
		<name>Hot Shots Golf: Out of Bounds</name>
		<desc>Hot Shots Golf makes its first appearance on PlayStation 3 with online support for multiplayer competition and a new shot system. The framework is otherwise the same as in previous games in the series, which began on the original PlayStation in 1998. Cutesy characters with large heads and whimsical expressions can compete on six new courses filled with onlookers, animals, and other animated surprises. The new venues take place along a coast, on a mountain range, in the woods, and across a desert. The shot system by default forgoes the horizontal power meter in favor of a swing-based approach in which players use visual cues to time their backswings and follow-throughs. Traditionalists can still, however, revert back to the old swing system from the options menu.

Once again a number of customization features are available to personalize each of the game's 15 characters and six caddies. By competing in different events, players can unlock new equipment such as enhanced clubs and balls. Hot Shots Golf: Out of Bounds also includes a robust online component, with the ability to create custom tournaments supporting up to 50 players. Online avatars can be tweaked with 300 visual options, including hairstyles, masks, clothing, and more. Players can also send messages to friends, or visit the PlayStation Store to purchase new courses, clubs, characters, and other features. Key play modes include Versus, Training, Tournament, Stroke, and Match Play. Detailed statistics are tracked throughout each mode and challenge, from best average score and driving distance to average putt length and putting accuracy.</desc>
		<image>./images/Hot Shots Golf Out of Bounds-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Hot Shots Golf Out of Bounds-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Hot Shots Golf Out of Bounds-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Hot Shots Golf Out of Bounds-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Hot Shots Golf Out of Bounds-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<releasedate>20080318T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SCE Santa Monica</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Sport</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<md5>769f288e55ea6b34cfa0df71c0ec0f54</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T151836" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T011252" />
	</game>
	<game id="25901">
		<path>./Hot Wheels Worlds Best Driver.m3u</path>
		<name>Hot Wheels World's Best Driver</name>
		<desc>Hot Wheels World?s Best Driver lets players get behind the wheel of thrilling Hot Wheels vehicles while joining the elite ranks of Team Hot Wheels. Gameplay includes competition in dozens of unique, fast-paced, re-playable challenges all highlighting the different driving styles of Team Hot Wheels: the speed record-breaking Green Team, the show-stopping stunts of the Red Team, the high-tech precision of the Blue Team and the world record-breaking jumps of the Yellow Team. The game pushes players to their limits to see if they have what it takes to become the World?s Best Driver.</desc>
		<image>./images/Hot Wheels Worlds Best Driver-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Hot Wheels Worlds Best Driver-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Hot Wheels Worlds Best Driver-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<developer>Warner Bros. Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Warner Bros. Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<family>Hot Wheels</family>
		<md5>333ff7050a5a35bb73ec0382b3c77c6b</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T023410" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T011351" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Injustice Gods Among Us.m3u</path>
		<name>Injustice: Gods Among Us</name>
		<desc>Injustice: Gods Among Us debuts as a bold new fighting game franchise that introduces a deep, original story featuring a large cast of favorite DC Comics icons such as Batman, Harley Quinn, Solomon Grundy, Superman, The Flash, Wonder Woman and many others. Set in a world where the lines between good and evil are blurred, players will experience heroes and villains engaging in epic battles on a massive scale.</desc>
		<marquee>./images/Injustice Gods Among Us-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Injustice Gods Among Us-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Injustice Gods Among Us-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20130416T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>NetherRealm Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Warner Bros. Interactive Entertainment Inc.</publisher>
		<md5>c38c0d83b07198425f85551bee45582a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T151853" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T011352" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jetpack Joyride.m3u</path>
		<name>Jetpack Joyride</name>
		<desc>You're going for a ride - from the creators of FRUIT NINJA! Join Barry as he breaks in to a secret laboratory to commandeer the experimental jetpacks from the clutches of science evildoers. After lift-off, simply touch the screen to ascend and release to descend, raining bullets, bubbles, rainbows and lasers downwards as you fly towards higher and higher scores!</desc>
		<image>./images/Jetpack Joyride-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Jetpack Joyride-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Jetpack Joyride-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Jetpack Joyride-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20121231T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Big Ant Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Halfbrick Studios</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>13fa0c473a05c425d9e2a1fd2fade34a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T023431" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T011353" />
	</game>
	<game id="24868">
		<path>./JSTARS Victory VS.m3u</path>
		<name>J-stars Victory Vs</name>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20140319T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Spike Chunsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<md5>cb216267f2f491e00f049b56146f7932</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T151854" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T011451" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Killzone3 Behind the Scenes.m3u</path>
		<name>Killzone3 Behind the Scenes</name>
		<md5>dc7aecf3488d381008af889802346ffd</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T023434" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T011451" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Killzone3 Multiplayer.m3u</path>
		<name>Killzone3 Multiplayer</name>
		<md5>6fbcff476242c6bd9603954861a08671</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T151856" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T011452" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./LEGO Batman 2 DC Super Heroes.m3u</path>
		<name>LEGO Batman 2: DC Super Heroes</name>
		<desc>LEGO Batman 2: DC Super Heroes is an action game and the sequel to LEGO Batman: The Videogame. Just like the first game it draws elements from the Batman universe but built entirely in LEGO-style bricks. It starts when a "Man of the Year" award ceremony in Gotham City is interrupted by the Joker and a gang of bandits. Bruce Wayne is a candidate for the award and changes into Batman to pursue them, teaming up with members of the Justice League.</desc>
		<image>./images/LEGO Batman 2 DC Super Heroes-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/LEGO Batman 2 DC Super Heroes-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/LEGO Batman 2 DC Super Heroes-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/LEGO Batman 2 DC Super Heroes-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/LEGO Batman 2 DC Super Heroes-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20120619T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Traveller's Tales Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>WB Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<md5>d8c96605edb8fb584891d844da9a1a36</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T151930" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T011551" />
	</game>
	<game id="25155">
		<path>./LEGO Harry Potter Years 57.m3u</path>
		<name>Lego Harry Potter: Years 5–7</name>
		<image>./images/LEGO Harry Potter Years 57-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/LEGO Harry Potter Years 57-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/LEGO Harry Potter Years 57-marquee.png</marquee>
		<fanart>./images/LEGO Harry Potter Years 57-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<developer>Warner Bros. Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>TT Games</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<family>LEGO</family>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<md5>ff31c3ec663fdda9fe343b6f02eaaa9f</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T151959" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T011551" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./LEGO Jurassic World.m3u</path>
		<name>LEGO Jurassic World</name>
		<desc>Following the epic storylines of Jurassic Park, The Lost World: Jurassic Park and Jurassic Park III, as well as the highly anticipated Jurassic World, LEGO® Jurassic World™  is the first videogame where players will be able to relive and experience all four Jurassic films.  Reimagined in LEGO form and told in TT Games’ signature classic LEGO humour, the thrilling adventure recreates unforgettable scenes and action sequences from the films, allowing fans to play through key moments and giving them the opportunity to fully explore the expansive grounds of Isla Nublar and Isla Sorna.</desc>
		<marquee>./images/LEGO Jurassic World-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/LEGO Jurassic World-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/LEGO Jurassic World-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20150630T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Warner Home Video Games</developer>
		<publisher>Warner Home Video Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>2ede392b9ba767fc60c072b40814b353</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T152019" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T011552" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./LEGO MARVEL Super Heroes.m3u</path>
		<name>LEGO Marvel Super Heroes</name>
		<desc>Marvel Super Heroes are assembling for an action-packed, brick-smashing good time! LEGO Marvel Super Heroes offers an original storyline in which Nick Fury calls upon Iron Man, the Hulk, Thor, Spider-Man, Wolverine and other heroes spanning the Marvel Universe to save Earth from such threats as the vengeance of Loki and the hunger of Galactus, Devourer of the Worlds. LEGO and Marvel fans will enjoy classic LEGO video game adventure and humor, while playing as their favorite Marvel characters.

In LEGO Marvel Super Heroes, players will unlock more than 100 characters from across the Marvel Universe, including fan favorites like Spider-Man, Iron Man, Wolverine, Captain America, the Hulk, Thor, Black Widow, Hawkeye, Deadpool, Loki and Galactus! The game will pack in a plethora of super-cool character abilities, combat-like action sequences, epic battle scenes, puzzle-solving and a unique story told with playful LEGO humor.</desc>
		<marquee>./images/LEGO MARVEL Super Heroes-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/LEGO MARVEL Super Heroes-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/LEGO MARVEL Super Heroes-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20131022T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Traveller's Tales</developer>
		<publisher>Warner Bros. Interactive Entertainment Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<md5>224d65cbd731f7fdce3b6604dcbf3f5a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T152021" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T011652" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./LEGO The Hobbit.m3u</path>
		<name>LEGO The Hobbit</name>
		<desc>LEGO: The Hobbit is an adventure game based off of Peter Jackson's trilogy of Hobbit movies inspired by J. R. R. Tolkien's The Hobbit.</desc>
		<marquee>./images/LEGO The Hobbit-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/LEGO The Hobbit-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/LEGO The Hobbit-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<releasedate>20140408T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Traveller's Tales</developer>
		<publisher>Warner,wb</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<md5>6d72e6e4128b906ca2c3c8108ff16253</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T023508" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T011653" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./LittleBigPlanet 3 .m3u</path>
		<name>LittleBigPlanet 3</name>
		<desc>LittleBigPlanet 3 is a puzzle-platformer video game developed by Sumo Digital for the PlayStation 3 and PlayStation 4. It was released worldwide through November and December 2014, and it is the third entry in the main LittleBigPlanet series, sixth entry overall. It was announced at Sony's E3 2014 media briefing on 9 June 2014. It was developed primarily by Sumo Digital, with XDev and Media Molecule assisting in an undisclosed capacity.[7]

LittleBigPlanet 3 received generally positive reviews upon release. Critics praised the visuals, the create mode, and the many new gameplay elements, such as the addition of the new characters. The game did however draw criticism for its technical issues.</desc>
		<image>./images/LittleBigPlanet 3 -image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/LittleBigPlanet 3 -video.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail>./images/LittleBigPlanet 3 -thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20141126T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sumo Digital</developer>
		<publisher>SCEI</publisher>
		<genre>Plate-formes</genre>
		<md5>797e120f62794bcbacbd5122eb8ca23d</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T152046" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T011752" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./LittleBigPlanet Karting  Digital.m3u</path>
		<name>LittleBigPlanet Karting  Digital</name>
		<md5>5808fa3dac5e79631d3f3342d6621484</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T152048" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T011752" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./LittleBigPlanet.m3u</path>
		<name>LittleBigPlanet</name>
		<desc>Imagine a world that's yours to shape, build and explore. Imagine the possibilities, then jump head first into the reality. LittleBigPlanet puts the power of absolute creation into your own hands. If you can see it, you can enhance it. If you can't see it, you can invent it. 

The LittleBigPlanet experience starts with players learning about their character's powers to interact physically with the environment. There are places to explore, creative resources to collect and puzzles to solve - all requiring a combination of brains and collaborative teamwork. As soon as players begin, their creative skills will grow and they will soon be ready to start creating and modifying their surroundings - the first step to sharing them with the whole community. 

Players can make their world as open or as secretive to explore as they like. When it's ready, they can invite anyone within the LittleBigPlanet community to come and explore their patch - or can go and explore everybody else's.</desc>
		<image>./images/LittleBigPlanet-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/LittleBigPlanet-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/LittleBigPlanet-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/LittleBigPlanet-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/LittleBigPlanet-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20081027T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Media Molecule</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Plate-formes</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<md5>d42020d78c8c3e581634c3ca61114212</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T023643" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T011753" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./LittleBigPlanet2 Digital Version.m3u</path>
		<name>LittleBigPlanet2 Digital Version</name>
		<md5>a40e6583086af6a4bea545673ce646f5</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T152049" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T011753" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./LittleBigPlanet3 Digital Version.m3u</path>
		<name>LittleBigPlanet3 Digital Version</name>
		<md5>a821569669ab70a94b2326831fa468e6</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T152051" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T011753" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Modern Warfare 3.m3u</path>
		<name>Call of Duty: Modern Warfare 3</name>
		<desc>Call of Duty: Modern Warfare 3 (stylized as Call of Duty: MW3) is a 2011 first-person shooter video game, developed by Infinity Ward and Sledgehammer Games (Treyarch for the Wii version), with development assistance from Raven Software, and published by Activision. It is the third installment in the Modern Warfare saga, a direct sequel to 2009's Call of Duty: Modern Warfare 2, and the eighth Call of Duty installment.

The game was released worldwide in November 2011 on Microsoft Windows, Xbox 360, PlayStation 3,[8] and Wii,[7] with a separate version for Nintendo DS developed by n-Space. In Japan, Square Enix handled the installment with a separate subtitled and dubbed version, as they did for Call of Duty: Black Ops. Within 24 hours of going on sale, the game sold 6.5 million copies in the U.S. and UK alone and grossed $400 million, making it the biggest entertainment launch of all time,[9][10][11] until it was surpassed by Call of Duty: Black Ops II in November 2012.</desc>
		<marquee>./images/Modern Warfare 3-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Modern Warfare 3-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Modern Warfare 3-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<releasedate>20111108T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Infinity Ward</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<md5>7fd80311c7488185eaae5f9c4ae5231f</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T152052" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T011855" />
	</game>
	<game id="25995">
		<path>./Mortal Kombat II.m3u</path>
		<name>Mortal Kombat II</name>
		<desc>Mortal Kombat II, is a fighting game on Playstation 3. Combos, fatalities and other special moves, these are the ingredients that underpin the success of a game renowned for the violence of its confrontations. The player embodies one of 12 characters and must defeat all of his direct competitors one by one to win the tournament and put an end to the reign of the evil Shao Kahn.</desc>
		<image>./images/Mortal Kombat II-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Mortal Kombat II-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Mortal Kombat II-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Mortal Kombat II-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Mortal Kombat II-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20070412T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Midway</developer>
		<publisher>Midway</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<family>Mortal Kombat</family>
		<md5>35cc4e37cb3a978a0df624f0967d02ba</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T152054" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T011855" />
		<boxback>./images/Mortal Kombat II-boxback.png</boxback>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mortal Kombat vs. DC Universe.m3u</path>
		<name>Mortal Kombat vs. DC Universe</name>
		<desc>For the first time ever Scorpion, Sub-Zero and the Mortal Kombat warriors battle with Batman, Superman and other popular DC Universe Super Heroes. Choose your side and challenge your opponents with a new fighting system including Freefall Kombat and Klose Kombat along with dynamic multi-tiered environments. Plus, pick your favorite character from MK or DCU and pursue a fighting adventure in the new single player mode with an intertwined storyline and two unique perspectives.</desc>
		<image>./images/Mortal Kombat vs. DC Universe-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Mortal Kombat vs. DC Universe-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Mortal Kombat vs. DC Universe-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Mortal Kombat vs. DC Universe-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Mortal Kombat vs. DC Universe-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20081116T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Midway Games</developer>
		<publisher>Midway Games</publisher>
		<genre>Combat</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<md5>71d06f0ccf708edd7483828a1d814fb9</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T152122" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T011955" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mortal Kombat.m3u</path>
		<name>Mortal Kombat</name>
		<desc>Prepare yourself to reenter the tournament in the triumphant return of Mortal Kombat. A complete reboot of the franchise, this latest iteration combines all-new mature oriented fighter gameplay with a deep story mode, improved graphics and game technology and new game modes to create a Mortal Kombat play experience like none before it. Feature details include: a storyline that takes players back to the original tournament, 4 player tag-team kombat, 3D TV compatibility, fatalities presented in graphic detail never imagined in earlier releases, enhanced online functionality and more. 

Having literally defined the mature game category, Mortal Kombat makes a triumphant return to its violent roots in the fastest and most brutal installment to date. Fighting game players will receive the Mortal Kombat they've been asking for, with Fatalities presented in more detail than ever before. 

After centuries of Mortal Kombat, Emperor Shao Kahn has finally defeated Raiden and his allies. Faced with extinction, Raiden has one last chance to save Earthrealm. To undo the Emperor's victory, he must strike Shao Kahn where he is vulnerable… the Past.</desc>
		<image>./images/Mortal Kombat-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Mortal Kombat-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Mortal Kombat-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Mortal Kombat-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Mortal Kombat-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Mortal Kombat-boxback.png</boxback>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20110419T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>NetherRealm Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Warner Bros. Interactive Entertainment Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Combat</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<md5>6fa89be864a4244664a79687c1bb3f4a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230215T184835" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T011956" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./MOTORSTORM 3D RIFT.m3u</path>
		<name>MOTORSTORM 3D RIFT</name>
		<md5>fa019bf7e1a0db612f7ebc3695e6d7e4</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T152124" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T012055" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./MOTORSTORM APOCALYPSE Digital Edition.m3u</path>
		<name>MOTORSTORM APOCALYPSE Digital Edition</name>
		<md5>a1ffa0214ec9121e7145bde5d43ab864</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T152126" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T012055" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Naughty Bear Gold Edition.m3u</path>
		<name>Naughty Bear Gold Edition</name>
		<desc>Naughty Bear is a third-person shooter/action video game. Players control the eponymous bear as they use various things to earn "Naughty Points", with extra points being given for random missions.
 
The game is set on a paradisiacal island where teddy bears live in harmony. The main character, Naughty Bear, is a shabby teddy bear who has a tendency to be mischievous, which earns him the dislike of the other bears. Like the other teddy bears, he does not speak but instead conveys his emotions through a variety of sounds and facial expressions. His actions are influenced by an unseen narrator with a demeanor reminiscent of that of a young children's television show host.</desc>
		<marquee>./images/Naughty Bear Gold Edition-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Naughty Bear Gold Edition-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/Naughty Bear Gold Edition-boxback.png</boxback>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20101109T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Artificial Mind and Movement</developer>
		<publisher>505 Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20230301T114404</lastplayed>
		<md5>fe6ae2c3533d6c9caf015ca01eb14121</md5>
		<gametime>225</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230215T184930" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T012155" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Naughty Bear Panic in Paradise.m3u</path>
		<name>Naughty Bear: Panic in Paradise</name>
		<image>./images/Naughty Bear Panic in Paradise-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Naughty Bear Panic in Paradise-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Naughty Bear Panic in Paradise-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Naughty Bear Panic in Paradise-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20121008T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Behaviour Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>505 Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<md5>9ce5713f07c39ced3b28fa4d2b2f7f98</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T152128" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T012155" />
		<boxback>./images/Naughty Bear Panic in Paradise-boxback.png</boxback>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Need for Speed Hot Pursuit.m3u</path>
		<name>Need for Speed: Hot Pursuit</name>
		<desc>Need for Speed Hot Pursuit players will experience the thrill of the chase and the rush of the escape as they play through full careers as both a cop and a racer solo or connected. The blistering speeds, brutal busts and heart-stopping getaways are all connected via Need for Speed Autolog. This network not only connects friends for epic head-to head pursuits and races, but also enables players to compare performances and stats, thereby setting the stage for the ultimate in friendly competition.</desc>
		<marquee>./images/Need for Speed Hot Pursuit-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Need for Speed Hot Pursuit-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20101116T000000</releasedate>
		<genre>Course</genre>
		<md5>262c3c850d807b62d069581115d575e6</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T152135" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T012156" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./NFL Blitz.m3u</path>
		<name>NFL Blitz</name>
		<desc>The hits of Blitz will rattle you once again in this revival of the classic, action-packed gridiron sports franchise.</desc>
		<image>./images/NFL Blitz-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/NFL Blitz-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/NFL Blitz-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>20120103T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tiburon</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Plate-formes</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<md5>6d67b5f4cff3bb4fafdf1a4ddde76f54</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230215T185023" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T012157" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./NHL 13.m3u</path>
		<name>NHL 13</name>
		<desc>NHL 13 is an ice hockey video game developed by EA Canada published by EA Sports. It is the 22nd installment of the NHL series and was released on September 11, 2012 in North America, Europe as well as Australia and New Zealand. The game was released on the PlayStation 3 and the Xbox 360, featuring Philadelphia Flyers forward Claude Giroux on the cover.[1] The game was featured at the Electronic Entertainment Expo 2012 (E3 2012), which took place between June 5–7, 2012. The demo of the game was released on August 21–22, 2012, at the Xbox Live Marketplace and the PlayStation Store.[4]

There was a vote deciding which player would be on the NHL 13 cover. Anybody could vote on the player(s) they wished to see on the cover of the game. The vote started on March 29, 2012 with 60 NHL players in a single-elimination voting with two players in each match-up, and was closed on June 4, receiving over 25 million votes worldwide.[5] On June 20, Claude Giroux was named the winner, over Pekka Rinne at the 2012 NHL Awards in Las Vegas.[6]

An exclusive "Stanley Cup Collector's Edition" was also released, apart from the actual NHL 13 game. The Collector's Edition includes five random Hockey Ultimate Team (HUT) player packs from the two 2012 Stanley Cup Finals teams; a Gold Jumbo HUT pack including legend Wayne Gretzky; and a boost pack featuring the CCM RBZ stick.[7]

Just like in NHL 12, Gary Thorne (play-by-play) and Bill Clement (color) provide commentary for NHL 13.[8]

This year, for the first time, two playable female characters, Hayley Wickenheiser and Angela Ruggiero have been added.[9] In NHL 12, users could create female characters, but there were no real-life players.[10]

On September 20, Gamesindustry.biz reported that NHL 13 had posted the best first week sales in the franchise's history.[11]</desc>
		<marquee>./images/NHL 13-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/NHL 13-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>20120911T000000</releasedate>
		<genre>Sport</genre>
		<md5>7cc92c51c03385c0d981f32436b03b03</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230215T185026" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T012257" />
	</game>
	<game id="24704">
		<path>./ONE PIECE PIRATE WARRIORS 3.m3u</path>
		<name>One Piece : Pirate Warriors 3</name>
		<desc>A beat'em all action game , One Piece: Pirate Warriors 3 takes place in the manga universe. The game offers missions in which you must conquer territories and capture points to prevent the enemy from advancing.</desc>
		<fanart>./images/ONE PIECE PIRATE WARRIORS 3-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>20150326T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tecmo</developer>
		<publisher>OMEGA Force</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<family>One Piece</family>
		<md5>8337d42eb81fc4b957151d37a1b67a4f</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T152141" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T012257" />
	</game>
	<game id="25722">
		<path>./PACMAN and the Ghostly Adventures 2.m3u</path>
		<name>Pac-Man and the Ghostly Adventures 2</name>
		<desc>Pac-Man and the Ghostly Adventures 2 is a 3D platform game based on the cartoon TV series of same name and it is the sequel to Pac-Man and the Ghostly Adventures. Betrayus, lord of the ghosts, and his servants come up with a plan to let Pac-Man steal the repository holding the Pac world bodies of all the ghosts in the Netherworld. It is now up to you to thwart this evil plan.

Pac-Man can enter two new modes:
PacKong: transforms you in to a ape like creature with great strength;
PacZilla: this transforms you into a giant.</desc>
		<marquee>./images/PACMAN and the Ghostly Adventures 2-marquee.png</marquee>
		<fanart>./images/PACMAN and the Ghostly Adventures 2-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<releasedate>20141014T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Monkey Bar Games</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<family>Pac-Man</family>
		<md5>aa738f522ad0c89efe1082169d722173</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T152156" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T012356" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./PAIN.m3u</path>
		<name>Greg Hastings Paintball 2</name>
		<image>./images/PAIN-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/PAIN-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/PAIN-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20110614T000000</releasedate>
		<md5>914bd0c5cfc9b266153155de4b7c070a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T152213" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T012357" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Persona 4 Arena Ultimax.m3u</path>
		<name>Persona 4 Arena Ultimax</name>
		<desc>In Persona 4 Arena Ultimax, the characters from Persona 4 and Persona 3 once again find themselves teaming up to face off in the P-1 Climax, a series of battles which must be won before the world ends. The original cast of characters from Persona 3 and 4 are back to discover the mastermind behind the whole tournament, while a few new faces join the fight, including Junpei Iori, Yukari Takeba, Rise Kujikawa, and more. But standing in their way is the dual katana-wielding Sho Minazuki, a huge threat to everyone involved in the P-1 Climax. Worse yet, there's a Sho lookalike who can wield a Persona...</desc>
		<image>./images/Persona 4 Arena Ultimax-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Persona 4 Arena Ultimax-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Persona 4 Arena Ultimax-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Persona 4 Arena Ultimax-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Persona 4 Arena Ultimax-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Persona 4 Arena Ultimax-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20140930T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Atlus</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus</publisher>
		<genre>Combat</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<md5>7a77ff8bff4973ad4ef5022e2e22729e</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230215T185320" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T012358" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Persona 4 ARENA.m3u</path>
		<name>Persona 4 Arena</name>
		<desc>Two months after the ending of the hit RPG Persona 4, a new threat has emerged in Persona 4 Arena! 

During Golden Week, a new rumor begins spreading through town about a mysterious TV program, the P-1 Grand Prix. Visible if you look into a turned-off TV on a rainy night, this fighting tournament broadcasts high school friends fighting one another to the bitter end. When Yu Narukami and the others test this rumor, they see their friend Teddie announcing the beginning of the show: "May the manliest of all men come on down!" With that, the participants are shown, one by one... The Investigation Team is horrified to see their own faces introduced with twisted nicknames. The members of the Investigation Team decide to dive into the TV once again to solve the case! What is behind the mysterious TV show? 

Jump into the next chapter of the story as Persona 4 enters a new genre in this 2D fighting game from the dream team of ATLUS and Arc System Works, made to be enjoyed by fighting game beginners and experts alike!</desc>
		<marquee>./images/Persona 4 ARENA-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Persona 4 ARENA-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Persona 4 ARENA-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<manual>./manuals/Persona 4 ARENA-manual.pdf</manual>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20120807T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Atlus</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus</publisher>
		<genre>Combat</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<md5>dd2fce0c8ae23a30f386e17895b7b888</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T152222" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T012400" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./PixelJunk 4am  Live Viewer.m3u</path>
		<name>PixelJunk 4am  Live Viewer</name>
		<md5>5b113a793f496ddf7823a255679fcdbc</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T152224" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T012457" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./PixelJunk Eden.m3u</path>
		<name>PixelJunk Eden</name>
		<desc>Utterly unique and spellbindingly beautiful, PixelJunk Eden welcomes you to a psychedelic world unlike anything you’ve ever experienced before. 

As a tiny, silk-spinning “grimp,” it is up to you to collect the lost “Spectra” that have been scattered across all the gardens of Eden. Swing and jump between plants and rock formations, collect pollen to seed new plants and explore the incredible gardens to locate the precious “Spectra.” 

Lush visuals, slick controls and amazing music make it an incredibly atmospheric and addictive experience.</desc>
		<thumbnail>./images/PixelJunk Eden-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/PixelJunk Eden-fanart.png</fanart>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20080731T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Q-Games</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Plate-formes</genre>
		<players>3</players>
		<md5>b17168a9f5dc7bc644a8c48f9e400f6c</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230215T185357" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T012458" />
	</game>
	<game id="26954">
		<path>./PixelJunk Monsters Encore.m3u</path>
		<name>Pixeljunk Monsters Encore</name>
		<desc>PixelJunk Monsters Encore is an add-on to the original game that you will also need to download from the Playstation Network for the Playstation 3. As a village chief, you must save the inhabitants from a monster invasion by building towers in the forest. This expansion includes a new island, 15 new levels, 5 new music tracks and a rebalancing of item prices.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<developer>Q-Games</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<family>PixelJunk</family>
		<md5>0ff2aa07857bc0a2b107488b02c67b7e</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T152225" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T012557" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./PixelJunk Racers 2nd Lap.m3u</path>
		<name>PixelJunk Racers: 2nd Lap</name>
		<desc>PixelJunk Racers 2nd Lap is an addictive slot car racing game that supports 1080p and features single player and multiplayer fun (up to 7 players simultaneously offline!). Intuitive controls, 32 different race modes, and online rankings will provide countless hours of racing mayhem. 

What's a race car driver without the podium trophy? Replay PixelJunk™ Racers 2nd Lap to unlock all the added Trophies! Think you're the best? Register your new record on the high score tables and allow anyone in the worldcan compete against your best race! 

See you on the race track!</desc>
		<thumbnail>./images/PixelJunk Racers 2nd Lap-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/PixelJunk Racers 2nd Lap-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<releasedate>20100824T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Q-Games</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Course</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<md5>812ff58f7d3b30e4abe6baf668899424</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230215T185407" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T012558" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SF3 Online Edition.m3u</path>
		<name>SF3 Online Edition</name>
		<md5>46c8a5106ca75be76719957cace5d928</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T152227" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T012558" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sly 2 Band of Thieves.m3u</path>
		<name>Sly 2: Band of Thieves</name>
		<desc>The sequel has a variety of changes, particularly in level design. The ultimate goal is to acquire Clockwerk parts, one or more of which can be found per "world". Sly 2 features a health meter for characters such as Sly, Bentley and Murray, replacing the "charm system" of the first game. It also takes several attacks to defeat guards. Other changes include missions where the player controls Bentley or Murray, who have their own unique skills and are able to do much more than in the previous game. However, Sly remains the main character despite these changes to character roles. Skills can be unlocked by opening safes in each world, as the previous game allowed (collecting clue bottles), but skills may also be acquired by collecting coins and purchasing them from safehouses via Thiefnet.</desc>
		<image>./images/Sly 2 Band of Thieves-image.jpg</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Sly 2 Band of Thieves-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Sly 2 Band of Thieves-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<releasedate>20101109T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sucker Punch Productions</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Plate-formes</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>39faabb5b93f80dce2aeda56e213b101</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T152228" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T012559" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sly 3 Honor Among Thieves.m3u</path>
		<name>Sly 3: Honor Among Thieves</name>
		<desc>Sly and the gang is back in this third outing of Sly Raccoon-series. This time, the story takes the boys (Sly, Bentley and Murray) to the fortress that houses the treasures of Sly's family. Although they are still weary from the adventures in the previous game, they have to get up and face the new threat that could mean the end of Sly's business and the loss of his family heritage. The game itself is a lot like the previous games: Sly sneaks, jumps, and swings himself around the levels, collecting various items, defeating bad guys and ultimately taking on the boss character. The other members of the gang step in on the action once in a while but the Sly centric sections are the main focus of the game. If you like games that had many things to do, this sneak-em-up/platform/action/adventure/puzzle game is for you.</desc>
		<image>./images/Sly 3 Honor Among Thieves-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Sly 3 Honor Among Thieves-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Sly 3 Honor Among Thieves-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Sly 3 Honor Among Thieves-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<releasedate>20101109T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sucker Punch Productions</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Plate-formes</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>7c415a906b9e872cb7b1472d6fe3c35e</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T152230" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T012700" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sly Cooper Thieves in Time.m3u</path>
		<name>Sly Cooper: Thieves in Time</name>
		<desc>Sly Cooper Thieves in Time continues to chronicle the adventures of the Sly Cooper gang from where Sly 3: Honor Among Thieves concluded. After completing their latest heist, Sly carries on with a case of alleged amnesia and dances off with gal pal Carmelita, leaving Bentley as the keeper of the treasured Thievius Raccoonus, The Cooper family's ancient book of master thievery. When Bentley discovers that pages of the book have begun to disappear in front of his eyes, he must round up the gang and save the Cooper Clan legacy from being destroyed forever.</desc>
		<image>./images/Sly Cooper Thieves in Time-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Sly Cooper Thieves in Time-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Sly Cooper Thieves in Time-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Sly Cooper Thieves in Time-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Sly Cooper Thieves in Time-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20130205T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sanzaru Games</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Plate-formes</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>9e8c164f005efe212e9b7cbc99251c42</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T152252" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T012701" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sly Cooper.m3u</path>
		<name>Sly Cooper and the Thievius Raccoonus HD</name>
		<desc>The game focuses on master thief Sly Cooper and his gang, Bentley the Turtle and Murray the Hippo, as they seek out the Fiendish Five to recover his family's "Thievius Raccoonus," a book with the accumulation of all of Sly's ancestors' thieving moves. The game was praised for using a variation on cel-shading rendering, which is used to create a film noir feel, while still rendered as a hand-drawn animated movie, though criticized for being too short.</desc>
		<image>./images/Sly Cooper-image.jpg</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Sly Cooper-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Sly Cooper-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<releasedate>20101109T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sucker Punch Productions</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Plate-formes</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>6e33a0b0578d41475468c04c87a6af76</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T152253" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T012800" />
	</game>
	<game id="24960">
		<path>./Sniper Elite 3.m3u</path>
		<name>Sniper Elite III</name>
		<desc>Featuring a greater focus on player agency/choice and expansive environments filled with opportunities for distinct play styles, and set in the exotic yet deadly terrain of North Africa during World War II, Sniper Elite 3 sees American OSS agent Karl Fairburne deep behind Nazi lines, providing crucial sharpshooter skills as the Allies battle Germany's fearsome Tiger tanks across the Western Desert. But it's not just the famed Afrika Korps that Karl has to worry about; he soon uncovers German plans to build a 'wunderwaffe' – a 'wonder weapon' – with the power to crush any Allied forces in its path, and turn the tide of the whole war.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<developer>Rebellion</developer>
		<publisher>505 Games</publisher>
		<genre>Lightgun Shooter</genre>
		<md5>e85823f3d5aa935b8d06dab4ea55d478</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230215T185450" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T012800" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sonic  AllStars Racing Transformed.m3u</path>
		<name>Sonic  AllStars Racing Transformed</name>
		<md5>1de6251546f31e05beac49d330540a08</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T152255" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T012859" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sonic Adventure 2.m3u</path>
		<name>Sonic Adventure 2</name>
		<desc>Sonic Adventure 2 is a 3D Platformer game, developed by Sonic Team and published by Sega, which was released in 2012.</desc>
		<image>./images/Sonic Adventure 2-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Sonic Adventure 2-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Sonic Adventure 2-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Sonic Adventure 2-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20121002T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sonic Team</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<md5>40f6079e109491881f33b3b939127a0b</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230215T185546" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T012901" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sonic Adventure.m3u</path>
		<name>Sonic Adventure</name>
		<desc>Sonic Adventure (??????????? Sonikku Adobencha?) is a platform video game developed by Sonic Team and published by Sega. It was originally released for the Dreamcast as a launch title in Japan in 1998, and worldwide the following year. It was the first game in the main Sonic the Hedgehog series since Sonic &amp; Knuckles in 1994, and was the best-selling game on the Dreamcast.

After series villain Doctor Eggman releases an ancient monster, protagonist Sonic the Hedgehog vows to stop him collecting the Chaos Emeralds. The other playable characters are flying fox Miles "Tails" Prower, love interest Amy Rose, Knuckles the Echidna, who plans to reassemble the Master Emerald, angler Big the Cat, and E-102 Gamma, one of Eggman's robots.

Sonic Adventure received generally positive reviews for its graphics, gameplay, and soundtrack. It became the best-selling Dreamcast game. A sequel, Sonic Adventure 2, was released in 2001 for the Dreamcast. Enhanced ports of the game were released in 2003 for the Nintendo GameCube and Microsoft Windows. It has since been re-released as a downloadable game for Xbox 360 via Xbox Live Arcade, and PlayStation 3 via PlayStation Network in 2010. It is also included in the Dreamcast Collection for the Xbox 360.</desc>
		<marquee>./images/Sonic Adventure-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Sonic Adventure-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20100921T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sonic Team</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Aventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>e3088bb004a7ac7739e5aa6676242384</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230215T185552" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T013001" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SONIC GENERATIONS.m3u</path>
		<name>Sonic Generations</name>
		<desc>The game features levels derived from 20 years of Sonic history, spreading across three eras: Classic, Dreamcast and Modern, which are played as either Classic Sonic or Modern Sonic. Classic Sonic's levels are strictly two dimensional side scrolling stages, using classic moves like the Spin Attack and Spin Dash, while Modern Sonic's levels follow the 2D/3D style gameplay of Sonic Unleashed and Sonic Colors, featuring techniques such as boosting and homing attacks. As well as classic power-ups such as Invincibility and Speed Shoes, certain levels have unique power-ups, such as skateboards in City Escape and Wisp powers in Planet Wisp.</desc>
		<image>./images/SONIC GENERATIONS-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/SONIC GENERATIONS-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/SONIC GENERATIONS-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/SONIC GENERATIONS-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20111101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sonic Team</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>24c030ac711dc9c362449f0686b8a360</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T152257" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T013001" />
		<boxback>./images/SONIC GENERATIONS-boxback.png</boxback>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sonic the Fighters.m3u</path>
		<name>Sonic the Fighters</name>
		<desc>Sonic Championship is a 3D fighting game, featuring characters from the Sonic the Hedgehog franchise. The background story is that Doctor Eggman built the Death Egg II, a new version of his facility that appeared in previous games. Stopping him requires Chaos Emeralds, and various individuals including heroes like Sonic the Hedgehog and Miles "Tails" Prower participate in a fighting tournament to gather them. In total there are eight playable characters (nine in later console releases) and two bosses (Metal Sonic and Doctor Eggman).

Gameplay is mostly typical for a versus fighter, it is a one-on-one fight on a best two out of three basis. Players use jumps, punches, kicks and special weapons. Bean the Dynamite for example, a duck-like character who makes his debut in the Sonic universe, uses bombs. Blocking is done by making use of a limited supply of barriers. The whole action is illustrated in a comical fashion though, like one would expect from a Sonic game. A round is won when a player managed to deplete an opponent's health, unless the timer runs out, in which case the character with the most energy left is the winner. Environments are 3D closed arenas, but the gameplay is mostly 2D, allowing limited sidestep maneuvers.</desc>
		<image>./images/Sonic the Fighters-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Sonic the Fighters-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Sonic the Fighters-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Sonic the Fighters-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20121127T000000</releasedate>
		<md5>8e9c31c3ef24854a66f7f0b768284163</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230215T185620" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T013100" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sonic The Hedgehog 2.m3u</path>
		<name>Sonic the Hedgehog (2006)</name>
		<desc>Sonic celebrates his 15th anniversary by blazing his way onto the next-generation consoles, with his first adventure set in the human world! Featuring interactive 3D environments and a large cast of returning and new characters, get ready for the reinvention of Sonic The Hedgehog, in his most intense, high velocity escapade to date!</desc>
		<image>./images/Sonic The Hedgehog 2-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Sonic The Hedgehog 2-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Sonic The Hedgehog 2-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Sonic The Hedgehog 2-fanart.png</fanart>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20061221T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sonic Team</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Plate-formes</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>55a86477be33e38779a44ce6d870a7dc</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230215T185622" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T013102" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SONIC THE HEDGEHOG 4 Episode I.m3u</path>
		<name>Sonic the Hedgehog 4: Episode 1</name>
		<desc>Sonic the Hedgehog 4: Episode I (?????????????4??? ?????I Sonikku za Hejjihoggu F?: Epis?do Wan?) is a 2010 episodic platform video game in the Sonic the Hedgehog series. The game was developed by Dimps, with assistance from Sonic Team,[7] and is intended to emulate the original Sonic the Hedgehog titles on the Sega Genesis.

Episode I was released in October 2010 for iOS, PlayStation Network, WiiWare and Xbox Live Arcade.[1] A release for Windows Phone 7 followed in June 2011,[2] for PC (via Steam) and Android in January 2012,[3][4] for BlackBerry PlayBook in July 2012,[5] and for Ouya in July 2013.[6] A sequel, Sonic the Hedgehog 4: Episode II, was released in 2012.</desc>
		<image>./images/SONIC THE HEDGEHOG 4 Episode I-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/SONIC THE HEDGEHOG 4 Episode I-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/SONIC THE HEDGEHOG 4 Episode I-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/SONIC THE HEDGEHOG 4 Episode I-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/SONIC THE HEDGEHOG 4 Episode I-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20101012T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sonic Team</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Plate-formes</genre>
		<md5>31640ecae688f785ab9ff3a9680780d2</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T152326" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T013102" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SONIC THE HEDGEHOG 4 Episode II.m3u</path>
		<name>Sonic the Hedgehog 4: Episode II</name>
		<desc>Sonic the Hedgehog 4: Episode II (?????????????4??? ?????II Sonikku za Hejjihoggu F?: Epis?do Ts??) is a 2012 episodic platform video game in the Sonic the Hedgehog series, created as a direct follow-on from Sonic the Hedgehog 4: Episode I. The game was developed by Dimps, with assistance from Sonic Team,[9] and is intended to emulate the original Sonic the Hedgehog titles on the Sega Genesis.

Episode II was released in May 2012 for PC (via Steam),[1] PlayStation Network,[2] Xbox Live Arcade,[3] Android,[4] and iOS,[5] and in July 2013 for Ouya,[10] and Nvidia Shield (as a preinstalled app).[7] A version for the Windows Phone was slated to be released in July 2012,[8][11] but was ultimately cancelled. An additional episode, "Episode Metal", is available for those who purchase both episodes for the same system. As of late 2014, the game is no longer available on iOS devices due to software incompatibility.</desc>
		<image>./images/SONIC THE HEDGEHOG 4 Episode II-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/SONIC THE HEDGEHOG 4 Episode II-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/SONIC THE HEDGEHOG 4 Episode II-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/SONIC THE HEDGEHOG 4 Episode II-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/SONIC THE HEDGEHOG 4 Episode II-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20120515T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sonic Team</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Plate-formes</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<md5>f5deed44c42118ac0a7f9b113f5f872f</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T152355" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T013201" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sonic The Hedgehog.m3u</path>
		<name>Sonic the Hedgehog</name>
		<desc>Sonic celebrates his 15th anniversary by blazing his way onto the next-generation consoles, with his first adventure set in the human world! Featuring interactive 3D environments and a large cast of returning and new characters, get ready for the reinvention of Sonic The Hedgehog, in his most intense, high velocity escapade to date!</desc>
		<image>./images/Sonic The Hedgehog-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Sonic The Hedgehog-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Sonic The Hedgehog-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Sonic The Hedgehog-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Sonic The Hedgehog-boxback.png</boxback>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20110329T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Backbone Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Plate-formes</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>7f0427d02a0f91e53ff19fddc413be67</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230215T185640" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T013201" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SONIC UNLEASHED.m3u</path>
		<name>Sonic Unleashed</name>
		<desc>Gameplay in Sonic Unleashed focuses on two modes of platforming play: fast-paced levels that take place during daytime, showcasing Sonic's trademark speed as seen in previous games in the series, and slower, night-time levels, during which Sonic's Werehog form emerges, and gameplay switches to an action-based, brawler style of play, in which Sonic battles Gaia enemies</desc>
		<image>./images/SONIC UNLEASHED-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/SONIC UNLEASHED-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/SONIC UNLEASHED-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/SONIC UNLEASHED-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/SONIC UNLEASHED-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<manual>./manuals/SONIC UNLEASHED-manual.pdf</manual>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20081118T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sonic Team</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>7325b7735fe0988638795d18472929e4</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T152356" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T013302" />
		<boxback>./images/SONIC UNLEASHED-boxback.png</boxback>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SOULCALIBUR  HD ONLINE.m3u</path>
		<name>SOULCALIBUR  HD ONLINE</name>
		<md5>7d460ebe57604cf8c942b856daed498a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T152358" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T013302" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SOULCALIBUR Lost Swords.m3u</path>
		<name>Soulcalibur: Lost Swords</name>
		<desc>Forge your own destiny. 

Take on a series of mighty enemies in an expansive single player campaign, Collect weapons and armour, and forge powerful new items as you progress. Use your weapons’ elemental properties to give you a handy advantage over certain adversaries.</desc>
		<image>./images/SOULCALIBUR Lost Swords-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/SOULCALIBUR Lost Swords-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/SOULCALIBUR Lost Swords-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/SOULCALIBUR Lost Swords-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.35</rating>
		<releasedate>20140422T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Project Soul</developer>
		<publisher>Namco Bandai</publisher>
		<genre>Combat</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>f6a3656732fa7d54efc4896d1cde4a0d</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T152407" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T013402" />
	</game>
	<game id="200611">
		<path>./SplitSecond.m3u</path>
		<name>Split-Second</name>
		<md5>8e5a4e47b05c34cf413b2169e7471aeb</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T152408" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T013403" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Street Fighter 2 Turbo HD.m3u</path>
		<name>Super Street Fighter 2 Turbo HD</name>
		<md5>62efef7845cb78d50c32b651a116dc2f</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T152409" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T013501" />
	</game>
	<game id="24901">
		<path>./SUPER STREET FIGHTER IVARCADE EDITION.m3u</path>
		<name>Super Street Fighter IV : Arcade Edition</name>
		<desc>The follow-up to the critically acclaimed Super Street Fighter IV will further redefine the fighting game genre with classic 2D Street Fighter fighting action, a host of new and returning characters, beefed up online modes, and more.Super Street Fighter IV Arcade Edition features a roster of 39 characters such as Ryu, Chun-li, Juri, El Fuerte, and Rufus, while adding 4 new characters to the roster including classic combatants from previous Street Fighter games like Yun and Yang as well as the all-new Oni.Beyond characters, Super Street Fighter IV Arcade Edition adds all-new balancing as well as an enhanced Replay Channel.</desc>
		<image>./images/SUPER STREET FIGHTER IVARCADE EDITION-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/SUPER STREET FIGHTER IVARCADE EDITION-marquee.png</marquee>
		<fanart>./images/SUPER STREET FIGHTER IVARCADE EDITION-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<family>Street Fighter</family>
		<md5>7c4ccfea8fec8a607cb4d394abd783a6</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T152430" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T013501" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tales of Xillia 2.m3u</path>
		<name>Tales of Xillia 2</name>
		<desc>Tales of Xillia 2 centers around Ludger Kresnik, a young man and a skilled chef who lives in Trigleph city in Elympios with his brother Julius and their cat Rollo. He strives to follow in his brother’s footsteps and work as an agent in the prestigious Spirius Corporation, a large scale and illustrious company that develops technology for every field imaginable. One day, through a chance encounter, he meets Elle Marta: a young girl travelling alone attempting to reunite with her father at the mythic “Land of Canaan” and ends up accompanying her. His choice to accompany her will send the two on a journey that will change the fate of the two worlds forever.</desc>
		<image>./images/Tales of Xillia 2-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Tales of Xillia 2-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Tales of Xillia 2-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Tales of Xillia 2-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Tales of Xillia 2-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<manual>./manuals/Tales of Xillia 2-manual.pdf</manual>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20140819T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco Tales Studio</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai Namco Games</publisher>
		<genre>RPG</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<md5>4b2b8bed09988f2017c07990cc575778</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230215T190223" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T013603" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tales of Xillia.m3u</path>
		<name>Tales of Xillia</name>
		<desc>Set in a world where humans and spirits share a symbiotic existence with each other, Tales of Xillia follows the adventures of two unlikely heroes in a land where two conflicting nations are heading to a clash. Building upon the signature real-time combat, epic storytelling, and strong character relationships from the series, Tales of Xillia immerses players into a sweeping role playing adventure beyond imagination. 

Tales of Xillia follows Jude Mathis, a clever medical student attending school in the capital city, and Milla Maxwell, a mysterious woman accompanied by four unseen beings. Players will be able to choose either Jude or Milla at the outset of their adventure through the world of Rieze Maxia, where humans and spirits live together in harmony. The kingdom of Rashugal has been experimenting with a powerful source that led to draining the mana from the world. Realizing the harm it is inflicting on the world, Jude and Milla set off on a journey to destroy it and restore the mana back to the world.</desc>
		<image>./images/Tales of Xillia-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Tales of Xillia-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Tales of Xillia-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Tales of Xillia-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Tales of Xillia-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20130806T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco Tales Studio</developer>
		<publisher>Namco Bandai</publisher>
		<genre>RPG</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<md5>9f6032e72a8828990b07e6a415971eef</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230215T190236" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T013603" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./TEKKEN REVOLUTION.m3u</path>
		<name>Tekken Revolution</name>
		<desc>Tekken Revolution (Japanese: ?????????? Hepburn: Tekken Rebory?shon?) is a free-to-play fighting video game developed and published by Namco Bandai. It was released exclusively on the PlayStation 3 via the PlayStation Store on June 11, 2013.[1][2] It is the first game in the Tekken franchise to be made free-to-play in this manner.[3]</desc>
		<image>./images/TEKKEN REVOLUTION-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/TEKKEN REVOLUTION-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/TEKKEN REVOLUTION-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/TEKKEN REVOLUTION-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<genre>Combat</genre>
		<md5>f3ad176d33f5e247176e5bb699610241</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T152431" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T013604" />
	</game>
	<game id="26059">
		<path>./TEKKEN5 DARK RESURRECTION ONLINE.m3u</path>
		<name>Tekken 5 : Dark Resurrection Online</name>
		<desc>Tekken 5: Dark Resurrection Online on PS3 features classic modes such as Arcade and Duel, as well as the all-new Training mode where you can hone your skills to meet the challenge of Survival mode. You'll also be able to pull off devastating moves against real opponents in the new Online Battle mode available for the first time in Tekken history.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<developer>Bandai Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<family>Tekken</family>
		<players>2</players>
		<md5>de5b129bc38fb7cd47ce777932bf57bb</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T152433" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T013703" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./The Smurfs 2.m3u</path>
		<name>The Smurfs 2</name>
		<desc>The Smurfs 2 video game is an action-packed adventure platformer that provides Smurfs fans of all ages with the opportunity to dive into the magical Smurfs Village and relive iconic moments and key environments from the feature film. Players assume the role of a Smurf and immerse themselves in an interactive adventure through the movie's enchanting environments including New York City and Paris, and expand their movie experience into worlds exclusive to the video game such as The Arctic Tundra and The Lava Jungle.</desc>
		<marquee>./images/The Smurfs 2-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/The Smurfs 2-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20130723T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<md5>a06af4f195f4652af8f6438d6281dd40</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230215T190357" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T013704" />
	</game>
	<game id="25641">
		<path>./Tom Clancys EndWar.m3u</path>
		<name>Tom Clancy's Endwar</name>
		<desc>EndWar on PS3 is set against the backdrop of a hypothetical World War III. Using a voice command system, the player must lead one of three rival factions into battle and capture strategic points that provide access to tactical support weapons. Playable in single-player, EndWar places a strong emphasis on multiplayer, with an innovative mode that allows players to evolve frontlines on a global map until final victory is achieved.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>35e619b36079925078e9c9e6f6a8bbed</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T152434" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T013704" />
	</game>
	<game id="25536">
		<path>./Tom Clancys Ghost Recon Advanced Warfighter 2.m3u</path>
		<name>Ghost Recon Advanced Warfighter 2</name>
		<desc>Not even a day has fully passed since you rescued the US president from Mexican soil and you and the rest of your Ghost team are on the way home, when the General phones in and gives you your next mission: a group of terrorists deposited two dirty bombs (normal blasting compositions combined with radioactive material) near the city of Juarez. Your goal as Captain Mitchell is to once again save the day with your three teammates.
nnLike in its predecessor Tom Clancy's Ghost Recon: Advanced Warfighter, you see Captain Mitchell from behind while you command your teammates directly over the Cross-Com to fulfil your objectives, like blowing up a bunch of anti-air vehicles and then raiding a rebel outpost. To do so, you have the normal Ghost team weaponry like the MR-C at your disposal, which you can equip you and your team with before and even at some points during the missions. You also have access to a tactical map which allows you to see an aerial view of the current level.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20070821T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / 1st person</genre>
		<family>Tom Clancy's Ghost Recon</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>a367ec5a84c301b21b00538a6d57a34d</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T152436" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T013704" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tom Clancys Ghost Recon Future Soldier  Multiplayer Beta.m3u</path>
		<name>Tom Clancys Ghost Recon Future Soldier  Multiplayer Beta</name>
		<md5>770b02539ddc99a172c8155fab25b4b3</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T152438" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T013804" />
	</game>
	<game id="25142">
		<path>./Tom Clancys Ghost Recon Future Soldier.m3u</path>
		<name>Ghost Recon : Future Soldier</name>
		<desc>Developed by the award-winning team behind Tom Clancy's Ghost Recon Advanced Warfighter and Tom Clancy's Ghost Recon Advanced Warfighter 2, the game will feature cutting-edge technology, prototype high-tech weaponry, and state-of-the-art single-player and multiplayer modes. Tom Clancy's Ghost Recon: Future Soldier will go beyond the core Ghost Recon franchise and deliver a fresh gameplay experience, with an unparalleled level of quality that will excite long-time fans and newcomers alike.</desc>
		<image>./images/Tom Clancys Ghost Recon Future Soldier-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Tom Clancys Ghost Recon Future Soldier-video.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail>./images/Tom Clancys Ghost Recon Future Soldier-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<family>Tom Clancy's Ghost Recon</family>
		<md5>473b58803376e38fe0354ef5fed995ce</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T152501" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T013804" />
	</game>
	<game id="25588">
		<path>./Tom Clancys H.A.W.X. 2.m3u</path>
		<name>Tom Clancy's H.a.w.x. 2</name>
		<desc>H.A.W.X. 2 is an air combat game for Playstation 3 inspired by the universe of the American novelist Tom Clancy. At the controls of a multitude of aircraft, the player embodies three pilots of different origins and tries to avoid the declaration of an international conflict.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<md5>914eb4a37e8cfb6368677e63bd599782</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T152502" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T013804" />
	</game>
	<game id="25648">
		<path>./Tom Clancys H.A.W.X.m3u</path>
		<name>Tom Clancy's H.a.w.x.</name>
		<desc>H.A.W.X. is a PlayStation 3 air combat game based on the universe of American novelist Tom Clancy. It takes place in 2012, in a near future where nations have become dependent on private military companies. In this warlike context, the player takes on the role of a pilot at the controls of a plane equipped with ultra-modern technology. As a squad leader, he can also give orders to his teammates.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<md5>6d6c8c1d77e89d3219be41bd2985103d</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T152504" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T013804" />
	</game>
	<game id="200551">
		<path>./Tom Clancys Rainbow Six Vegas 2.m3u</path>
		<name>Tom Clancy's Rainbow Six - Vegas 2</name>
		<md5>d31e505eb8efeecc3af585b506bed3fc</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230215T190546" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T013904" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tom Clancys Splinter Cell Blacklist Digital.m3u</path>
		<name>Tom Clancys Splinter Cell Blacklist Digital</name>
		<md5>418ab24336bff82ad3447b47c58336db</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T152505" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T013904" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Toy Story 3.m3u</path>
		<name>Toy Story 3</name>
		<desc>Toy Story 3: The Video Game is a platform video game loosely based on the film Toy Story 3. It was published by Disney Interactive Studios (which is the developer for iOS) and developed by Avalanche Software (PS3, Wii, Xbox 360, PC, Mac OS X), Asobo Studio (PS2, PSP) and n-Space (DS). The game was released in North America on June 15, 2010, for the iOS, Nintendo DS, Wii, PlayStation Portable, PlayStation 3, Microsoft Windows, Mac OS X, and the Xbox 360. A special PlayStation 2 bundle with Toy Story 3: The Video Game was released on October 31, 2010, followed by the game's individual release on November 2, 2010.[1][2] It's the only video game based on the Toy Story franchise to be released for the PlayStation 2, as well as the last video game based on a Disney and/or Pixar product on the console.

Toy Story 3 is the first game based on a film by Pixar to be published entirely by Disney Interactive Studios. Past Disney/Pixar movie games have been made in conjunction with Activision first, then THQ.[3] It is the sequel to the second game that was based on the second film in the franchise.

Most of the voice cast from the film returned to reprise their characters in the game with the exception of Tom Hanks (Woody) and Tim Allen (Buzz Lightyear). Jim Hanks returned to voice Woody from the Toy Story 2 game, and Mike MacRae voiced Buzz. The game also contains content exclusive to the PlayStation 3 version that allows the player(s) to turn into Zurg in Woody's Round up.[4] The game was well received by critics and was a top-seller in the UK.</desc>
		<image>./images/Toy Story 3-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Toy Story 3-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Toy Story 3-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Toy Story 3-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20100615T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Avalanche Productions</developer>
		<publisher>Disney Interactive Studios</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<md5>b2b2776dafa8525943d0b6607f4e857e</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230215T190619" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T013906" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Twisted Metal U.S. Digital.m3u</path>
		<name>Twisted Metal U.S. Digital</name>
		<md5>9bbbfbbe481db851144e2a2bdd0a0be2</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T152506" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T014004" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./UFC 3 Alpha.m3u</path>
		<name>UFC 3 Alpha</name>
		<md5>6a9ec7df4d4213df1ce9b6d34b2ad7f1</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T152507" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T014004" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Virtua Fighter 2.m3u</path>
		<name>Virtua Fighter 2</name>
		<desc>Go back to the roots of 3-D fighting with Virtua Fighter 2™, the second title in AM2's flagship fighting franchise. Experience the legendary polygon-based 3-D graphics and fluid fighting mechanics that made the game so influential in the arcades, and later on the Sega Saturn. With all-new online play you can battle friends throughout the world.

Features include:

Arcade perfect with all-new online modes

All 10 original characters and arenas

Online versus mode for head-to-head matches

Online Room match mode for up to 6 players</desc>
		<image>./images/Virtua Fighter 2-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Virtua Fighter 2-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Virtua Fighter 2-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Virtua Fighter 2-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.25</rating>
		<releasedate>20121127T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>AM R&amp;D Dept. #2</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA of America, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Combat</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<md5>c8e7c5ee5f6d14cdcc7aaf6bdb533cd1</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230215T190831" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T014005" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Virtua Fighter 5 Final Showdown.m3u</path>
		<name>Virtua Fighter 5: Final Showdown</name>
		<desc>Definitive version of the Virtua Fighter 5 series that incorporates all the enhancements SEGA has rolled out since 2007 and introduces a new character: Taka-Arashi, returning from Virtua Fighter 3 and a karate expert Jean Kujo makes his debut in this gang of 19 playable characters. Its fighting mechanics were overhauled making Final Showdown more accessible to new players while retaining the trademark depth and balance of the game. Final Showdown introduces new stage arenas and interactive environments. In the new Online Mode you can challenge a friend to a Ranked Match or Player Match or play with up to 7 others in Room Match mode. Costumes can be customized, adding a huge variety of customization items sold separately (as DLC packs) for the ultimate Virtua Fighter experience.</desc>
		<image>./images/Virtua Fighter 5 Final Showdown-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Virtua Fighter 5 Final Showdown-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Virtua Fighter 5 Final Showdown-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Virtua Fighter 5 Final Showdown-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20120605T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega AM2</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Combat</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<md5>d6ae99c7e9b4cfb17dda1ae020208344</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T152539" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T014105" />
	</game>
	<game id="26932">
		<path>./Wakeboarding HD.m3u</path>
		<name>Wakeboarding Hd</name>
		<desc>Wakeboarding HD is a game of... wakeboarding on Playstation 3! A bit crazy, the software offers you to ride on the most beautiful seas and oceans of the world, to jump over trees, submarines and even helicopters!</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20100325T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>TikGames</developer>
		<publisher>Creat Studios</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<md5>b2d7cd9d677edb954d9b53aa62732a90</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230215T190859" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T014105" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Warhawk.m3u</path>
		<name>Warhawk</name>
		<desc>Warhawk is a multiplayer third-person vehicle and flight combat video game developed by Incognito Entertainment exclusively for the PlayStation 3. It is a remake of an aerial warfare game of the same name, which was a launch title on the original PlayStation. Apart from the similarity of controlling aircraft, the remake bears little other resemblance. It was the first PlayStation 3 game to be available both for download on the PlayStation Network and for retail on Blu-ray Disc. For the United States, Blu-ray Disc and PlayStation Network versions were released on August 28, 2007. The PlayStation Network version was released in Europe, Australia and Japan on August 30, August 31 and October 4 respectively. The Blu-ray Disc version was released in Australia and Europe on September 20 and September 21, respectively, but was not released in Japan.</desc>
		<marquee>./images/Warhawk-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Warhawk-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Warhawk-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20070827T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Incognito Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<md5>d96be4f580d763e852d842ef0c791169</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230215T190906" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T014206" />
	</game>
	<game id="25151">
		<path>./WARRIORS OROCHI 3 Ultimate.m3u</path>
		<name>Warriors Orochi 3 Ultimate</name>
		<desc>Set in a parallel universe created by the suddenly appearing Serpent King Orochi, players can enjoy the refreshing action of mighty warriors in the tactical action game series WARRIORS OROCHI. The series is full of unique components such as an original story with heroes from the Dynasty Warriors and Samurai Warriors series and a three-man team battle mode.
Players can fully enjoy the dramatic story WARRIORS OROCHI 3's many heroes even more with new characters who can participate in battle and additional scenarios. Additionally, many new components, such as new actions, and a new 'Gauntlet Mode,' in which players can enjoy a party battle have been added, making this truly the ultimate WARRIORS OROCHI 3.</desc>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>20130926T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>OMEGA Force</developer>
		<publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<family>Warriors Orochi</family>
		<players>2</players>
		<md5>76eed2b4eeb3d5081aa6c6e163aedcd0</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T152540" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T014207" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./WARRIORS OROCHI 3.m3u</path>
		<name>Warriors Orochi 3</name>
		<desc>Warriors Orochi 3 is the third installment in the Warriors Orochi series and the sequel of Warriors Orochi 2.

After vanquishing Orochi, a period of peace came to the land. That peace is suddenly shattered by the appearance of a Hydra. Warriors from different worlds gather to father the Hydra, but only three survive. With the help of the mystic Kaguya, Sima Zhao, Ma Chao and Hanbei Takenaka set to travel in time to save their fallen comrades and form an army against the new threat.

Starting with only four characters, the player sets to gather warriors by altering the outcome of different battles. The characters consist of the characters from the Dynasty Warriors series and Samurai Warriors series and a few from other games such as Ninja Gaiden and Dead or Alive.

The player chooses three warriors before each stage. In battle, these characters can switch places at any time to fight against hordes of enemy soldiers and officers, gathering experience and gems until the victory conditions are met. Weapons and items can also be acquired in battle. Between each battle, the player is sent back to the camp, where he can buy and customize weapons, make characters bond together, equip the characters and distribute growth points to raise the character's level. If certain conditions are met, discussions between specific warriors will unlock new stages or an alternate "Redux" version of a previously cleared battle.</desc>
		<image>./images/WARRIORS OROCHI 3-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/WARRIORS OROCHI 3-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/WARRIORS OROCHI 3-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/WARRIORS OROCHI 3-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20120320T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Omega Force</developer>
		<publisher>Tecmo Koei</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<md5>a758f239190739fb3fabb3c5125d96e9</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T152550" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T014207" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Watchmen The End is Nigh Part 2.m3u</path>
		<name>Watchmen The End is Nigh Part 2</name>
		<md5>a79c0fdf335fe00af2225b4744292fdf</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231126T152552" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T014307" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Worms 2 Armageddon.m3u</path>
		<name>Worms 2: Armageddon</name>
		<desc>This is a 2D turn-based strategy game in which players control worms in a battle to be the last man (worm) standing. Players take turns positioning their worms around fantastical landscapes and use a variety of over-the-top weapons ('cartoony' bazookas, grenades, uzis, exploding sheep, etc.) to defeat opponents' worms.</desc>
		<image>./images/Worms 2 Armageddon-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Worms 2 Armageddon-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Worms 2 Armageddon-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Worms 2 Armageddon-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20100908T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Team 17</developer>
		<publisher>Team 17</publisher>
		<genre>Strategie</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<md5>10fc4107556ba7e4cd33c5834e150db0</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230215T191045" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T014307" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Worms Crazy Golf.m3u</path>
		<name>Worms Crazy Golf</name>
		<desc>Worms Crazy Golf is a 2011 action game developed by Team17. A sequel to the mobile exclusive "Worms Golf", the game uses the basic framework of the "Worms" series as the foundation for a 2D golf title.</desc>
		<image>./images/Worms Crazy Golf-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Worms Crazy Golf-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Worms Crazy Golf-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Worms Crazy Golf-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<developer>Team17</developer>
		<publisher>Team17</publisher>
		<genre>Combat</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<md5>021481e7e4466a671eb76c5f2f410de4</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230215T191054" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T014407" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Worms Revolution.m3u</path>
		<name>Worms Revolution</name>
		<desc>The game has been developed from the ground up and features a completely new game-engine. Exciting new features and challenges have been introduced whilst old favourites such as the Super Sheep and Holy Hand Grenade remain to thrill fans worldwide.</desc>
		<marquee>./images/Worms Revolution-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Worms Revolution-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20121009T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Team17</developer>
		<publisher>Team17</publisher>
		<genre>Strategie</genre>
		<md5>a490e402d0a06c5ba665c95fd1e9ea2c</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230215T191056" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T014408" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Worms.m3u</path>
		<name>Worms</name>
		<desc>Players control a small platoon of worms across a deformable landscape, battling computer or player controlled teams. The game features bright and humorous cartoon-style animation and a varied arsenal of weapons. Full voice communication is also available among the players of the game.</desc>
		<marquee>./images/Worms-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Worms-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>20070307T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Team17</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<md5>0103217a5e1b8d012f45720a70f4b900</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230215T191058" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T014507" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Young Justice Legacy.m3u</path>
		<name>Young Justice: Legacy</name>
		<desc>In Young Justice: Legacy fans can look forward to an original storyline set in between Seasons 1 and 2 of the television series, written in collaboration with show writers Greg Weisman and Brandon Vietti. The game is packed with fan favorite playable characters, cameo appearances by popular Justice League heroes and villains, and includes online multiplayer as well as local multiplayer modes.</desc>
		<marquee>./images/Young Justice Legacy-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Young Justice Legacy-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/Young Justice Legacy-boxback.png</boxback>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>20131119T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Freedom Factory</developer>
		<publisher>Little Orbit</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<md5>f2f6fdc345f03ecb64bec4223d26f221</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230215T191132" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20231127T014508" />
	</game>
</gameList>
