<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game id="195821">
		<path>./Games/1-2-Switch.xci</path>
		<name>1-2-switch</name>
		<desc>Throw an impromptu party anywhere with anyone thanks to a new play style in which players look at each other—not the screen! Bring the action and fun into the real world as you face off in wild-west duels, cow-milking competitions, a copycat dance-off, and more. Each game takes advantage of the Joy-Con controller features of the Nintendo Switch system in different ways. While the action unfolds off- screen, the audience watches the players themselves instead of the screen. That makes it as hilarious to watch as it is to play – an instant party amplifier!</desc>
		<image>./images/1-2-Switch-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/1-2-Switch-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/1-2-Switch-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/1-2-Switch-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/1-2-Switch-boxback.png</boxback>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20170303T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Various</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073303" />
	</game>
	<game id="196355">
		<path>./Games/Aces of The Luftwaffe Squadron.xci</path>
		<name>Aces Of The Luftwaffe - Squadron</name>
		<desc>Every end is a new beginning! When Europe seemed to be freed, a secret German commando called The Aces of the Luftwaffe took their chance to strike back and invade the USA! It's your duty to restore peace and liberty by climbing aboard deadly wings of steel and fight against their fearsome war machines in bombastic air battles! Experience an epic storyline and survive the bullet hail above US coasts and cities! Command your wingmen, fight as a team, fight as a squadron!

ACES OF THE LUFTWAFFE – SQUADRON is an action-packed, vertically scrolling shoot 'em up with a captivating and fully voiced narrative. Dodge bullets, collect massive power ups and wisely use special abilities as you defeat waves of enemies. Upgrade each member of your squadron with their personal skill tree as you level up. But don't go to war alone! You can take on the Aces with up to 3 friends in an epic 4 player local co-op battle. Are you up to the task?</desc>
		<marquee>./images/Aces of The Luftwaffe Squadron-marquee.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20171116T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Handygames</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073305" />
	</game>
	<game id="198135">
		<path>./Games/Air Conflicts Collection.xci</path>
		<name>Air Conflicts Collection</name>
		<desc>Take to the skies with the combat flight simulator Air Conflicts Collection for Nintendo Switch! This collection contains remastered versions of two classic flight sims: Air Conflicts: Secret Wars and Air Conflicts: Pacific Carriers. In Secret Wars, pilot your way through seven different campaigns and 49 missions set during World War I and World War II. In Pacific Carriers, choose to fight for either the US Navy or the Imperial Japanese Navy, climbing into the cockpit and immersing yourself in the famous battles of the War of the Pacific. Both games feature plenty of action, dozens of planes and weapons, and four robust multiplayer modes.</desc>
		<marquee>./images/Air Conflicts Collection-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Air Conflicts Collection-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/Air Conflicts Collection-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20190322T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Games Farm</developer>
		<publisher>Kalypso Media Group</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation / Vehicle</genre>
		<family>Air Combat</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073308" />
	</game>
	<game id="198121">
		<path>./Games/American Ninja Warrior Challenge.xci</path>
		<name>American Ninja Warrior - Challenge</name>
		<desc>Begin your quest to achieve Total Victory with the action-packed obstacle course competition game, American Ninja Warrior Challenge! Do you have the strength and endurance to jump, swing, and sprint your way to hitting the buzzer at the end? Race against the clock with your friends and family while testing your skills in couch multi-player or take on the challenging career mode. Those who successfully complete the city courses move on to the finals will face a stunning four-stage course modeled after the famed Mt. Midoriyama in Japan. Enjoy all the thrills and spills to become the next American Ninja Warrior!Features:• Take on classic obstacles such as the Salmon Ladder, Warped Wall, Log Grip and more!• Build your own custom course and have your own personalized Ninja race through it• In-game commentary voiced by the TV show hosts Matt Iseman and Akbar Gbajabiamila• Offline multi-player &amp; online leaderboards</desc>
		<marquee>./images/American Ninja Warrior Challenge-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/American Ninja Warrior Challenge-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/American Ninja Warrior Challenge-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20190319T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Gaming Corps</developer>
		<publisher>GameMill Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073311" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Americas Greatest Game Shows Wheel Of Fortune and Jeopardy.xci</path>
		<name>Americas Greatest Game Shows Wheel Of Fortune and Jeopardy</name>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073312" />
	</game>
	<game id="196365">
		<path>./Games/Anima Arcane Edition.xci</path>
		<name>Anima - Gate of Memories</name>
		<desc>Anima: Gate of Memories is a third person action RPG that tells the story of two beings bound by an unwilling pact, an ancient monster and a girl who lost her past...
Forced to stay together, their lives will take a unexpected turn when both discover that something darker than they could imagine is about to start, a war in the shadows in which they will have a leading role.

Anima: Gate of Memories brings to videogames the world of Gaia from the Anima: Beyond Fantasy RPG table-top books. You will enjoy a deep and multifaceted story where your choices and actions directly impact the journey and decide the fate of the characters.</desc>
		<marquee>./images/Anima Arcane Edition-marquee.png</marquee>
		<releasedate>20180629T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>BLG Publishing</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073315" />
	</game>
	<game id="359214">
		<path>./Games/Animal Crossing - New Horizons (World).xci</path>
		<name>Animal Crossing - New Horizons</name>
		<desc>Escape to a deserted island and create your own paradise as you explore, create, and customize in the Animal Crossing: New Horizons game. Your island getaway has a wealth of natural resources that can be used to craft everything from tools to creature comforts. You can hunt down insects at the crack of dawn, decorate your paradise throughout the day, or enjoy sunset on the beach while fishing in the ocean. The time of day and season match real life, so each day on your island is a chance to check in and find new surprises all year round.</desc>
		<image>./images/Animal Crossing - New Horizons (World)-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Animal Crossing - New Horizons (World)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Animal Crossing - New Horizons (World)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Animal Crossing - New Horizons (World)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Animal Crossing - New Horizons (World)-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Animal Crossing - New Horizons (World)-boxback.png</boxback>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20200320T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation / Life</genre>
		<family>Animal Crossing</family>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>wr</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073317" />
	</game>
	<game id="196129">
		<path>./Games/Aqua Moto Racing Utopia.xci</path>
		<name>Aqua Moto Racing Utopia</name>
		<desc>Exotic courses, spectacular stunts, split-screen multiplayer: experience all the intensity of jet skiing on your own or with friends.</desc>
		<image>./images/Aqua Moto Racing Utopia-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Aqua Moto Racing Utopia-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Aqua Moto Racing Utopia-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/Aqua Moto Racing Utopia-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20180427T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Zordix</developer>
		<publisher>Bigben Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving / Motorcycle</genre>
		<players>8</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073320" />
	</game>
	<game id="198037">
		<path>./Games/Aragami Shadow Edition.xci</path>
		<name>Aragami - Shadow Edition</name>
		<desc>Aragami is a third person stealth game that casts you as an undead assassin with the power to control the shadows. Teleport to any shadow, become invisible, materialize weapons or even summon a shadow dragon to infiltrate the enemy ranks and dispose of your targets.Aragami: Shadow Edition includes Aragami: Nightfall, a story campaign which takes place before the events of Aragami, and all content released so far for Aragami.You are Aragami, a vengeful spirit with the power to control the shadows. You’ve been summoned by Yamiko, a girl imprisoned in the city fortress of Kyuryu. Embark on a dark journey full of blood and secrets to discover the truth about Aragami. Infiltrate the occupied city of Kyuryu with your supernatural powers and fight Light with Shadow. Uncover a story about twin souls bound together by destiny that surpasses time and memory.In Aragami: Nightfall, shadow assassins Hyo and Shinobu go after the mysterious ‘Alchemist’ in one last mission to bring back a long lost companion. Play as Hyo and Shinobu and use new Shadow Powers in a story campaign that will put your stealth skills to test.</desc>
		<marquee>./images/Aragami Shadow Edition-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Aragami Shadow Edition-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Aragami Shadow Edition-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Aragami Shadow Edition-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20190221T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Lince Works S.L.</developer>
		<publisher>Merge Games</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<family>Aragami</family>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073322" />
	</game>
	<game id="198449">
		<path>./Games/Astral Chain (World).xci</path>
		<name>Astral Chain</name>
		<desc>Master multiple combat styles in this synergetic action game!Humanity’s last chance against an interdimensional invasion is a special living weapon called the Legion. As a rookie officer in the elite police task force Neuron, you and your Legion will work together to solve cases and save humankind.The ASTRAL CHAIN game gives you full control over two characters at once for thrilling Synergetic Action, courtesy of PlatinumGames. Alternate between several Legion types and skills to save the world your way.</desc>
		<image>./images/Astral Chain (World)-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Astral Chain (World)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Astral Chain (World)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Astral Chain (World)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Astral Chain (World)-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Astral Chain (World)-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20190830T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>PlatinumGames Inc</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>wr</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073329" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Atelier Lydie and Suelle The Alchemist and the Mysterious Paintings.xci</path>
		<name>Atelier Lydie and Suelle The Alchemist and the Mysterious Paintings</name>
		<marquee>./images/Atelier Lydie and Suelle The Alchemist and the Mysterious Paintings-marquee.png</marquee>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073330" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Atelier Shallie Alchemists of the Dusk Sea DX.nsp</path>
		<name>Atelier Shallie Alchemists of the Dusk Sea DX</name>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073332" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Attack on Titan 2 (alt).xci</path>
		<name>Attack on Titan 2 (alt)</name>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073333" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Attack on Titan 2.xci</path>
		<name>Attack on Titan 2</name>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073335" />
	</game>
	<game id="195937">
		<path>./Games/Azure Striker Gunvolt - Striker Pack (Europe, USA).xci</path>
		<name>Azure Striker Gunvolt - Striker Pack</name>
		<desc>In "Azure Striker Gunvolt", you take control of Gunvolt's high-speed mobility and repertoire of electrical attacks to make short work of your enemies. As an "adept" who possesses supernatural "septimal powers," Gunvolt fights for the freedom of the nation from the tyrannical rule of the massive conglomerate known as the Sumeragi Group and the invasion of a super-powerful group of adepts known as Eden.</desc>
		<image>./images/Azure Striker Gunvolt - Striker Pack (Europe, USA)-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Azure Striker Gunvolt - Striker Pack (Europe, USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Azure Striker Gunvolt - Striker Pack (Europe, USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Azure Striker Gunvolt - Striker Pack (Europe, USA)-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Azure Striker Gunvolt - Striker Pack (Europe, USA)-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20170831T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Inti Creates Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Inti Creates Co., Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073337" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Badland - Game of the Year Edition.xci</path>
		<name>Badland - Game of the Year Edition</name>
		<video>./videos/Badland - Game of the Year Edition-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Badland - Game of the Year Edition-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Badland - Game of the Year Edition-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Badland - Game of the Year Edition-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Badland - Game of the Year Edition-boxback.png</boxback>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073339" />
	</game>
	<game id="359227">
		<path>./Games/BALAN WONDERWORLD.xci</path>
		<name>Balan Wonderworld</name>
		<desc>Welcome to a wonderous all-action show, the likes of which has never been seen before! 
BALAN WONDERWORLD is a wondrous action platformer game themed around the Balan Theatre. Led by the enigmatic maestro named Balan, the stars of the show Emma and Leo will use special abilities from a multitude of characterful costumes as they adventure in the bizarre and imaginary land of Wonderworld. Here memories and vistas from the real world mix with the things that people hold dear. 
Twelve different tales await our stars in the Wonderworld, each with their own unique quirks. They will explore all corners of these labyrinthine stages, filled with a myriad of tricks and traps, to get to the heart of each story.</desc>
		<thumbnail>./images/BALAN WONDERWORLD-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/BALAN WONDERWORLD-boxback.png</boxback>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073344" />
	</game>
	<game id="197697">
		<path>./Games/Banner Saga Trilogy.xci</path>
		<name>The Banner Saga Trilogy</name>
		<desc>Weave your own thread through this epic strategy RPG adventure. Guide your caravan across the landsacpe of a breaking world, where tough choices, bold leadership decisions, wise use of resources and skillful battle tactics all matter in this desperate struggle for survival.- Beautifully hand drawn combat sequences and animations, accompanied by an evocative score from Grammy-nominated composer Austin Wintory, will immerse you into a fantasy realm inspired by Norse mythology.- Choose from 48 playable characters from 4 different races and 40 classes, each with unique abilities and upgrade options.- Strategic combat with consequences where victory or defeat and even the permanent loss of a character depends on which characters you choose to take into battle.- Your role in building and managing your caravan as you travel the vast landscape is critical to not only your own survival but the survival of an entire civilization.</desc>
		<image>./images/Banner Saga Trilogy-image.jpg</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Banner Saga Trilogy-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/Banner Saga Trilogy-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20180920T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Stoic Studio</developer>
		<publisher>Gearbox Publishing</publisher>
		<genre>Compilation / Tactical RPG</genre>
		<family>The Banner Saga</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073347" />
	</game>
	<game id="195917">
		<path>./Games/Batman - The Telltale Series.xci</path>
		<name>Batman - The Telltale Series</name>
		<desc>The billionaire and the bat: enter the fractured psyche of Bruce Wayne and discover the powerful and far-reaching consequences of your choices as the Dark Knight. In this gritty and violent new story, you'll make discoveries that will shatter Bruce Wayne's world, and shake the stability of a corrupt Gotham City to its very foundations. At your disposal is the sophisticated genius of Wayne and the fearsome skills of the Batman. What happens next is entirely up to you.</desc>
		<marquee>./images/Batman - The Telltale Series-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Batman - The Telltale Series-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Batman - The Telltale Series-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Batman - The Telltale Series-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20171114T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>LCG Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Athlon Games</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure / Graphics</genre>
		<family>Batman</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073349" />
	</game>
	<game id="196049">
		<path>./Games/Battle Chasers - Nightwar.xci</path>
		<name>Battle Chasers - Nightwar</name>
		<desc>Battle Chasers: Nightwar is an RPG inspired by the console genre-greats, featuring deep dungeon diving, turn-based combat presented in classic JRPG format, and a rich story driven by exploration of the world.</desc>
		<image>./images/Battle Chasers - Nightwar-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Battle Chasers - Nightwar-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Battle Chasers - Nightwar-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/Battle Chasers - Nightwar-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20180515T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Airship Syndicate</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073351" />
	</game>
	<game id="195951">
		<path>./Games/Bayonetta 2.xci</path>
		<name>Bayonetta 2</name>
		<desc>Bayonetta is back with stylish moves and powerful weaponsBayonetta's back and more powerful than ever. Wield wild weapons and execute deadly moves—like the powerful Umbran Climax—to take out angels and demons in this breathtaking action game. You can even team up with friends in 2-player online or local wireless co-op fights (additional accessories required; sold separately.)Bayonetta is a butt-kicking, havoc-wreaking witch who wields sweet weapons like pistols, whips, hammers, flamethrowers, and poison bows. But it's not just about brawn—it's also about style. Bayonetta is deadly but sleek, with moves like Witch Time that slows down time itself, and the all-new Umbran Climax—a special magic attack that summons Infernal Demons to devastate enemies.The Bayonetta 2 game also features an online and local wireless 2-player cooperative mode where players bet halos on their performance and work together to amplify their sass, cause destruction, and score some riches.</desc>
		<image>./images/Bayonetta 2-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Bayonetta 2-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Bayonetta 2-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Bayonetta 2-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Bayonetta 2-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Bayonetta 2-boxback.png</boxback>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20180216T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>PlatinumGames</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<family>Bayonetta</family>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073353" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Ben 10.xci</path>
		<name>Ben 10</name>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073355" />
	</game>
	<game id="198107">
		<path>./Games/BLADE ARCUS Rebellion from Shining.xci</path>
		<name>Blade Arcus Rebellion From Shining</name>
		<desc>Peace has arrived in the continent of Alfheim, however, it was again disturbed. Now the continent of Alfhiem and the fantasy continent of Endias are connected at the gate of the sealed god opens a new journey and a new story to unfold.Now for the gameplay, players can select up to two characters to form a tag-team pairing. As you fight against your opponent, you can switch your primary character to your secondary character after each round. Of course, the main objective is to defeat your opponents. So, you better crush them down using your character’s special skills for on your way to victory.</desc>
		<marquee>./images/BLADE ARCUS Rebellion from Shining-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/BLADE ARCUS Rebellion from Shining-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/BLADE ARCUS Rebellion from Shining-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20190314T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Studio Saizensen</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / Versus</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073358" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/BLAZBLUE CENTRALFICTION.xci</path>
		<name>BLAZBLUE CENTRALFICTION</name>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073359" />
	</game>
	<game id="196115">
		<path>./Games/BlazBlue Cross Tag Battle.xci</path>
		<name>BlazBlue - Cross Tag Battle</name>
		<desc>THE COLLISION IS INEVITABLE! THE IMPACT WILL BE UNAVOIDABLE!
An unrivaled clash of explosive proportions! The beloved BlazBlue franchise Crosses universes, Tags in fan favorites, and Battles it out in BlazBlue: Cross Tag Battle! Created through an all-star collaboration between BlazBlue, Atlus' Persona, French Bread's Under Night In-Birth, and Rooster Teeth's hugely popular RWBY web series, Cross Tag Battle celebrates the fighting genre for pros and newcomers alike! Choose your team in fast paced 2v2 team battles filled with the craziness you've come to love from BlazBlue, with all the tight mechanics, smooth gameplay, and gorgeous 2D graphics you expect from Arc System Works.</desc>
		<image>./images/BlazBlue Cross Tag Battle-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/BlazBlue Cross Tag Battle-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/BlazBlue Cross Tag Battle-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/BlazBlue Cross Tag Battle-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/BlazBlue Cross Tag Battle-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20180605T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Arc System Works</developer>
		<publisher>Arc System Works</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<family>BlazBlue</family>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073402" />
	</game>
	<game id="197689">
		<path>./Games/Broken Sword 5 The Serpents Curse.xci</path>
		<name>Broken Sword 5 - The Serpents Curse</name>
		<desc>Paris in the spring. Shots ring out from a gallery.

A robbery... a murder... and the beginning of another epic Broken Sword adventure.

Playing as intrepid American George Stobbart and sassy French journalist Nico Collard, you find yourself on the trail of a stolen painting - and a murderous conspiracy. A conspiracy whose roots lie in mysteries older than the written word...

Armed only with logic, integrity and a wry sense of humor - can George and Nico save mankind from disaster? Can you solve the secret of the Serpent's Curse? A curse some say was forged by the Devil himself...</desc>
		<image>./images/Broken Sword 5 The Serpents Curse-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20180921T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Revolution</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073405" />
	</game>
	<game id="197757">
		<path>./Games/Candle The Power of the Flame.xci</path>
		<name>Candle - The Power Of The Flame</name>
		<desc>Candle is an adventure with challenging puzzles. Play as Teku, a young novice on a dangerous journey to rescue his tribe's shaman from the evil tribe of the Wakcha. But the way is littered with sinister traps and difficult obstacles.</desc>
		<releasedate>20180726T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Teku Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Merge Games</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073407" />
	</game>
	<game id="196203">
		<path>./Games/Captain Toad - Treasure Tracker.xci</path>
		<name>Captain Toad Treasure Tracker</name>
		<desc>Captain Toad stars in his own puzzling quest on the Nintendo Switch™ system! Our stubby hero must dodge dangers and track treasures across many trap-filled courses. Survive smoldering volcanoes, hazardous steam engines, haunted houses, and even new courses based on the Super Mario Odyssey™ game! Luckily, a second player can join in by tossing turnips at enemies.</desc>
		<image>./images/Captain Toad - Treasure Tracker-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Captain Toad - Treasure Tracker-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Captain Toad - Treasure Tracker-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Captain Toad - Treasure Tracker-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Captain Toad - Treasure Tracker-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Captain Toad - Treasure Tracker-boxback.png</boxback>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20180701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073409" />
	</game>
	<game id="195831">
		<path>./Games/Cars 3 - Driven to Win.xci</path>
		<name>Cars 3: Driven to Win</name>
		<desc>Start your engines and gear up for the ultimate racing experience in Cars 3: Driven to Win inspired by Disney Pixar's film, Cars 3. Play with over 20 customizable characters including Lightning McQueen, Jackson Storm, Cruz Ramirez and the next generation of racers in over 20 tracks set in iconic locations from the film such as Radiator Springs.

Train and advance your abilities in 6 game modes and challenge your family and friends in the Battle Race to become the Ultimate Champion. On the road to becoming a Hall of Fame Driver, training and skill will give you an edge in a race that anyone can win.</desc>
		<image>./images/Cars 3 - Driven to Win-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Cars 3 - Driven to Win-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Cars 3 - Driven to Win-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Cars 3 - Driven to Win-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Cars 3 - Driven to Win-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20170613T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>TT Games</developer>
		<publisher>WB Games</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<family>Cars</family>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073412" />
	</game>
	<game id="196449">
		<path>./Games/Cat Quest.xci</path>
		<name>Cat Quest</name>
		<desc>Leap into a grand adventure in purrsuit of the evil Drakoth and your catnapped sister! Explore Felingard's huge overworld map, risk life and limb delving into dungeons for epic loot, and lend a paw to a furry cast of characters in a flurry of side quests.</desc>
		<image>./images/Cat Quest-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Cat Quest-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Cat Quest-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/Cat Quest-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20171110T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>The Gentlebros</developer>
		<publisher>PQube</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073415" />
	</game>
	<game id="359311">
		<path>./Games/Catherine Full Body.xci</path>
		<name>Catherine: Full Body</name>
		<desc>Our indecisive protagonist, Vincent, has been with his long-time girlfriend, Katherine, for five years. But instead of taking the next step into marriage, Vincent finds himself in an affair with the provocative blonde bombshell, Catherine! Thrown into discord by his own infidelity, he finds solace in the innocent Rin – further complicating matters. Adding to Vincent's dilemma, he begins having nightmares that force him to climb for his life... Will he survive the trials and tribulations of love, or fall to temptations?</desc>
		<image>./images/Catherine Full Body-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Catherine Full Body-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Catherine Full Body-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Catherine Full Body-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Catherine Full Body-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20200707T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Studio Zero</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073417" />
	</game>
	<game id="197819">
		<path>./Games/Chicken Range.xci</path>
		<name>Chicken Range</name>
		<desc>Fun and Quirky shoot-em-up game.

The object of the game is to shoot the chickens using an array of different weaponry, from pistols, to AK47, RPG's to Alien Ray Guns! Gameplay is set over a field twice as wide as the screen, so you must be constantly moving your aim side to side in order to reach the whole game field.

To increase the difficulty, the chickens throw eggs at the screen to obscure the player's field of view. Once your screen is covered….GAME OVER!

During each level, ammo crates drop at varying intervals which will refresh your ammo levels and “Shino”.</desc>
		<thumbnail>./images/Chicken Range-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/Chicken Range-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20181025T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Funbox Media</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073423" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Child Of Light Ultimate Edition Plus Valiant Hearts The Great War.xci</path>
		<name>Child Of Light Ultimate Edition Plus Valiant Hearts The Great War</name>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073424" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Closed Nightmare CHT.xci</path>
		<name>Closed Nightmare CHT</name>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073426" />
	</game>
	<game id="196261">
		<path>./Games/Code of Princess EX.xci</path>
		<name>Code Of Princess Ex</name>
		<desc>Code of Princess EX brings a unique combination of hack-and-slash beat-'em-up action and role-playing depth to Nintendo Switch™! The story follows Princess Solange of DeLuxia as she fights to restore order in a world where monsters are trying to overtake the human race. Armed with the legendary sword DeLuxcalibur, Solange assembles a team of talented fighters to join her quest. Together, they embark on an epic journey where they will confront the monster uprising and try to discover it's secret origins.</desc>
		<image>./images/Code of Princess EX-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Code of Princess EX-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Code of Princess EX-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Code of Princess EX-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Code of Princess EX-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20180731T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Studio Saizensen</developer>
		<publisher>Nicalis</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073429" />
	</game>
	<game id="198079">
		<path>./Games/Constructor Plus.xci</path>
		<name>Constructor Plus</name>
		<desc>Take on the role of a budding property developer and build yourself up from minor-league housing crook to interplanetary property tycoon, wheeling, dealing and thieving all the way.</desc>
		<thumbnail>./images/Constructor Plus-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/Constructor Plus-boxback.png</boxback>
		<developer>System 3 Software</developer>
		<publisher>System 3 Software</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073435" />
	</game>
	<game id="196153">
		<path>./Games/Crash Bandicoot N. Sane Trilogy.xci</path>
		<name>Crash Bandicoot N. Sane Trilogy</name>
		<desc>Play Crash Bandicoot™ anywhere!Your favorite marsupial, Crash Bandicoot™, is back! He's enhanced, entranced and ready-to-dance with the N. Sane Trilogy game collection. Now you can experience Crash Bandicoot like never before. Spin, jump, wump and repeat as you take on the epic challenges and adventures through the three games that started it all, Crash Bandicoot™, Crash Bandicoot™ 2: Cortex Strikes Back and Crash Bandicoot™ 3: Warped. Relive all your favorite Crash moments in their fully-remastered graphical glory and get ready to put some UMPH in your WUMP!</desc>
		<image>./images/Crash Bandicoot N. Sane Trilogy-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Crash Bandicoot N. Sane Trilogy-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Crash Bandicoot N. Sane Trilogy-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Crash Bandicoot N. Sane Trilogy-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Crash Bandicoot N. Sane Trilogy-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20180629T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Toys For Bob</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Platform / Run Jump</genre>
		<family>Crash Bandicoot</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073438" />
	</game>
	<game id="198331">
		<path>./Games/Crash Team Racing Nitro-Fueled (USA, Europe).xci</path>
		<name>Crash Team Racing Nitro-fueled</name>
		<desc>Crash is back in the driver's seat! Get ready to go fur-throttle with Crash™ Team Racing Nitro-Fueled. It's the authentic CTR experience plus a whole lot more, now fully-remastered and revved up to the max</desc>
		<image>./images/Crash Team Racing Nitro-Fueled (USA, Europe)-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Crash Team Racing Nitro-Fueled (USA, Europe)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Crash Team Racing Nitro-Fueled (USA, Europe)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Crash Team Racing Nitro-Fueled (USA, Europe)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Crash Team Racing Nitro-Fueled (USA, Europe)-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Crash Team Racing Nitro-Fueled (USA, Europe)-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20190621T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Beenox Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-8</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073440" />
	</game>
	<game id="197753">
		<path>./Games/Crayola Scoot.xci</path>
		<name>Crayola Scoot</name>
		<desc>Creativity wins in this colorful freestyle scooter championship! In Crayola Scoot, more tricks mean more color – and color can change the world in impossible ways. So get ready to take on Scoot Legends in a rainbow of thrilling events, or grab 3 friends for a split-screen color clash. It’s time to make your mark on the scootpark!</desc>
		<marquee>./images/Crayola Scoot-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Crayola Scoot-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/Crayola Scoot-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20181016T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Climax Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Outright Games</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073443" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Cris Tales.xci</path>
		<name>Cris Tales</name>
		<marquee>./images/Cris Tales-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Cris Tales-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Cris Tales-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Cris Tales-boxback.png</boxback>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073445" />
	</game>
	<game id="197769">
		<path>./Games/Dark Souls Remastered.xci</path>
		<name>Dark Souls - Remastered</name>
		<desc>Deep and Dark Universe— Delve into an epic dark fantasy universe stricken by the Curse. Explore its intricate world design, full of hidden passages, dungeons and secrets.

Each End is a New Beginning— Each playthrough surprises you with new challenges and discoveries.</desc>
		<image>./images/Dark Souls Remastered-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Dark Souls Remastered-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Dark Souls Remastered-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Dark Souls Remastered-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Dark Souls Remastered-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Dark Souls Remastered-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20181019T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>From Software</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure / Action RPG</genre>
		<family>Dark Souls</family>
		<players>1-6</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073447" />
	</game>
	<game id="196033">
		<path>./Games/Darkest Dungeon - Ancestral Edition.xci</path>
		<name>Darkest Dungeon - Ancestral Edition</name>
		<marquee>./images/Darkest Dungeon - Ancestral Edition-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Darkest Dungeon - Ancestral Edition-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Darkest Dungeon - Ancestral Edition-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<genre>Role playing games / Tactical RPG</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073450" />
	</game>
	<game id="198161">
		<path>./Games/Darksiders Warmastered Edition.xci</path>
		<name>Darksiders - Warmastered Edition</name>
		<desc>Deceived by the forces of evil into prematurely bringing about the end of the world, War – the first Horseman of the Apocalypse – stands accused of breaking the sacred law by inciting a war between Heaven and Hell. In the slaughter that ensued, the demonic forces defeated the heavenly hosts and laid claim to the Earth.</desc>
		<image>./images/Darksiders Warmastered Edition-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Darksiders Warmastered Edition-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Darksiders Warmastered Edition-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Darksiders Warmastered Edition-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Darksiders Warmastered Edition-boxback.png</boxback>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<family>Darksiders</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073452" />
	</game>
	<game id="197285">
		<path>./Games/de Blob 2.xci</path>
		<name>De Blob 2</name>
		<desc>In de Blob 2 Comrade Black and the Inkies are back with a whole new plot to rid the world of color. With all-new help from Papa Blanc and his followers the Blancs, Blob and his friends will have their work cut out for them bringing color back to the citizens of Prisma City.</desc>
		<image>./images/de Blob 2-image.png</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/de Blob 2-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/de Blob 2-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20180828T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>BlitWorks</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073454" />
	</game>
	<game id="196145">
		<path>./Games/de Blob.xci</path>
		<name>De Blob</name>
		<desc>de Blob is a 3D platformer where players maneuver their hero, de Blob. Equal parts amorphous blob of paint, struggling artist, revolutionary and juvenile delinquent, de Blob's goal is to replace the drab, lifeless gray coloring that the I.N.K.T. Corporation has imposed on Chroma City and its inhabitants, the Raydians, with a range of vibrant life-giving colors, all the while avoiding and battling the gray-clad forces of the Inkies.</desc>
		<image>./images/de Blob-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/de Blob-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/de Blob-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/de Blob-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20180626T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073456" />
	</game>
	<game id="198127">
		<path>./Games/Dead or Alive Xtreme 3 Scarlet.xci</path>
		<name>Dead Or Alive Xtreme 3 - Scarlet</name>
		<desc>Take on a vacation where you can have fun-fight on the south island. Various activities await you there! Build teamwork in beach volleyball, compete in a race to retrieve beach flags and rock climbing. You can also enjoy the benefit of Photo Paradise as you witness the charming and sexy characters. Take gravure pictures of them in a variety of poses and swimsuits</desc>
		<image>./images/Dead or Alive Xtreme 3 Scarlet-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Dead or Alive Xtreme 3 Scarlet-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Dead or Alive Xtreme 3 Scarlet-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Dead or Alive Xtreme 3 Scarlet-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Dead or Alive Xtreme 3 Scarlet-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Dead or Alive Xtreme 3 Scarlet-boxback.png</boxback>
		<publisher>Koei</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<family>Dead or Alive</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073458" />
	</game>
	<game id="197823">
		<path>./Games/Death Mark.xci</path>
		<name>Death Mark</name>
		<desc>You have been Marked...A strange rumor is spreading through the shadows of Tokyo's H City: a mysterious disfigurement, like a grotesque birthmark, has been appearing on the bodies of certain individuals. Anyone who receives the Mark will rapidly die of unknown, horrifying causes.Deprived of your memories, you arrive at a mansion rumored to protect the bearers of the Mark. As the doors swing open, the countdown to death has already begun...</desc>
		<thumbnail>./images/Death Mark-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/Death Mark-boxback.png</boxback>
		<publisher>Aksys Games</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073504" />
	</game>
	<game id="197817">
		<path>./Games/Diablo III Eternal Collection.xci</path>
		<name>Diablo III - Eternal Collection</name>
		<desc>Ages ago, angels and demons birthed your world in a forbidden union. Now they've come to claim it. Stand tall among Sanctuary's meek and wicked to battle walking corpses, horrifying cultists, fallen seraphs, and the Lords of Hell. When the High Heavens and the Burning Hells war, humanity must be its own salvation.</desc>
		<image>./images/Diablo III Eternal Collection-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Diablo III Eternal Collection-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Diablo III Eternal Collection-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Diablo III Eternal Collection-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Diablo III Eternal Collection-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20181102T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Blizzard Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Blizzard Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games / Action RPG</genre>
		<family>Diablo</family>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073507" />
	</game>
	<game id="197743">
		<path>./Games/Disgaea 1 Complete.xci</path>
		<name>Disgaea 1 Complete</name>
		<desc>Relive the expanded adventures of Laharl, Etna, and Flonne in Disgaea 1 Complete!</desc>
		<image>./images/Disgaea 1 Complete-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Disgaea 1 Complete-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Disgaea 1 Complete-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Disgaea 1 Complete-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Disgaea 1 Complete-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20181009T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nippon Ichi Software</developer>
		<publisher>NIS America</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<family>Disgaea</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073509" />
	</game>
	<game id="195833">
		<path>./Games/Disgaea 5 Complete.xci</path>
		<name>Disgaea 5 Complete</name>
		<desc>As a terrible Supreme Leader named Void Dark surfaces to enslave the countless Netherworlds, Killia, a young demon, dares to challenge him to end his reign. In Disgaea 5 Complete, lead Killia and her army of rebels on their dark and dangerous path to vengeance to thwart the plans of the Demonic Emperor.</desc>
		<image>./images/Disgaea 5 Complete-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Disgaea 5 Complete-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Disgaea 5 Complete-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Disgaea 5 Complete-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Disgaea 5 Complete-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20170523T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nippon Ichi Software</developer>
		<publisher>NIS America</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<family>Disgaea</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073511" />
	</game>
	<game id="196039">
		<path>./Games/Donkey Kong Country - Tropical Freeze.xci</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong Country : Tropical Freeze</name>
		<desc>Arctic invaders have turned Donkey Kong Island into their personal frozen fortress, and it's up to you to save the day. Play as Donkey Kong in Original Mode and team up with Diddy Kong, Dixie Kong, and Cranky Kong—each with unique abilities—to overcome platforming challenges and frosty foes.</desc>
		<image>./images/Donkey Kong Country - Tropical Freeze-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Donkey Kong Country - Tropical Freeze-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Donkey Kong Country - Tropical Freeze-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Donkey Kong Country - Tropical Freeze-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Donkey Kong Country - Tropical Freeze-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Donkey Kong Country - Tropical Freeze-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20180504T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Retro Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073513" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/DOOM.xci</path>
		<name>DOOM</name>
		<marquee>./images/DOOM-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/DOOM-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/DOOM-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/DOOM-boxback.png</boxback>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073515" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Dragan Ball Xenoverse 2.xci</path>
		<name>Dragan Ball Xenoverse 2</name>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073516" />
	</game>
	<game id="197705">
		<path>./Games/DRAGON BALL FighterZ.xci</path>
		<name>Dragon Ball Fighterz</name>
		<desc>DRAGON BALL FighterZ is born from what makes the DRAGON BALL series so loved and famous: endless spectacular fights with its all-powerful fighters.Partnering with Arc System Works, DRAGON BALL FighterZ maximizes high end Anime graphics and brings easy to learn but difficult to master fighting gameplay.High-end Anime GraphicsUsing the power of the Unreal engine and the talented team at Arc System Works, DRAGON BALL FighterZ is a visual tour-de-force.3vs3 Tag/SupportBuild your dream team and sharpen your skills to master high-speed tag combinations.Thrilling Online FeaturesRanked matches, interactive lobby, crazy 6-player Party Match... There is something for every taste!Exclusive Story ModeDiscover a scenario featuring Android 21, a brand new character whose creation was supervised by Akira Toriyama himself.</desc>
		<image>./images/DRAGON BALL FighterZ-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/DRAGON BALL FighterZ-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/DRAGON BALL FighterZ-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/DRAGON BALL FighterZ-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/DRAGON BALL FighterZ-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/DRAGON BALL FighterZ-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20180928T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Bandai Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<family>Dragon Ball Z</family>
		<players>1-6</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073519" />
	</game>
	<game id="198191">
		<path>./Games/Dragons Dogma Dark Arisen.xci</path>
		<name>Dragons Dogma - Dark Arisen</name>
		<desc>Choose between three different starter vocations, which you can further develop for a total of nine unique vocations. Use a dynamic combat system to wield devastating skills and magicks to tackle deadly foes. Embark on your epic adventure with three AI companions, known as Pawns. These partners fight independently, demonstrating prowess and ability that they have developed based on traits learned from your playing style. Share these Pawns online and reap rewards of treasure, tips, and strategy hints for taking down the terrifying enemies.</desc>
		<releasedate>20190423T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073521" />
	</game>
	<game id="196013">
		<path>./Games/Farming Simulator - Nintendo Switch Edition.xci</path>
		<name>Farming Simulator Nintendo Switch Edition</name>
		<desc>Take on the challenges of the modern farmer! Explore a huge open world including a detailed North American environment, loaded with farming activities, over hundreds of acres of land. Drive over 250 authentic farming vehicles and equipment from over 75 manufacturers, including brands such as Challenger, Fendt, Massey Ferguson and Valtra.

Harvest many types of crops, tend to your livestock, take part in forestry work, and sell your products to expand and invest in your farm! Transport your goods in trucks and trailers, or load and drive trains to reach your destination.</desc>
		<image>./images/Farming Simulator - Nintendo Switch Edition-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Farming Simulator - Nintendo Switch Edition-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Farming Simulator - Nintendo Switch Edition-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>20171107T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Giants Software</developer>
		<publisher>Focus Home Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<family>Farming Simulator</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073523" />
	</game>
	<game id="195845">
		<path>./Games/Fate Extella - The Umbral Star.xci</path>
		<name>Fate/extella - The Umbral Star</name>
		<desc>Experience lightning-fast battlefield action across an epic story! In the digital realm of SE.RA.PH, the Holy Grail War is over, but the land's new ruler faces challenges and threats from all sides. The servants now find themselves drawing up tense and unlikely alliances, preparing for a conflict that may tear SE.RA.PH apart...or destroy it entirely.</desc>
		<marquee>./images/Fate Extella - The Umbral Star-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Fate Extella - The Umbral Star-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>20170725T000000</releasedate>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073525" />
	</game>
	<game id="198011">
		<path>./Games/Fate EXTELLA LINK.xci</path>
		<name>Fate/extella Link</name>
		<desc>Servants from across the Fate series have come together to battle a new sinister threat to SE.RA.PH. Fully-loaded with new elements, Fate/EXTELLA LINK includes never-before-seen servants, fresh scenarios, polished graphics and refined gameplay.</desc>
		<marquee>./images/Fate EXTELLA LINK-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Fate EXTELLA LINK-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>20190319T000000</releasedate>
		<players>1-8</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073527" />
	</game>
	<game id="196011">
		<path>./Games/FIFA 18.xci</path>
		<name>FIFA 18</name>
		<desc>Are you ready for your biggest season yet?FIFA 18 on Nintendo Switch™ is the most immersive, social, and authentic football game ever created for Nintendo players. Feature packed, you can now play the world's game anytime, anywhere and in unique ways with FIFA 18 on Nintendo Switch.BUILT FOR NINTENDO SWITCH.Your FIFA, Your Way: Brand-new ways to play single and multiplayer on the most social FIFA experience ever. With a variety of controller and display configurations available, as well as split Joy-Con™ support, FIFA 18 on Nintendo Switch offers a responsive and engaging gaming experience – no matter how you play.YOUR FAVOURITE FIFA MODES.With FIFA Ultimate Team, Career Mode, and Nintendo Switch-tailored Kickoff, and Local Seasons, FIFA 18 on Nintendo Switch is the deepest portable FIFA ever.FUT ICONS.Ronaldo Nazario. Diego Maradona. Pele. Ronaldinho. Play with the most iconic legends of football in FIFA Ultimate Team. Experience unique versions of each ICON with Stories, with ratings that reflect how their style and attributes evolved throughout their illustrious careers.</desc>
		<image>./images/FIFA 18-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/FIFA 18-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/FIFA 18-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/FIFA 18-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/FIFA 18-boxback.png</boxback>
		<developer>EA Games</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Soccer</genre>
		<family>FIFA</family>
		<players>1-8</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073531" />
	</game>
	<game id="197713">
		<path>./Games/Fifa 19.xci</path>
		<name>Fifa 19</name>
		<desc>CHAMPIONS RISE IN FIFA 19EA SPORTS™ FIFA 19 delivers a champion-caliber experience on and off the pitch. Led by the prestigious UEFA Champions League, FIFA 19 offers enhanced gameplay features that allow you to control the pitch in every moment. There are new and unrivaled ways to play, including a new mode in the ever-popular FIFA Ultimate Team™ and a new Kick-Off mode experience. Champions Rise in FIFA 19.UEFA Champions League / UEFA Europa League / UEFA Super CupPlay the pinnacle of club football across a variety of modes in FIFA 19 with official match presentation, breadth in tournament experiences, including UEFA Champions League, Europa League and Super Cup, and an all-new commentary team in Derek Rae and Lee Dixon.In-Match ExperienceImmerse yourself in the most authentic football experience ever seen before on Nintendo Switch™. Featuring distinctive team and player personalities, introducing official broadcast presentation for the some of the world’s biggest leagues, and elevating your ability to finish with the all-new striking overhaul.Console ConfigurationsExperience FIFA wherever, whenever and however you want. Connect to your television and play Single or Multiplayer, or take the same modes on-the-go.Split Joy-Con™ SupportBuilt exclusively for Nintendo Switch, Split Joy-Con™ controls enables you to compete with your friends anytime and anywhere. Without any additional hardware, players can separate the Joy-Con™ controllers and enjoy multiplayer game modes at home, or on the go. FIFA 19 Standard Edition includes:• 1 Loan Player Item: One of Neymar Jr., Kevin De Bruyne or Paulo Dybala for 10 FUT Matches*• 4 UEFA Champions League Kits*• 5 UEFA Champions League Player Items (up to 85 overall rating)</desc>
		<image>./images/Fifa 19-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Fifa 19-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Fifa 19-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/Fifa 19-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20180928T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>EA Games</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Soccer</genre>
		<family>FIFA</family>
		<players>1-8</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073534" />
	</game>
	<game id="198173">
		<path>./Games/Final Fantasy X X 2 HD Remaster.xci</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy X X-2 Hd Remaster</name>
		<desc>FINAL FANTASY X-2 returns to the world of Spira two years after the beginning of the Eternal Calm. Having been shown a mysterious but familiar image in a sphere, Yuna becomes a Sphere Hunter and along with her companions Rikku and Paine, embarks on a quest around the world to find the answers to the mystery within.</desc>
		<image>./images/Final Fantasy X X 2 HD Remaster-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Final Fantasy X X 2 HD Remaster-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Final Fantasy X X 2 HD Remaster-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Final Fantasy X X 2 HD Remaster-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Final Fantasy X X 2 HD Remaster-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Final Fantasy X X 2 HD Remaster-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20190416T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<family>Final Fantasy</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073537" />
	</game>
	<game id="198197">
		<path>./Games/Final Fantasy XII The Zodiac Age.xci</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy Xii The Zodiac Age</name>
		<desc>Return to the World of Ivalice…

This HD remaster is based on the smash hit 12th instalment of the FINAL FANTASY series, which has shipped over 6,100,000 units worldwide, featuring a new, re-worked game design!

Not only have the graphics and sound been updated to take advantage of the power of new hardware, but the core game design has also been tweaked to produce an evolution of the original FFXII fitting for the current generation.

Enjoy a classic adventure reborn!</desc>
		<image>./images/Final Fantasy XII The Zodiac Age-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Final Fantasy XII The Zodiac Age-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Final Fantasy XII The Zodiac Age-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Final Fantasy XII The Zodiac Age-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Final Fantasy XII The Zodiac Age-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Final Fantasy XII The Zodiac Age-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20180430T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<family>Final Fantasy</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073539" />
	</game>
	<game id="198389">
		<path>./Games/Fire Emblem - Three Houses (World) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It,Zh,Ko).xci</path>
		<name>Fire Emblem: Three Houses</name>
		<desc>War is coming to the continent of Fódlan. Here, order is maintained by the Church of Seiros, which hosts the prestigious Officer's Academy within its headquarters. You are invited to teach one of its three mighty houses, each comprised of students brimming with personality and represented by a royal from one of three territories.</desc>
		<image>./images/Fire Emblem - Three Houses (World) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It,Zh,Ko)-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Fire Emblem - Three Houses (World) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It,Zh,Ko)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Fire Emblem - Three Houses (World) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It,Zh,Ko)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Fire Emblem - Three Houses (World) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It,Zh,Ko)-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Fire Emblem - Three Houses (World) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It,Zh,Ko)-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20190726T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<family>Fire Emblem</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>de,en,jp,es,fr,it</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073542" />
	</game>
	<game id="195867">
		<path>./Games/Fire Emblem Warriors.xci</path>
		<name>Fire Emblem Warriors</name>
		<desc>Clash with legions of enemies as Marth, Xander, Corrin, Chrom, and other warriors from Fire Emblem by unleashing over-the-top-powerful Dynasty Warriors-style moves. Take control of characters with distinct attacks, issue strategic commands, pair up warriors for stunning moves, and more in an epic tactical action game from the Hyrule Warriors team.</desc>
		<image>./images/Fire Emblem Warriors-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Fire Emblem Warriors-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Fire Emblem Warriors-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Fire Emblem Warriors-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Fire Emblem Warriors-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20171020T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Koei</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<family>Fire Emblem</family>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073544" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Furi.xci</path>
		<name>Furi</name>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073546" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Gal Gun 2.xci</path>
		<name>Gal Gun 2</name>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073548" />
	</game>
	<game id="196079">
		<path>./Games/Gal Metal.xci</path>
		<name>Gal Metal</name>
		<desc>Take down alien invaders with the power of metal!

One night while on his way home from school, a high school boy is abducted by the Octoids, an extraterrestrial species bent on revenge. The boy's soul is transplanted into a high school girl's body in a sinister experiment. Now sharing a body, the duo must work together with her high school band, K.M.G. (Kichijoji Metal Girls) to defeat the aliens with their greatest weakness: metal!</desc>
		<thumbnail>./images/Gal Metal-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/Gal Metal-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20181030T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>DMM GAMES</developer>
		<publisher>Marvelous Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Music and Dance</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073553" />
	</game>
	<game id="195879">
		<path>./Games/Gear Club Unlimited.xci</path>
		<name>Gear Club Unlimited</name>
		<desc>Get behind the wheel of the most incredible cars from the most prestigious manufacturers. Race through over 400 challenging races. Learn to master the controls of the world's fastest supercars and collect them in your garage: you can customize and tune them across the numerous workshops, then take them to the race track for the win!</desc>
		<thumbnail>./images/Gear Club Unlimited-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/Gear Club Unlimited-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20171121T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Microïds</developer>
		<publisher>Microïds</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073559" />
	</game>
	<game id="196279">
		<path>./Games/Genso Wanderer Reloaded.xci</path>
		<name>Gensowanderer -reloaded-</name>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073601" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Ghosts n Goblins Resurrection.xci</path>
		<name>Ghosts n Goblins Resurrection</name>
		<video>./videos/Ghosts n Goblins Resurrection-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Ghosts n Goblins Resurrection-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Ghosts n Goblins Resurrection-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Ghosts n Goblins Resurrection-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<manual>./manuals/Ghosts n Goblins Resurrection-manual.pdf</manual>
		<boxback>./images/Ghosts n Goblins Resurrection-boxback.png</boxback>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073603" />
	</game>
	<game id="197711">
		<path>./Games/Giana Sisters Twisted Dreams Owltimate Edition.xci</path>
		<name>Giana Sisters - Twisted Dreams - Owltimate Edition</name>
		<desc>Fluidly morph between two dynamically different dream worlds to solve puzzles and combat grueling enemies and bosses.</desc>
		<marquee>./images/Giana Sisters Twisted Dreams Owltimate Edition-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Giana Sisters Twisted Dreams Owltimate Edition-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/Giana Sisters Twisted Dreams Owltimate Edition-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20180928T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Black Forest Games</developer>
		<publisher>Handygames</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<family>Giana Sisters</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073605" />
	</game>
	<game id="196581">
		<path>./Games/Ginger Beyond The Crystal.xci</path>
		<name>Ginger - Beyond The Crystal</name>
		<desc>A world destroyed by a crystal explosion, a mysterious threat hanging over its inhabitants, and a goddess who creates a hero. This is Ginger: Beyond The Crystal.

The towns are devastated and their inhabitants disappeared, but there is still hope. Ginger must reestablish the connection with the goddess by purifying corrupted crystals that have spread throughout the worlds.</desc>
		<image>./images/Ginger Beyond The Crystal-image.jpg</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Ginger Beyond The Crystal-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>20171117T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Badland Games</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073608" />
	</game>
	<game id="198063">
		<path>./Games/Girls und Panzer Dream Tank Match DX.xci</path>
		<name>Girls Und Panzer - Dream Tank Match Dx</name>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073610" />
	</game>
	<game id="196249">
		<path>./Games/Go Vacation.xci</path>
		<name>Go Vacation</name>
		<desc>Welcome to Kawawii Island, a paradise resort where friends and family can enjoy 50+ co-op and competitive activities. There are all sorts of exciting ways to explore the island.</desc>
		<image>./images/Go Vacation-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Go Vacation-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Go Vacation-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>20180727T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bandai Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073612" />
	</game>
	<game id="196155">
		<path>./Games/God Wars The Complete Legend.xci</path>
		<name>God Wars - Nihon Shinwa Taisen</name>
		<desc>This new version features improvements such as sped up battles, improvements to the Help feature, the ability to dispatch units of 8 characters (instead of 6 previously, though only in high level stages apparently), a raised level and skill cap, and a New Game+ mode.But that’s not all: Momotaro, the Pheasant, the Monkey, and the Dog are to be playable. There will also be a brand new episode, and the developers are adding a multi-ending system. Finally, there’s a new theme song sung by Orihime (a new character voiced by Yuu Serizawa).The Famitsu article also mentions DLC, with the following:an additional story called “Hyuga’s Future”, featuring new types of enemies;Labyrinth of Yomi, that you can play after clearing the main story. Includes Momotaro and 3 animals, but also multiple endings, various balance adjustments, and more</desc>
		<image>./images/God Wars The Complete Legend-image.jpg</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/God Wars The Complete Legend-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/God Wars The Complete Legend-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20180831T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Kadokawa Shoten</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073614" />
	</game>
	<game id="197745">
		<path>./Games/Goosebumps The Game.xci</path>
		<name>Goosebumps - The Game</name>
		<desc>The walk home from school today is going to be a lot spookier than usual… Your sleepy neighborhood’s been overrun by monsters! Werewolves prowl the woods, Gnomes roam underfoot and scarecrows walk at midnight. But these aren’t ordinary monsters — they’re R.L. Stine’s famous Goosebumps monsters, released from their books and looking to wreak havoc!You’ll need to use your wits to investigate the surroundings,puzzle out clues, and outsmart the monsters before it’s too late!Survive a trek through your neighborhood, unravel the mysteriesof the Dead House, and sneak through the mall after hours; only then can you confront Slappy and stop his plans for revenge!</desc>
		<thumbnail>./images/Goosebumps The Game-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/Goosebumps The Game-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20181009T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Wayforward</developer>
		<publisher>GameMill</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073621" />
	</game>
	<game id="359984">
		<path>./Games/Greak Memories of Azur.xci</path>
		<name>Greak: Memories of Azur</name>
		<marquee>./images/Greak Memories of Azur-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Greak Memories of Azur-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Greak Memories of Azur-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Greak Memories of Azur-boxback.png</boxback>
		<publisher>Team17</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073623" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Hades.xci</path>
		<name>Hades</name>
		<marquee>./images/Hades-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Hades-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Hades-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Hades-boxback.png</boxback>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073625" />
	</game>
	<game id="359965">
		<path>./Games/Harvest Moon - One World (Europe).xci</path>
		<name>Harvest Moon: One World</name>
		<desc>Trek across beaches, the desert, and even a volcano in the latest entry into the long-running Harvest Moon series! The Harvest Goddess has gone missing, and it's up to you to help bring her back! Along the way, you'll come across cows, sheep, camels, and even reindeer! Dig in, because in this game, the world is literally your oyster! Before the Harvest Goddess disappeared from this world, she imbued the tiny Harvest Wisps with the knowledge of various seeds, thus ensuring the various fruits and vegetables of the world would not be lost. Using the power given to these Harvest Wisps, you'll unlock various seeds as you progress through the game! But the Harvest Wisps can be tricky to find, as they all appear at different times and places. You'll need to use your noggin to make sure to seek as many as you can of them out!</desc>
		<image>./images/Harvest Moon - One World (Europe)-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Harvest Moon - One World (Europe)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Harvest Moon - One World (Europe)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Harvest Moon - One World (Europe)-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Harvest Moon - One World (Europe)-boxback.png</boxback>
		<publisher>Rising Star Games</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<family>Harvest Moon</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073627" />
	</game>
	<game id="197811">
		<path>./Games/Hasbro Game Night.xci</path>
		<name>Hasbro Game Night</name>
		<desc>Play MONOPOLY, TRIVIAL PURSUIT LIVE!, and RISK anytime, anywhere. Challenge family, friends, and players around the world. Choose your favorite game mode and enjoy hours of fun with Hasbro Game Night for Nintendo Switch™!Great value: Three classic games in one bundle, providing hours of entertainment.MONOPOLY: Discover 3D boards, exclusive tokens, and new ways to play, including shorter sessions. For up to six players.TRIVIAL PURSUIT LIVE!: Experience the thrill of TV-show trivia gameplay with up to three other players.RISK: Lead troops to victory in this modern version of the classic, with 3D visuals and custom rules. Up to four players.</desc>
		<thumbnail>./images/Hasbro Game Night-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/Hasbro Game Night-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20181030T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1-6</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073633" />
	</game>
	<game id="196127">
		<path>./Games/Hello Kitty - Kruisers with Sanrio Friends.xci</path>
		<name>Hello Kitty Kruisers With Sanrio Friends</name>
		<desc>The world famous and incredibly popular Hello Kitty is back and starring in an all-new 3D racing game! Join Hello Kitty and her Sanrio friends as they race on land, through air and over water. Race by yourself or with up to three of your friends. Unlock new outfits and vehicles for Hello Kitty and her Sanrio Friends, or challenge your racing skills in the all-new Adventure Mode!</desc>
		<fanart>./images/Hello Kitty - Kruisers with Sanrio Friends-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<releasedate>20180426T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Maestro Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Rising Star Games</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073638" />
	</game>
	<game id="196215">
		<path>./Games/Hotel Transylvania 3 - Monsters Overboard.xci</path>
		<name>Hotel Transylvania 3 - Monsters Overboard</name>
		<desc>Dracula, Mavis and the gang have been marooned on the mysterious Lost Islands!Only you, with help from lovable little creatures, the Impa, can reunite them with the rest of the Drac-Pack! Lead your Impa team on daring missions to explore the Lost Islands and rescue Frankenstein, Murray and Wayne. Discover new Impa varieties – including Frankenimpa, Wolfimpa and more – and use their scary skills to battle fearsome enemies, solve puzzles and save your monster friends, in a hilarious new adventure that continues the story of Sony Pictures Animation’s Hotel Transylvania 3 movie!</desc>
		<image>./images/Hotel Transylvania 3 - Monsters Overboard-image.jpg</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Hotel Transylvania 3 - Monsters Overboard-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/Hotel Transylvania 3 - Monsters Overboard-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20180710T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Torus Games</developer>
		<publisher>Outright Games</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games / Action RPG</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073640" />
	</game>
	<game id="196189">
		<path>./Games/Hunting Simulator.xci</path>
		<name>Hunting Simulator</name>
		<desc>A real hunting simulation, Hunting Simulator offers you many hours of immersion in the wilderness thanks to different single and multiplayer game modes, numerous hunting areas and hundreds of hunting plans to achieve.
The game features environments recreated from the most famous hunting regions, including the mountains of Colorado, the forests of French oaks or the snowy plains of Alaska. Each area is populated by many animals faithfully modeled and animated by realistic artificial intelligence.</desc>
		<image>./images/Hunting Simulator-image.jpg</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Hunting Simulator-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/Hunting Simulator-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20180710T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Neopica</developer>
		<publisher>Bigben Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073643" />
	</game>
	<game id="196015">
		<path>./Games/Hyrule Warriors - Definitive Edition.xci</path>
		<name>Hyrule Warriors: Definitive Edition</name>
		<desc>Race into the thick of battle as the mightiest legends of Hyrule in Hyrule Warriors: Definitive Edition.
Slash through legions of enemies unleashing devastating blows worthy of Dynasty Warriors and dominate the battlefield as famous heroes from The Legend of Zelda series.</desc>
		<image>./images/Hyrule Warriors - Definitive Edition-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Hyrule Warriors - Definitive Edition-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Hyrule Warriors - Definitive Edition-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Hyrule Warriors - Definitive Edition-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Hyrule Warriors - Definitive Edition-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Hyrule Warriors - Definitive Edition-boxback.png</boxback>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20180518T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Koei</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<family>The Legend of Zelda</family>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073645" />
	</game>
	<game id="359947">
		<path>./Games/Hyrule Warriors Age of Calamity.xci</path>
		<name>Hyrule Warriors: Age of Calamity</name>
		<desc>Hyrule Warriors: Age of Calamity mashes together the gameplay of Hyrule Warriors and the gorgeous world of Breath of the Wild. Set 100 years before the events of Breath of the Wild, Age of Calamity details the story of Zelda and the Champions as they prepare to put a stop to impending return of Calamity Ganon.</desc>
		<image>./images/Hyrule Warriors Age of Calamity-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Hyrule Warriors Age of Calamity-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Hyrule Warriors Age of Calamity-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Hyrule Warriors Age of Calamity-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Hyrule Warriors Age of Calamity-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Hyrule Warriors Age of Calamity-boxback.png</boxback>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20201120T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Koei Tecmo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<family>The Legend of Zelda</family>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073647" />
	</game>
	<game id="359921">
		<path>./Games/Immortals Fenyx Rising.xci</path>
		<name>Immortals Fenyx Rising</name>
		<image>./images/Immortals Fenyx Rising-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Immortals Fenyx Rising-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Immortals Fenyx Rising-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Immortals Fenyx Rising-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Immortals Fenyx Rising-boxback.png</boxback>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073649" />
	</game>
	<game id="195837">
		<path>./Games/Just Dance 2017.xci</path>
		<name>Just Dance 2017</name>
		<desc>Just Dance 2017 is more fun to play than ever!Grab your friends and family and start dancing anytime, anywhere, with anyone on Nintendo Switch. Be sure to keep the party going with the included three-month trial of Just Dance Unlimited, giving you access to an online catalog with 300+ of your favorite Just Dance tracks!</desc>
		<image>./images/Just Dance 2017-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Just Dance 2017-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Just Dance 2017-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Just Dance 2017-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Just Dance 2017-boxback.png</boxback>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Music and Dance</genre>
		<family>Just Dance</family>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073652" />
	</game>
	<game id="196027">
		<path>./Games/Just Dance 2018.xci</path>
		<name>Just Dance 2018</name>
		<desc>Whether you're a party starter, a dancer in the making, or a seasoned pro, get ready to turn up the volume and unleash your inner dancer with Just Dance® 2018!Just Dance 2018 is coming back on October 24th 2018 with over 40 tracks at launch, and more than 300 songs available with Just Dance Unlimited and the 3-month trial included!From the hottest hits to family favorites, dance to 40 new tracks, including:Despacito - Luis Fonsi &amp; Daddy Yankee24K Magic - Bruno MarsJohn Wayne - Lady GagaWaka Waka - ShakiraNaughty Girl - BeyoncéRockabye - Clean Bandit Ft. Sean Paul &amp; Anne-Marie...and many more!Whether you are a young dancer in the making or a pro dancer looking for new challenges, it’s never been so easy to Just Dance.</desc>
		<image>./images/Just Dance 2018-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Just Dance 2018-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Just Dance 2018-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Just Dance 2018-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Just Dance 2018-boxback.png</boxback>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Music and Dance</genre>
		<family>Just Dance</family>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073655" />
	</game>
	<game id="197777">
		<path>./Games/Just Dance 2019.xci</path>
		<name>Just Dance 2019</name>
		<desc>Dance to your own beat with Just Dance® 2019, the ultimate dance game featuring 40 hot tracks from chart-topping hits to family favorites, including "Havana" by Camila Cabello, "Bang Bang Bang" by BIGBANG, "No Tears Left To Cry" by Ariana Grande, and many more! With a one-month trial of Just Dance Unlimited included, dance to more than 400 songs!Your Just Dance experience is now personalized as the game learns your dancing habits and suggests content!Experience eight exclusive choreographies created with the help of kids’ development experts to encourage healthy movement.Featuring seasonal and special-event content for an even more dynamic experience on a new curated homepage.</desc>
		<image>./images/Just Dance 2019-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Just Dance 2019-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Just Dance 2019-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Just Dance 2019-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Just Dance 2019-boxback.png</boxback>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Music and Dance</genre>
		<family>Just Dance</family>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073656" />
	</game>
	<game id="197935">
		<path>./Games/Katamari Damacy REROLL.xci</path>
		<name>Katamari Damacy Reroll</name>
		<desc>The stop-at-nothing pushing prince is back and ready to reroll! When the King of All Cosmos accidentally destroys all the stars in the sky, he orders you, his pint-sized princely son, to put the twinkle back in the heavens above. Join the King and Prince of Cosmos on their wacky adventure to restore the stars.</desc>
		<marquee>./images/Katamari Damacy REROLL-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Katamari Damacy REROLL-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Katamari Damacy REROLL-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<releasedate>20181207T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>MONKEYCRAFT</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073658" />
	</game>
	<game id="359863">
		<path>./Games/Kingdoms of Amalur Re-Reckoning.xci</path>
		<name>Kingdoms of Amalur - Re-Reckoning</name>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073701" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Kings Bounty II.xci</path>
		<name>Kings Bounty II</name>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073702" />
	</game>
	<game id="195955">
		<path>./Games/Kirby Star Allies.xci</path>
		<name>Kirby Star Allies</name>
		<desc>When a new evil threatens Planet Popstar, Kirby will need a little help from his...enemies?! By making friends out of foes, up to three* players can drop in or out of the adventure at any time. With new and expanded copy abilities, classic Kirby action is deeper than ever: combine abilities with elements such as ice or fire to create new friend abilities!</desc>
		<image>./images/Kirby Star Allies-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Kirby Star Allies-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Kirby Star Allies-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Kirby Star Allies-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Kirby Star Allies-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Kirby Star Allies-boxback.png</boxback>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20180316T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<family>Kirby</family>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073705" />
	</game>
	<game id="195893">
		<path>./Games/L A Noire.xci</path>
		<name>L.a. Noire</name>
		<desc>Amid the post-war boom of Hollywood's Golden Age, Cole Phelps, an LAPD detective is thrown headfirst into a city drowning in its own success. Corruption is rampant, the drug trade is exploding, and murder rates are at an all-time high. In his fight to climb the ranks and do what's right, Phelps must unravel the truth behind a string of arson attacks, racketeering conspiracies and brutal murders, battling the L.A. underworld and even members of his own department to uncover a secret that could shake the city to its rotten core.</desc>
		<marquee>./images/L A Noire-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/L A Noire-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/L A Noire-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/L A Noire-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20171114T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rockstar Games</developer>
		<publisher>Rockstar Games</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073707" />
	</game>
	<game id="196707">
		<path>./Games/Layers of Fear Legacy.xci</path>
		<name>Layers Of Fear - Legacy</name>
		<desc>The Masterpiece of FearLayers of Fear: Legacy is a psychological and psychedelic horror game about a madness-engulfed painter striving to create his Magnum Opus. Learn the dark story of his past while gathering carefully crafted personal items that can be found in the game. Traverse the vision-induced, constantly changing house full of supernatural phenomena, where each move of the camera can shift the environment, and discover the true motive of the artist.</desc>
		<thumbnail>./images/Layers of Fear Legacy-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Layers of Fear Legacy-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Layers of Fear Legacy-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20180221T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bloober Team</developer>
		<publisher>Bloober Team</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure / Survival Horror</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073715" />
	</game>
	<game id="196043">
		<path>./Games/Legend of Kay Anniversary.xci</path>
		<name>Legend Of Kay Anniversary</name>
		<desc>Legend of Kay - Anniversary is a thoroughly remastered version of the original game: high-resolution textures; new, more detailed character models; modern rendering techniques and crystal-clear surround sound give this great classic a new shine.</desc>
		<image>./images/Legend of Kay Anniversary-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Legend of Kay Anniversary-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Legend of Kay Anniversary-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Legend of Kay Anniversary-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Legend of Kay Anniversary-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Legend of Kay Anniversary-boxback.png</boxback>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20180529T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Kaiko</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073717" />
	</game>
	<game id="195809">
		<path>./Games/LEGO City Undercover.xci</path>
		<name>Lego City Undercover</name>
		<desc>Join the Chase! In Lego City Undercover, play as Chase McCain, a police officer who's been tasked with going undercover to hunt down the notorious and recently escaped criminal Rex Fury and putting an end to his city-wide crime wave.</desc>
		<image>./images/LEGO City Undercover-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/LEGO City Undercover-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/LEGO City Undercover-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/LEGO City Undercover-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/LEGO City Undercover-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20170404T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>TT Games</developer>
		<publisher>Warner Bros. Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<family>LEGO</family>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073719" />
	</game>
	<game id="197751">
		<path>./Games/LEGO DC Super-Villains.xci</path>
		<name>Lego Dc Super-villains</name>
		<desc>It's good to be bad… Embark on an all-new DC/LEGO® adventure by becoming the best villain the universe has seen. Players will create and play as an all-new super-villain throughout the game, unleashing mischievous antics and wreaking havoc in an action-packed story. Set in an open world experience within the DC universe, the Justice League has disappeared, leaving Earth's protection to their counterparts, who have proclaimed themselves as the "Justice Syndicate". It's up to you and a crazy group of misfits to uncover the intentions of Earth's new, strange, wannabe superheroes. Joined by renowned DC Super-Villains: The Joker, Harley Quinn, and countless others from the Injustice League, players will set out on an epic adventure.</desc>
		<image>./images/LEGO DC Super-Villains-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/LEGO DC Super-Villains-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/LEGO DC Super-Villains-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/LEGO DC Super-Villains-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20181016T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>TT Games</developer>
		<publisher>WB Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action / Adventure</genre>
		<family>LEGO</family>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073722" />
	</game>
	<game id="197821">
		<path>./Games/LEGO Harry Potter Collection.xci</path>
		<name>Lego Harry Potter Collection</name>
		<desc>The LEGO® Harry Potter™ Collection brings LEGO® Harry Potter™: Years 1-4 and LEGO® Harry Potter™: Years 5-7 remastered! This compilation unites the creative prowess of LEGO and the expansive world of Harry Potter, with an exciting journey full of spell-casting, potion-making, puzzle-solving, lessons, dueling and much more for players of all ages to enjoy.</desc>
		<thumbnail>./images/LEGO Harry Potter Collection-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/LEGO Harry Potter Collection-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20181030T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>TT Games</developer>
		<publisher>Warner Bros. Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<family>LEGO</family>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073727" />
	</game>
	<game id="195939">
		<path>./Games/LEGO Marvel Super Heroes 2.xci</path>
		<name>Lego Marvel Super Heroes 2</name>
		<desc>Play as the Guardians of the Galaxy, Spider-Man, Thor, Hulk, Black Panther, Captain Marvel, Doctor Strange, Green Goblin and dozens of other Marvel Super Heroes and Villains in this cosmic battle across the time-tossed city of Chronopolis!</desc>
		<image>./images/LEGO Marvel Super Heroes 2-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/LEGO Marvel Super Heroes 2-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/LEGO Marvel Super Heroes 2-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/LEGO Marvel Super Heroes 2-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/LEGO Marvel Super Heroes 2-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20171114T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>TT Games</developer>
		<publisher>Warner Bros. Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<family>LEGO</family>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073729" />
	</game>
	<game id="197581">
		<path>./Games/LEGO The Incredibles.xci</path>
		<name>Lego The Incredibles</name>
		<desc>Experience the thrilling adventures of the Parr family as they conquer crime and family life through both Disney-Pixar films The Incredibles and Incredibles 2, in a LEGO world full of fun and humor.</desc>
		<image>./images/LEGO The Incredibles-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/LEGO The Incredibles-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/LEGO The Incredibles-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/LEGO The Incredibles-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/LEGO The Incredibles-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20180615T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>TT Games</developer>
		<publisher>Warner Bros. Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<family>LEGO</family>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073732" />
	</game>
	<game id="195847">
		<path>./Games/LEGO Worlds.xci</path>
		<name>Lego Worlds</name>
		<desc>EXPLORE. DISCOVER. CREATE. TOGETHER. LEGO® Worlds is an open environment of procedurally-generated Worlds made entirely of LEGO bricks which you can freely manipulate and dynamically populate with LEGO models. Create anything you can imagine one brick at a time, or use large-scale landscaping tools to create vast mountain ranges and dot your world with tropical islands. Drop in prefabricated structures to build and customize any world to your liking. Explore using helicopters, dragons, motorbikes or even gorillas and unlock treasures that enhance your gameplay. Watch your creations come to life through characters and creatures that interact with you and each other in unexpected ways. In LEGO Worlds, anything is possible!</desc>
		<image>./images/LEGO Worlds-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/LEGO Worlds-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/LEGO Worlds-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/LEGO Worlds-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/LEGO Worlds-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20170905T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Travellers Tales</developer>
		<publisher>Warner Bros. Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<family>LEGO</family>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073734" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Lets Sing 10 ESP.xci</path>
		<name>Lets Sing 10 ESP</name>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073736" />
	</game>
	<game id="195903">
		<path>./Games/Lets Sing 2018.xci</path>
		<name>Lets Sing 2018</name>
		<image>./images/Lets Sing 2018-image.jpg</image>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073738" />
	</game>
	<game id="197291">
		<path>./Games/Little Dragons Cafe.xci</path>
		<name>Little Dragons Café</name>
		<desc>Little Dragons Café opens with a twin brother and sister learning to cook and manage a small café with their mother. All was routine until one morning when the twins discover that their mother won't wake up. Suddenly, a strange old man appears and tells them that they must raise a dragon to save her. Working with three quirky café employees, the twins must wrangle a dragon and run the family business while finding a way to save their mother.</desc>
		<image>./images/Little Dragons Cafe-image.jpg</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Little Dragons Cafe-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>20180824T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Aksys Games</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073740" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Little Friends Dogs and Cats.xci</path>
		<name>Little Friends Dogs and Cats</name>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073742" />
	</game>
	<game id="196047">
		<path>./Games/Little Nightmares Complete Edition.xci</path>
		<name>Little Nightmares: Complete Edition</name>
		<desc>Do you remember your childhood fears? Immerse yourself in Little Nightmares, a dark whimsical tale that will confront you with your childhood fears as you help Six &amp; The Kid escape The Maw, a vast mysterious vessel inhabited by corrupted souls looking for their next meal!</desc>
		<image>./images/Little Nightmares Complete Edition-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Little Nightmares Complete Edition-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Little Nightmares Complete Edition-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Little Nightmares Complete Edition-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Little Nightmares Complete Edition-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20180518T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tarsier Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073744" />
	</game>
	<game id="359463">
		<path>./Games/Luigi's Mansion 3 (Europe).xci</path>
		<name>Luigi's Mansion 3</name>
		<desc>Luigi's invited to the towering Last Resort hotel, but when Mario and friends go missing, our green-clad hero will have to conquer his fears to save them! Slam, blow away, and vacuum up ghosts with the all-new Poltergust G-00, and join forces with Gooigi to overcome the puzzling contraptions and mischievous boss on each themed floor.</desc>
		<image>./images/Luigi's Mansion 3 (Europe)-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Luigi's Mansion 3 (Europe)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Luigi's Mansion 3 (Europe)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Luigi's Mansion 3 (Europe)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Luigi's Mansion 3 (Europe)-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Luigi's Mansion 3 (Europe)-boxback.png</boxback>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20191031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Next Level Games</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1-8</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073747" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Lumo.xci</path>
		<name>Lumo</name>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073748" />
	</game>
	<game id="196735">
		<path>./Games/Mantis Burn Racing.xci</path>
		<name>Mantis Burn Racing</name>
		<desc>Mantis Burn Racing is a modern top-down style racing game that combines physics-based gameplay with intuitive arcade racing in highly competitive, fast and addictive races. Prove your skills in 5 unique classes of vehicles over an epic 11-season single-player career with more than 150 events and 13 event types in frenetic, bumper-to-bumper races where winning is everything!</desc>
		<video>./videos/Mantis Burn Racing-video.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail>./images/Mantis Burn Racing-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>20171123T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>VooFoo Studios</developer>
		<publisher>VooFoo Studios</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-8</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073750" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Mario &amp; Sonic at the Olympic Games Tokyo 2020 (Japan).xci</path>
		<name>Mario &amp; Sonic at the Olympic Games Tokyo 2020 (Japan)</name>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073752" />
	</game>
	<game id="195817">
		<path>./Games/Mario + Rabbids - Kingdom Battle (USA, Europe).xci</path>
		<name>Mario + Rabbids: Kingdom Battle</name>
		<desc>The Mushroom Kingdom has been torn apart by a mysterious vortex, transporting the chaotic Rabbids into this once-peaceful land. To restore order, Mario, Luigi, Princess Peach, and Yoshi must team up with a whole new crew: four Rabbids heroes! Together, they will battle with weapons through four worlds filled with combat, puzzles, and unpredictable enemies.</desc>
		<image>./images/Mario + Rabbids - Kingdom Battle (USA, Europe)-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Mario + Rabbids - Kingdom Battle (USA, Europe)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Mario + Rabbids - Kingdom Battle (USA, Europe)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Mario + Rabbids - Kingdom Battle (USA, Europe)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Mario + Rabbids - Kingdom Battle (USA, Europe)-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Mario + Rabbids - Kingdom Battle (USA, Europe)-boxback.png</boxback>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20170829T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073754" />
	</game>
	<game id="195801">
		<path>./Games/Mario Kart 8 Deluxe.xci</path>
		<name>Mario Kart 8 Deluxe</name>
		<desc>Race and battle your friends in the definitive version of Mario Kart 8.Switch_MK8-Deluxe_description-charHit the road with the definitive version of Mario Kart 8 and play anytime, anywhere! Race your friends or battle them in a revised battle mode on new and returning battle courses. Play locally in up to 4-player multiplayer in 1080p while playing in TV Mode. Every track from the Wii U version, including DLC, makes a glorious return. Plus, the Inklings appear as all-new guest characters, along with returning favorites, such as King Boo, Dry Bones, and Bowser Jr.!Features:Race your friends in the definitive version of Mario Kart 8, only on Nintendo Switch!Race as every character on every track from the Wii U version, including DLC characters and tracks.Pop some balloons in the revamped Battle mode, complete with Balloon Battle and Bob-omb Blast.Battle on new courses, like Urchin Underpass and Battle Stadium, or returning ones, such as GCN Luigi's Mansion and SNES Battle Course 1.Inkling Girl &amp; Inkling Boy from Splatoon, King Boo, Dry Bones, and Bowser Jr. join the roster!Players can choose a new Smart Steering feature which makes driving and staying on the track easy for novice players and kids even at 200ccThree new vehicles have been added, two are even inspired by SplatoonCarry two items at the same timeReturning items include Boo, the item stealing ghost, and the Feather, which gives you a high jump in battle mode.Play your friends in local wireless multiplayer with up to 8 players.Drive through in 1080p HD quality in TV modePlay on the go with handheld mode and play anytime, anywhere</desc>
		<image>./images/Mario Kart 8 Deluxe-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Mario Kart 8 Deluxe-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Mario Kart 8 Deluxe-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Mario Kart 8 Deluxe-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Mario Kart 8 Deluxe-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Mario Kart 8 Deluxe-boxback.png</boxback>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20170428T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<family>Mario Kart</family>
		<players>1-12</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073756" />
	</game>
	<game id="196103">
		<path>./Games/Mario Tennis Aces (World) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It,Nl,Ru).xci</path>
		<name>Mario Tennis Aces</name>
		<desc>Unleash an arsenal of shots and strategies in all-out tennis battles with friends, family, and fan-favorite Mushroom Kingdom characters. Whether you play locally, online, or using simple motion controls, intense rallies await! In Adventure mode, experience a new favor of tennis gameplay, with a variety of missions, boss battles and more.</desc>
		<image>./images/Mario Tennis Aces (World) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It,Nl,Ru)-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Mario Tennis Aces (World) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It,Nl,Ru)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Mario Tennis Aces (World) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It,Nl,Ru)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Mario Tennis Aces (World) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It,Nl,Ru)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Mario Tennis Aces (World) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It,Nl,Ru)-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Mario Tennis Aces (World) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It,Nl,Ru)-boxback.png</boxback>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20180622T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Camelot Software</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>de,en,nl,jp,es,fr,ru,it</lang>
		<region>ru</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073758" />
	</game>
	<game id="198375">
		<path>./Games/Marvel Ultimate Alliance 3 - The Black Order (World).xci</path>
		<name>Marvel Ultimate Alliance 3 The Black Order</name>
		<desc>In this new storyline, heroes and villains unite in a race across the Marvel Universe to find the Infinity Stones before Thanos and The Black Order use them to unleash cosmic chaos. From Avengers Tower to the X-Mansion and beyond, every stop on the dangerous quest to thwart Thanos results in unexpected collisions of fan-favorite characters and iconic locations.</desc>
		<image>./images/Marvel Ultimate Alliance 3 - The Black Order (World)-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Marvel Ultimate Alliance 3 - The Black Order (World)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Marvel Ultimate Alliance 3 - The Black Order (World)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Marvel Ultimate Alliance 3 - The Black Order (World)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Marvel Ultimate Alliance 3 - The Black Order (World)-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Marvel Ultimate Alliance 3 - The Black Order (World)-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20190719T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Koei</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>wr</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073801" />
	</game>
	<game id="196035">
		<path>./Games/Max - The Curse of Brotherhood.xci</path>
		<name>Max - The Curse of Brotherhood</name>
		<desc>A warm Summer day, Max comes home from school and finds his room in a mess. His little brother Felix is playing with his toys again! In anger, Max turns to his laptop and makes a search: “How to make your brother disappear”.

Max: The Curse of Brotherhood is a cinematic adventure filled with action-packed platforming and creative puzzle-solving. Armed with only a Magic Marker, Max must confront evil at every turn in a hostile and fantastical world in order to save his kid brother, Felix. Fortunately, the Magic Marker has the power to bend the elements and create magic objects that can help Max on his quest. Join Max on the greatest adventure of his life!</desc>
		<thumbnail>./images/Max - The Curse of Brotherhood-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/Max - The Curse of Brotherhood-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20171221T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Stage Clear Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Flashbulb</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073806" />
	</game>
	<game id="196237">
		<path>./Games/Mega Man X Legacy Collection.xci</path>
		<name>Mega Man X : Legacy Collection</name>
		<desc>The ultimate Mega Man X experience!The celebrated Mega Man X series returns! Play as Mega Man X – the powerful successor of classic fighting robot Mega Man – as he battles a variety of deadly bosses known as Mavericks in four hit titles. Mega Man X Legacy Collection includes the legendary 16-bit titles and the series' exciting foray into the 32-bit era: Mega Man X, Mega Man X2, Mega Man X3, and Mega Man X4. The heroic robot grows stronger as he takes down Mavericks and steals their weapons, and can dash and wall jump making for a thrilling, fast-paced combat experience.Mega Man X Legacy Collection comes with an armory of new features. Test your skills in the new X Challenge mode, which pits players against two deadly bosses in two-on-one battles. Explore a huge museum filled with rare production art, catalogs of classic merchandise, a playlist of nostalgic commercials, and more.</desc>
		<image>./images/Mega Man X Legacy Collection-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Mega Man X Legacy Collection-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Mega Man X Legacy Collection-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Mega Man X Legacy Collection-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Mega Man X Legacy Collection-boxback.png</boxback>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20180624T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<family>Mega Man</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073809" />
	</game>
	<game id="359779">
		<path>./Games/Memories Off Innocent Fille for Dearest.xci</path>
		<name>Memories Off - Innocent Fille for Dearest</name>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073811" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Minecraft Story Mode Season 1 + Season 2.xci</path>
		<name>Minecraft Story Mode Season 1 + Season 2</name>
		<marquee>./images/Minecraft Story Mode Season 1 + Season 2-marquee.png</marquee>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073813" />
	</game>
	<game id="196007">
		<path>./Games/Monopoly for Nintendo Switch.xci</path>
		<name>Monopoly for Nintendo Switch</name>
		<desc>America's favorite family board game, MONOPOLY®, makes its debut on Nintendo Switch™ system with new ways to play!Experience three unique 3D boards at home or on-the-go with up to six players in total, or take your game online and challenge players in quick matches. Customize your game by selecting from six official House Rules chosen by MONOPOLY® fans around the world. Don't have time for a full game? Speed it up with Special Goals that shorten play sessions, and Actions Cards to move you around the board and penalize your opponents. Build your empire and trade your way to victory!</desc>
		<image>./images/Monopoly for Nintendo Switch-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Monopoly for Nintendo Switch-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Monopoly for Nintendo Switch-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Monopoly for Nintendo Switch-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Monopoly for Nintendo Switch-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20171031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Engine Software</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Board game</genre>
		<players>1-6</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073815" />
	</game>
	<game id="197931">
		<path>./Games/Monster Boy and the Cursed Kingdom.xci</path>
		<name>Monster Boy And The Cursed Kingdom</name>
		<desc>Monster Boy and the Cursed Kingdom borrows the best from the classic series to deliver a fresh, modern adventure with fun gameplay, memorable music and gorgeous hand drawn animations.

Can Jin save Monster World Kingdom? Help our young hero defeat challenging enemies, discover hidden locations, upgrade powerful equipment, and more! You'll also unlock special forms with unique skills used to open new paths where mighty bosses and secret treasures await.</desc>
		<image>./images/Monster Boy and the Cursed Kingdom-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Monster Boy and the Cursed Kingdom-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Monster Boy and the Cursed Kingdom-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Monster Boy and the Cursed Kingdom-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Monster Boy and the Cursed Kingdom-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20181204T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Atelier</developer>
		<publisher>FDG Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073818" />
	</game>
	<game id="198041">
		<path>./Games/Monster Energy Supercross The Official Videogame 2.xci</path>
		<name>Monster Energy Supercross - The Official Videogame 2</name>
		<desc>The official Monster Energy AMA Supercross Championship game is back!Live like a champion with the updated career mode and set weekly activities in your agenda: new challenges, sponsors and incredible prizes all await you!Train in the Compound. Ride freely or put your custom rider's skills to the test, competing against rivals on four different tracks. Learn to control your bike when leaning, starting, braking, cornering and scrubbing.Compete against more than 80 official 2018 championship 250SX and 450SX riders, including Jason Anderson, Marvin Musquin and the superstar, Eli Tomac!Customize your bike and rider with more than 3000 objects and show everyone what you're made of!Create new tracks and share your creations thanks to an upgraded track editor. New features and simplified accessibility will help you design and share your custom tracks online!</desc>
		<thumbnail>./images/Monster Energy Supercross The Official Videogame 2-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/Monster Energy Supercross The Official Videogame 2-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20190208T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Milestone</developer>
		<publisher>Milestone</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>8</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073824" />
	</game>
	<game id="196019">
		<path>./Games/Monster Energy Supercross The Official Videogame.xci</path>
		<name>Monster Energy Supercross - The Official Videogame</name>
		<desc>Live the adrenaline of the 2017 Monster Energy Supercross Championship with the official videogame!
Race on the official tracks with the official riders from 250SX and 450SX or create your custom rider and bike and conquer the top of the leaderboard.</desc>
		<releasedate>20180213T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Milestone</developer>
		<publisher>Milestone</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073826" />
	</game>
	<game id="197289">
		<path>./Games/Monster Hunter Generations Ultimate.xci</path>
		<name>Monster Hunter Generations Ultimate</name>
		<desc>This critically acclaimed action RPG series makes its debut on Nintendo Switch. Take on epic hunts on the go or from the comfort of your own home! Choose from 14 different weapon types, mix and match them with unique Hunting Styles and Hunter Arts, or even play as an adorable but ferocious Felyne in Prowler Mode! Featuring the largest cast of monsters for any game in the series, from returning fan favourites to mysterious never-before-seen monsters!You can join up to three other players for co-op multiplayer action, either online or in person using local wireless. Join the hunt in Monster Hunter Generations Ultimate for Nintendo Switch!</desc>
		<image>./images/Monster Hunter Generations Ultimate-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Monster Hunter Generations Ultimate-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Monster Hunter Generations Ultimate-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Monster Hunter Generations Ultimate-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Monster Hunter Generations Ultimate-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Monster Hunter Generations Ultimate-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20180828T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<family>Monster Hunter</family>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073829" />
	</game>
	<game id="198199">
		<path>./Games/Mortal Kombat 11.xci</path>
		<name>Mortal Kombat 11</name>
		<desc>Mortal Kombat 11 is the latest installment in the critically acclaimed franchise, providing a deeper and more personalized experience than ever before. The all new Custom Character Variations give you unprecedented control of your fighters to make them your own. Featuring a roster of new and returning Klassic Fighters, Mortal Kombat's best-in-class cinematic story mode continues the epic saga over 25 years in the making. Players take on the role of a variety of past and present characters in a time-bending new narrative that pits Raiden against Kronika, the Keeper of Time. Packed to the brim with multiple modes, including the Towers of Time, allowing players to test their skills through various challenges, providing more ways than ever to continue the Mortal Kombat 11 experience.</desc>
		<image>./images/Mortal Kombat 11-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Mortal Kombat 11-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Mortal Kombat 11-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Mortal Kombat 11-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Mortal Kombat 11-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Mortal Kombat 11-boxback.png</boxback>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20190422T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>NetherRealm Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Warner Bros. Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<family>Mortal Kombat</family>
		<players>1-8</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073831" />
	</game>
	<game id="197795">
		<path>./Games/Moto Racer 4.xci</path>
		<name>Moto Racer 4</name>
		<desc>Moto Racer 4 is racing game you can play on asphalt or dirt.In a world where freestyle and risk-taking dominate, impose your riding style all around the world. Impress your opponents and win races with class!Master drifting, wheelies, sharp turns and other techniques to earn a place on the podium!Customize and upgrade your bike! Progress through Moto Racer 4 and take in the stunning environments.From the United States to the Himalayas by way of the desert, Moto Racer 4 takes you through perilous, breathtaking courses at 100 miles an hour.</desc>
		<marquee>./images/Moto Racer 4-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Moto Racer 4-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Moto Racer 4-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Moto Racer 4-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20181120T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Microïds</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving / Motorcycle</genre>
		<family>Moto Racer</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073833" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/MotoGP 18 EUR.xci</path>
		<name>MotoGP 18 EUR</name>
		<image>./images/MotoGP 18 EUR-image.jpg</image>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073835" />
	</game>
	<game id="197825">
		<path>./Games/Mutant Football League Dynasty Edition.xci</path>
		<name>Mutant Football League Dynasty Edition</name>
		<thumbnail>./images/Mutant Football League Dynasty Edition-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/Mutant Football League Dynasty Edition-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20181030T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Digital Dreams</developer>
		<publisher>Digital Dreams</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Football</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073841" />
	</game>
	<game id="195981">
		<path>./Games/MXGP3 - The Official Motocross Videogame.xci</path>
		<name>Mxgp3 - The Official Motocross Videogame</name>
		<desc>Experience all the adrenaline of Motocross with the official Championship's only videogame! MXGP3 - The Official Motocross Videogame offers the most involving game experience ever, with completely new gameplay. Race on 18 official tracks and in the MXoN with all riders and bikes from the 2016 MXGP and MX2 seasons and be the first to experience the thrill of riding one of the 10 2-strokes available! Render your rider and your bike unique, with more than 300 official components for a complete customisation!</desc>
		<releasedate>20171121T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Milestone</developer>
		<publisher>Milestone</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073843" />
	</game>
	<game id="198083">
		<path>./Games/My Girlfriend is a Mermaid.xci</path>
		<name>My Girlfriend Is A Mermaid!?</name>
		<releasedate>20190228T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Cosen</developer>
		<publisher>Sekai Games</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073845" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/My Hero Ones Justice MULTi8.xci</path>
		<name>My Hero Ones Justice MULTi8</name>
		<image>./images/My Hero Ones Justice MULTi8-image.jpg</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/My Hero Ones Justice MULTi8-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/My Hero Ones Justice MULTi8-boxback.png</boxback>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073847" />
	</game>
	<game id="197975">
		<path>./Games/My Little Riding Champion.xci</path>
		<name>My Little Riding Champion</name>
		<desc>Your horse. Your passion.

Get ready to fulfil your dreams at a gallop. The village's riding club needs you to win the next major competitions. Choose your favourite horse, train it and win medals for your club!
Create a bond by going out riding in the countryside and taking care of it. Together you will set out on a large number of missions and earn new outfits and equipment for both of you.</desc>
		<thumbnail>./images/My Little Riding Champion-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/My Little Riding Champion-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20190305T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Maximum Games</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073853" />
	</game>
	<game id="197483">
		<path>./Games/My Riding Stables Life With Horses.xci</path>
		<name>My Riding Stables - Life With Horses</name>
		<desc>Make your dreams come true on the stud farm near the old mill: renovate your own riding school, look after your horses and tend the cute little foals. As well as wonderful hacks, working in the stables and caring for the horses, you'll have plenty of other exciting things to do!</desc>
		<thumbnail>./images/My Riding Stables Life With Horses-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/My Riding Stables Life With Horses-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20181113T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Independent Arts</developer>
		<publisher>Kalypso Media</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073859" />
	</game>
	<game id="197721">
		<path>./Games/Namco Museum Arcade Pac.xci</path>
		<name>Namco Museum Arcade Pac</name>
		<desc>Save your quarters and bring the arcade home with the ultimate 2-in-1 game ‘pac’, NAMCO MUSEUM™ ARCADE PAC™! Enjoy the nostalgic classics in “Namco Museum” and the flashy maze madness of “PAC-MAN Championship Edition 2 PLUS” with friends or solo, at home or on the go for exciting arcade fun wherever you are – exclusively for the Nintendo Switch™!NAMCO MUSEUM• Enjoy Namco classics such as PAC-MAN, GALAGA, SPLATTERHOUSE, and TOWER OF DRUAGA, or play games such as ROLLING THUNDER, SKYKID, or TANK FORCE with friends and family on the Nintendo Switch™!PAC-MAN CHAMPIONSHIP EDITION 2 PLUS• The highly acclaimed PAC-MAN CHAMPIONSHIP EDITION series has finally come to the Nintendo Switch™ in PAC-MAN CHAMPIONSHIP EDITION 2 PLUS! Featuring eye-popping high-resolution 3D graphics and funky visuals, the latest version of the classic game takes chomping and chasing through mazes to a whole new level! Play by yourself or with your friends in the all new co-op mode, “PAC-MAN CHAMPIONSHIP EDITION 2 PLUS 2P” – exclusive only to the Nintendo Switch™! When one player gets caught by a ghost, the other player can come to the rescue. Team up with your friends and family to weave through the mazes and make it to the boss battle together!</desc>
		<thumbnail>./images/Namco Museum Arcade Pac-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/Namco Museum Arcade Pac-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20180928T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bandai Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai Namco</publisher>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073906" />
	</game>
	<game id="196091">
		<path>./Games/Naruto Shippuden Ultimate Ninja Storm Trilogy.xci</path>
		<name>Naruto Shippuden - Ultimate Ninja Storm Trilogy</name>
		<releasedate>20180426T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bandai Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<family>Naruto</family>
		<players>1-8</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073908" />
	</game>
	<game id="197851">
		<path>./Games/NBA 2K Playgrounds 2.xci</path>
		<name>Nba 2k Playgrounds 2</name>
		<desc>NBA arcade action is back with NBA 2K Playgrounds 2! The sequel to the original smash hit takes street balling to the next level with a massive roster of current and retired NBA players, improved online matchmaking with dedicated servers, four-player online matches, three-point contests, new playgrounds, custom matches, and more! Pick your team, get ready to jam, and Ball Without Limits!</desc>
		<marquee>./images/NBA 2K Playgrounds 2-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/NBA 2K Playgrounds 2-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/NBA 2K Playgrounds 2-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20181016T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Saber Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>2K Games</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Basketball</genre>
		<family>NBA 2K</family>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073911" />
	</game>
	<game id="196009">
		<path>./Games/NBA 2K18.xci</path>
		<name>NBA 2K18</name>
		<desc>RUN THE NEIGHBORHOODThe future of sports career modes has arrived, allowing you to play the game the way you like. Build your career in NBA games, hit the courts in The Playground, join the Pro-Am circuit, or explore an all-new open neighborhood setting.Road to 99A unified badge system across Pro-Am, Park, and MyCAREER, with attributes, animations, and badges all defining your play style on your road to a 99 rating.MyTEAMCollect cards featuring NBA legends from yesterday and today, and compete in a variety of modes.Motion SystemThe new motion system dynamically creates animations to deliver the best gameplay experience possible.Special Guest CommentaryKobe Bryant and Kevin Garnett join the booth on a rotating basis to lend their expertise to the broadcast.All-Time TeamsThe greatest players in NBA history from all 30 teams, together on All-Time franchise rosters for the very first time.Classic TeamsPlay with 62 of the NBA's greatest teams from the past, including 17 new additions.</desc>
		<image>./images/NBA 2K18-image.jpg</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/NBA 2K18-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/NBA 2K18-boxback.png</boxback>
		<developer>Visual Concepts</developer>
		<publisher>Take 2 Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Basketball</genre>
		<family>NBA 2K</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073914" />
	</game>
	<game id="197397">
		<path>./Games/NBA 2K19.xci</path>
		<name>Nba 2k19</name>
		<desc>NBA 2K celebrates 20 years of redefining what sports gaming can be, from best in class graphics &amp; gameplay to groundbreaking game modes and an immersive open-world “Neighborhood.” NBA 2K19 continues to push limits as it brings gaming one step closer to real-life basketball excitement and culture.</desc>
		<image>./images/NBA 2K19-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/NBA 2K19-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/NBA 2K19-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/NBA 2K19-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/NBA 2K19-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20180911T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Visual Concepts</developer>
		<publisher>2K Games</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Basketball</genre>
		<family>NBA 2K</family>
		<players>1-10</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073917" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Nelke and the Legendary Alchemists Ateliers of the New World.xci</path>
		<name>Nelke and the Legendary Alchemists Ateliers of the New World</name>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073918" />
	</game>
	<game id="359703">
		<path>./Games/NEO The World Ends with You.xci</path>
		<name>NEO - The World Ends with You</name>
		<thumbnail>./images/NEO The World Ends with You-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/NEO The World Ends with You-boxback.png</boxback>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073924" />
	</game>
	<game id="197985">
		<path>./Games/New Super Mario Bros. U Deluxe.xci</path>
		<name>New Super Mario Bros. U Deluxe</name>
		<desc>Join Mario, Luigi, and pals for single-player or multiplayer fun anytime, anywhere! Take on two family-friendly, side-scrolling adventures with up to three friends as you try to save the Mushroom Kingdom. Includes the New Super Mario Bros. U and harder, faster New Super Luigi U games—both of which include Nabbit and Toadette as playable characters!</desc>
		<image>./images/New Super Mario Bros. U Deluxe-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/New Super Mario Bros. U Deluxe-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/New Super Mario Bros. U Deluxe-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/New Super Mario Bros. U Deluxe-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/New Super Mario Bros. U Deluxe-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/New Super Mario Bros. U Deluxe-boxback.png</boxback>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20190111T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073926" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Night Trap 25th Anniversary Edition USA.xci</path>
		<name>Night Trap 25th Anniversary Edition USA</name>
		<marquee>./images/Night Trap 25th Anniversary Edition USA-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Night Trap 25th Anniversary Edition USA-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073928" />
	</game>
	<game id="195887">
		<path>./Games/Nights of Azure 2 Bride of the New Moon.xci</path>
		<name>Nights of Azure 2: Bride of the New Moon</name>
		<desc>A Tale of Three Beautiful Maidens Drawn to Each Other.

When three friends, deceived and separated by the tricks of darkness, find each other again, their bond shall become the light that will clear away the shadows and guide them towards the truth...

Beautiful women, Servans, battles and growth system - all these elements return in an evolved form in the second instalment of the gothic fairy tale action RPG series "Nights of Azure".</desc>
		<image>./images/Nights of Azure 2 Bride of the New Moon-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Nights of Azure 2 Bride of the New Moon-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Nights of Azure 2 Bride of the New Moon-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Nights of Azure 2 Bride of the New Moon-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Nights of Azure 2 Bride of the New Moon-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20171024T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Koei Tecmo</developer>
		<publisher>Koei Tecmo</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073930" />
	</game>
	<game id="197969">
		<path>./Games/Nightshade Hyakka Hakuro.xci</path>
		<name>Nightshade Hyakka Hakuro</name>
		<desc>Iga and Koka have achieved their own development in a warring world. In their long history, the two Shinan forces were in hostile relationship with each other, but in Tensho 9th, Iga was destroyed by Oda Nobunaga's "Tansei Iga's Rebellion". Iga Shinobu who survived slightly was taken in by Koka. Seventeen years later, the Warring States period ended, and a long peace had come to the world. Koga's long-eared daughter of Kendo, Ueno, the protagonist (protagonist) dreamed of sneaking into the day when she got out of work, and she practiced every day. And in the first mission chosen at the end, a major incident occurs that makes the fate of the main character and the village go wrong</desc>
		<thumbnail>./images/Nightshade Hyakka Hakuro-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/Nightshade Hyakka Hakuro-boxback.png</boxback>
		<publisher>D3 Publisher</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073936" />
	</game>
	<game id="198175">
		<path>./Games/Nintendo Labo ToyCon 04 VR Kit.xci</path>
		<name>Nintendo Labo Toy-con 04 - Vr Kit</name>
		<image>./images/Nintendo Labo ToyCon 04 VR Kit-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Nintendo Labo ToyCon 04 VR Kit-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Nintendo Labo ToyCon 04 VR Kit-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/Nintendo Labo ToyCon 04 VR Kit-boxback.png</boxback>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073939" />
	</game>
	<game id="359681">
		<path>./Games/No More Heroes 3.xci</path>
		<name>No More Heroes 3</name>
		<image>./images/No More Heroes 3-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/No More Heroes 3-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/No More Heroes 3-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/No More Heroes 3-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/No More Heroes 3-boxback.png</boxback>
		<developer>Grasshopper Manufacture</developer>
		<publisher>Grasshopper Manufacture</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073941" />
	</game>
	<game id="196201">
		<path>./Games/OCTOPATH TRAVELER.xci</path>
		<name>Octopath Traveler</name>
		<desc>Choose your fate. Eight stories await.Eight travelers. Eight adventures. Eight roles to play in a new world brought to life by Square Enix. And now, you can enjoy all of them in the new demo. Step into the shoes and live the stories of each of the eight travelers and freely explore the world of Orsterra. Then, carry your choices and adventure into the main game with save data transfer.Use each character’s special abilities in and out of battle. Break through enemy defenses by discovering and targeting weaknesses. Store Boost Points with each turn and then spend them at strategic times to strengthen abilities, chain attacks, or provide aid. Choose the path you wish to walk and discover what lies beyond the horizon.Explore multiple, distinct RPG adventures in a world created by Square EnixChoose from eight characters, each with their own distinct storyDeep, strategic turn-based combat with a layered battle systemVisuals inspired by retro RPGs, brought to life with modern touches and a rousing, dynamic musical score</desc>
		<image>./images/OCTOPATH TRAVELER-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/OCTOPATH TRAVELER-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/OCTOPATH TRAVELER-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/OCTOPATH TRAVELER-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/OCTOPATH TRAVELER-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/OCTOPATH TRAVELER-boxback.png</boxback>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20180713T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073944" />
	</game>
	<game id="196287">
		<path>./Games/Okami HD.xci</path>
		<name>Ōkami HD</name>
		<desc>Take the role of Amaterasu, the Japanese sun goddess who inhabits the form of a legendary white wolf Shiranui. Use magical abilities, attacks, and Celestial Brush techniques to restore the land of Nippon to its previous glory full of life and color.</desc>
		<image>./images/Okami HD-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Okami HD-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Okami HD-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Okami HD-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Okami HD-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Okami HD-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20180809T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073946" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/One Piece - Pirate Warriors 3.xci</path>
		<name>One Piece - Pirate Warriors 3</name>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073948" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/One Piece - Unlimited World Red.xci</path>
		<name>One Piece - Unlimited World Red</name>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073950" />
	</game>
	<game id="197965">
		<path>./Games/Onimusha Warlords.xci</path>
		<name>Onimusha - Warlords</name>
		<desc>Capcom's riveting samurai adventure returns!This version includes the original game’s intense swordplay and dramatic revenge story, plus improved controls, widescreen display, a new soundtrack, and more. Experience this enhanced version of the best-selling action-adventure classic!</desc>
		<thumbnail>./images/Onimusha Warlords-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/Onimusha Warlords-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20190115T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073956" />
	</game>
	<game id="359482">
		<path>./Games/Ori and the Blind Forest Definitive Edition.nsp</path>
		<name>Ori and the Blind Forest: Definitive Edition</name>
		<desc>The forest of Nibel is dying. After a powerful storm sets a series of devastating events in motion, Ori must journey to find courage and confront a dark nemesis to save the forest of Nibel. “Ori and the Blind Forest” tells the tale of a young orphan destined for heroics, through a visually stunning Action-Platformer crafted by Moon Studios. Featuring hand-painted artwork, meticulously animated character performance, a fully orchestrated score and dozens of new features in the Definitive Edition, “Ori and the Blind Forest” explores a deeply emotional story about love and sacrifice, and the hope that exists in us all.</desc>
		<image>./images/Ori and the Blind Forest Definitive Edition-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Ori and the Blind Forest Definitive Edition-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Ori and the Blind Forest Definitive Edition-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Ori and the Blind Forest Definitive Edition-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Ori and the Blind Forest Definitive Edition-boxback.png</boxback>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20190927T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Moon Studio</developer>
		<publisher>Microsoft Studios</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073958" />
	</game>
	<game id="359480">
		<path>./Games/Ori and the Will of the Wisps.xci</path>
		<name>Ori and the Will of the Wisps</name>
		<desc>Play the critically acclaimed masterpieceFrom the creators of Ori and the Blind Forest comes the highly-anticipated sequel, Ori and the Will of the Wisps. Embark on an all-new adventure in a vast and exotic world where you’ll encounter towering enemies and challenging puzzles on your quest to discover Ori’s true destiny.Immerse yourself in a hand-crafted narrative experience with deeply emotional storytelling, strikingly beautiful environments, and a stunning soundtrack.Master new skills to guide Ori through a journey of untold danger using newly acquired spirit weapons, spells, and attacks. Utilize an all-new shard system to power-up Ori’s newfound abilities.Face larger-than-life bosses and seek help from an expansive cast of new characters who will help you uncover Ori’s mysterious fate.Race to the top of the leaderboards in the all-new Spirit Trials mode where players dash, burrow, grapple, and leap to high scores in unique speed-run challenges throughout the game.</desc>
		<image>./images/Ori and the Will of the Wisps-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Ori and the Will of the Wisps-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Ori and the Will of the Wisps-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Ori and the Will of the Wisps-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Ori and the Will of the Wisps-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Ori and the Will of the Wisps-boxback.png</boxback>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20200917T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Moon Studio</developer>
		<publisher>iam8bit</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<family>Ori</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074000" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Ostwind Das Spiel EUR.xci</path>
		<name>Ostwind Das Spiel EUR</name>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074002" />
	</game>
	<game id="196823">
		<path>./Games/Outlast 2.xci</path>
		<name>Outlast 2</name>
		<desc>Outlast 2 is the sequel to the acclaimed survival horror game Outlast. Set in the same universe as the first game, but with different characters and a different setting, Outlast 2 is a twisted new journey into the depths of the human mind and its dark secrets.

Outlast 2 introduces you to Sullivan Knoth and his followers, who left our wicked world behind to give birth to Temple Gate, a town, deep in the wilderness and hidden from civilization. Knoth and his flock are preparing for the tribulations of the end of times and you're right in the thick of it.</desc>
		<thumbnail>./images/Outlast 2-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/Outlast 2-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20180327T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Red Barrels</developer>
		<publisher>Red Barrels</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074008" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Outlast.xci</path>
		<name>Outlast</name>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074010" />
	</game>
	<game id="196023">
		<path>./Games/Overcooked - Special Edition.xci</path>
		<name>Overcooked! Special Edition</name>
		<desc>Working as a team, you and your fellow chefs must prepare, cook and serve up a variety of tasty orders before the baying customers storm out in a huff. Sharpen your knives and dust off your chef's whites, there isn't mushroom for error and the steaks are high in these crazy kitchens!</desc>
		<marquee>./images/Overcooked - Special Edition-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Overcooked - Special Edition-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Overcooked - Special Edition-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Overcooked - Special Edition-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20170727T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ghost Town Games</developer>
		<publisher>Team17</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074012" />
	</game>
	<game id="196273">
		<path>./Games/Overcooked! 2.xci</path>
		<name>Overcooked! 2</name>
		<desc>Overcooked returns with a whole new slice of chaotic culinary action!
Return to the Onion Kingdom and assemble your team of chefs in this local or online co-op game for up to 4 players. Grab your aprons... it's time to save the world again.

From the stove to the fire...

You've saved the world from the Insatiable. Now a new threat has surfaced and it's time to get back in the kitchen to fend off the zombie attack!

- Get your hands dirty to get the highest score in a chaotic multiplayer mode.

- Discover new kitchens: sushi restaurants, magic schools and mines!

- Use teleporters and mobile platforms, and save time by sending your ingredients to dynamic kitchens.

 - Prepare new recipes including sushi, cakes, burgers and pizzas.</desc>
		<image>./images/Overcooked! 2-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Overcooked! 2-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Overcooked! 2-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Overcooked! 2-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Overcooked! 2-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20180807T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ghost Town Games</developer>
		<publisher>Team17</publisher>
		<genre>Casual Game</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074014" />
	</game>
	<game id="359665">
		<path>./Games/Paper Mario The Origami King.xci</path>
		<name>Paper Mario: The Origami King</name>
		<desc>A new paper-crafted Mario adventure unfolds on Nintendo Switch!The kingdom has been ravaged by an origami menace! Join Mario and his new partner, Olivia, as they battle evil Folded Soldiers, repair the damaged landscape, and try to free Princess Peach’s castle from the clutches of King Olly in this comedy-filled adventure.</desc>
		<image>./images/Paper Mario The Origami King-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Paper Mario The Origami King-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Paper Mario The Origami King-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Paper Mario The Origami King-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Paper Mario The Origami King-boxback.png</boxback>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20200717T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action / Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074017" />
	</game>
	<game id="196021">
		<path>./Games/Payday 2.xci</path>
		<name>Payday 2</name>
		<desc>PAYDAY 2 is an action-packed, four-player co-op shooter that once again lets gamers don the masks of the original PAYDAY crew - Dallas, Hoxton, Wolf and Chains - as they descend on Washington DC for an epic crime spree.Up to four friends co-operate on each heist, and as the crew progresses the heists gets bigger, better and more rewarding. Along with earning more money and becoming an infamous criminal comes new customization that lets players build and alter their guns and gear.PAYDAY 2 comes with full touch screen menu support, and a newly developed rumble feature that responds as you, for example, fire weapons or throw grenades. There’s also an added local multiplayer mode to the CRIME.NET - called CRIME.NET Local Play, that will make you able to set up a local game and invite friends that share the same local network. Finally, PAYDAY 2 comes with an exclusive character called Joy who’s initially releasing only on Nintendo Switch™ - complete with her own mask and weapons.Rob Banks, Get Paid – Players must choose their crew carefully, because when the job goes down they will need the right mix of skills on their side.CRIME.NET – The dynamic contract database CRIME.NET lets players pick and choose from available jobs by connecting with local Contractors - all with their own agenda and best interests in mind.Dynamic Scenarios – No heist ever plays out the same way twice, as heists comes with random geometry and events.Choose Your Skills – As players progress they can invest in any of five special Skill Trees: Mastermind, Enforcer, Ghost, Technician and Fugitive. Each features a deep customization tree of associated skills and equipment to master.More Masks than Ever – PAYDAY 2 features a completely new mask system, giving players the ability to craft their own unique mask together with a pattern and a color.Weapons and Modifications – A huge arsenal for the serious heister, covering everything from sniper to assault rifles. You can modify your weapon with optics, suppressors, fore grips, reticles, barrels, frames, stocks and lots more.Play It Your Way – Each job allows for multiple approaches, such as slow and stealthy ambushes, to running in guns blazing.</desc>
		<image>./images/Payday 2-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Payday 2-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Payday 2-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Payday 2-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Payday 2-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20180227T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Starbreeze Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Starbreeze Publishing AB</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074020" />
	</game>
	<game id="196301">
		<path>./Games/Penguin Wars.xci</path>
		<name>Penguin Wars</name>
		<desc>Penguin Wars is a remake of the classic released in 1985. The original rule of using 10 balls to throw at each other is still the core of the game. However, now you can evolve your characters in Story Mode and use those super up characters in both local and online gameplay against your friends. This release also introduces multiple sets of new rules, which new and seasoned gamer can both enjoy. Music from the original version released in 1985 has been remixed and updated by notable musicians from Japan, which will make you want to listen to the music while you’re out for a run or dance to on a Friday night with the family.</desc>
		<thumbnail>./images/Penguin Wars-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/Penguin Wars-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20190627T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>City Connection</developer>
		<publisher>Dispatch Games</publisher>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074026" />
	</game>
	<game id="195959">
		<path>./Games/Penny Punching Princess.xci</path>
		<name>Penny-Punching Princess</name>
		<desc>Penny-Punching Princess is an isometric brawler that takes place in a world ruled by capitalism, where cash is king. Fight or bribe your way to reclaiming your kingdom from the greedy Dragoloans.</desc>
		<image>./images/Penny Punching Princess-image.jpg</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Penny Punching Princess-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/Penny Punching Princess-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20180403T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nippon Ichi Software</developer>
		<publisher>NIS America</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074030" />
	</game>
	<game id="196855">
		<path>./Games/Pic A Pix Deluxe.xci</path>
		<name>Pic-a-pix Deluxe</name>
		<desc>Pic-a-Pix are exciting logic puzzles that form whimsical pixel-art pictures when solved. Pic-a-Pix are sometimes known by other names, such as Picross, Nonogram, Paint by Numbers, Griddlers, Hanjie and many more.</desc>
		<releasedate>20180104T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Lightwood Games</developer>
		<publisher>Lightwood Games</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<md5>856dc9db475fd4a8b189642232d701f0</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074033" />
	</game>
	<game id="198207">
		<path>./Games/Piczle Puzzle Pack 3 in 1.xci</path>
		<name>Piczle Puzzle Pack 3-in-1</name>
		<desc>Piczle Puzzle Pack 3-in-1 is a collection of the following games.Piczle Lines DXDraw lines to connect pairs of numbers to complete a hidden picture in this feverishly addictive PICture puzZLE game!Connect numbers of the same color, using the same number of blocks as the number! Easy controls let you draw line after line as you gradually reveal the picture! Once you start you'll be hooked!Play through 100 levels in Story Mode as you follow the adventure of a professor and his mysterious Piczle-Matic camera. Each puzzle solved unlocks the next step in the story!Continue the fun in Puzzle Mode with 200+ more puzzles!Solve picture puzzles in of all sorts, including sports, pets, vehicles, food and many more! Select them in any order or have multiple puzzles on the go, resuming anyone at any time.Piczle Lines DX 500 More Puzzles!Couldn't get enough of Piczle Lines DX? This is for you!Another Piczle Lines game with 500 new and sometimes feisty puzzles to wrap your mind around.25 new puzzle packs with 20 puzzles each, containing famous places and people, works of genius and very challenging 1 color puzzles!Draw lines to connect pairs of numbers to complete a hidden picture in this feverishly addictive PICture puzZLE game!Connect numbers of the same color, using the same number of blocks as the number! Easy controls let you draw line after line as you gradually reveal the picture! Once you start you'll be hooked!Piczle ColorsUse the numbers around the side of the puzzle to work out how many blocks of which color should be painted in each row and column. Since the order of the numbers doesn't determine the order you need to paint the colors you'll need to stretch your brain to figure it out. Luckily there are two types of numbers that indicate if the colors should be painted together or separately.Smaller puzzles ease you into this new way of thinking and you’ll soon be hooked, working your way through 6 color packs with 50 puzzles in each, ranging in size from 5x5 to 15x10.Clear puzzles without using hints to earn coins and unlock lots of cool extra features, such as trophies, a 3D model viewer and lots more.Professor Matrix, Score-Chan, and D-Bug all return in a new story where their usual mischief this time see’s the world drain of its color. Find out what happens as you strive to return color to the world!</desc>
		<thumbnail>./images/Piczle Puzzle Pack 3 in 1-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/Piczle Puzzle Pack 3 in 1-boxback.png</boxback>
		<publisher>Rainy Frog</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074040" />
	</game>
	<game id="196867">
		<path>./Games/PixelJunk Monsters 2.xci</path>
		<name>Pixeljunk Monsters 2</name>
		<desc>In the acclaimed tower defense series' first ever official sequel, play as Tikiman and build towers to defend your Tiki Hut from the monster hordes. The sequel brings with it FOUR PLAYER online co-op, new and sometimes quite explosive fruit bombs and on top of that the game has been fully re-imagined in beautifully detailed 3D. Get ready to defend your Chibis again in this fun and addictive game for all the family.</desc>
		<releasedate>20180525T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Q-Games</developer>
		<publisher>Spike Chunsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<family>PixelJunk</family>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074042" />
	</game>
	<game id="197875">
		<path>./Games/Pokemon Lets Go Eevee.xci</path>
		<name>Pokémon - Lets Go, Eevee!</name>
		<desc>Partner up with Eevee to catch and collect Pokémon on a rich and vibrant adventure. Become the best Pokémon Trainer you can be as you battle other Trainers, Gym Leaders, and the sinister Team Rocket. Explore the vibrant region of Kanto—home to beloved characters like Brock, Misty, and the nefarious trio Jessie, James, and Meowth! Throughout the story, your bond with your partner Pokémon grows stronger as you care for it and travel together. See the world in style by customizing Eevee and your Trainer with a selection of outfits. True-to-size wild Pokémon roam around in the game—catch them like a real Pokémon Trainer by using timing and a well-placed Poké Ball™.</desc>
		<image>./images/Pokemon Lets Go Eevee-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Pokemon Lets Go Eevee-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Pokemon Lets Go Eevee-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Pokemon Lets Go Eevee-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Pokemon Lets Go Eevee-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Pokemon Lets Go Eevee-boxback.png</boxback>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20181116T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<family>Pokémon</family>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074044" />
	</game>
	<game id="197861">
		<path>./Games/Pokemon Lets Go Pikachu.xci</path>
		<name>Pokémon:Let's Go, Pikachu!</name>
		<desc>Pokémon: Let's Go, Pikachu! bring the experience of a classic Pokémon RPG to Nintendo Switch with gameplay that is easily approachable for newcomers to the series, but is also deep enough to keep veteran Trainers on their toes.

The games also have two-player simultaneous play, so you can take the journey with a friend! And there's a deep connection between Pokémon: Let's Go, Pikachu! and Pokémon GO, so fans of the hit mobile game will find even more to enjoy.</desc>
		<image>./images/Pokemon Lets Go Pikachu-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Pokemon Lets Go Pikachu-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Pokemon Lets Go Pikachu-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Pokemon Lets Go Pikachu-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Pokemon Lets Go Pikachu-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Pokemon Lets Go Pikachu-boxback.png</boxback>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20181116T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<family>Pokémon</family>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074046" />
	</game>
	<game id="359653">
		<path>./Games/Pokemon Mystery Dungeon - Rescue Team DX (Europe).xci</path>
		<name>Pokémon Mystery Dungeon: Rescue Team DX</name>
		<desc>What if you woke up one day, and you were a Pokémon? You can meet and recruit Pokémon in a dungeon-crawling adventure within their world! Build a rescue team to take on mysterious, changing dungeons and strategically plan your moves as you venture forth to make the Pokémon world a safer place…and uncover your true purpose along the way.As you recruit Pokémon, these trusty teammates will need somewhere to stay, so build rescue team camps to house, manage, and strengthen your Pokémon friends. Think hard about who is right for the job and how to approach each mysterious dungeon as you prepare a rescue team. You’ll move a single square at a time or use Auto mode to speed up movement until you engage other Pokémon in turn-based battles—but don’t forget about Pokémon strengths, weaknesses and potential rare qualities! This version adds Mega Evolved Pokémon, gorgeous watercolor-inspired graphics, and more! Get comfortable in your Pokémon form, there’s a lot of work to do.</desc>
		<image>./images/Pokemon Mystery Dungeon - Rescue Team DX (Europe)-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Pokemon Mystery Dungeon - Rescue Team DX (Europe)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Pokemon Mystery Dungeon - Rescue Team DX (Europe)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Pokemon Mystery Dungeon - Rescue Team DX (Europe)-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Pokemon Mystery Dungeon - Rescue Team DX (Europe)-boxback.png</boxback>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<family>Pokémon</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074048" />
	</game>
	<game id="359649">
		<path>./Games/Pokemon Shield (Europe).xci</path>
		<name>Pokémon Shield</name>
		<desc>A new generation of Pokémon is coming to the Nintendo Switch™ system. Begin your adventure as a Pokémon Trainer by choosing one of three new partner Pokémon: Grookey, Scorbunny, or Sobble. Then embark on a journey in the new Galar region, where you'll challenge the troublemakers of Team Yell, while unraveling the mystery behind the Legendary Pokémon Zacian and Zamazenta! Explore the Wild Area, a vast expanse of land where the player can freely control the camera.</desc>
		<image>./images/Pokemon Shield (Europe)-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Pokemon Shield (Europe)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Pokemon Shield (Europe)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Pokemon Shield (Europe)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Pokemon Shield (Europe)-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Pokemon Shield (Europe)-boxback.png</boxback>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20191115T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games / Action RPG</genre>
		<family>Pokémon</family>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074051" />
	</game>
	<game id="359646">
		<path>./Games/Pokemon Sword (Europe).xci</path>
		<name>Pokemon Sword</name>
		<desc>Begin your adventure as a Pokémon Trainer by choosing one of three new partner Pokémon: Grookey, Scorbunny, or Sobble. Then embark on a journey in the new Galar region, where you'll challenge the troublemakers of Team Yell, while unraveling the mystery behind the Legendary Pokémon Zacian and Zamazenta! Explore the Wild Area, a vast expanse of land where the player can freely control the camera. Team up with three other players locally or online in the new multiplayer co-op Max Raid Battles* in which players will face off against gigantic and super-strong Pokémon known as Dynamax Pokémon. Certain Pokémon can even Gigantamax to gain a new look and a powerful set of G-Max moves. But there's more to being a champion than honing your battle skills: you can pick your own clothes and get a new hairdo while visiting the stores in town, so you can be the Trainer you want to be. Throughout your journey, you'll encounter newly discovered Pokémon as well as familiar ones that will look a little different in their new Galarian forms! And for another way to level up your Pokémon, assign them Poké Jobs to complete. You can even play with your Pokémon in Pokémon Camp, just for fun!</desc>
		<image>./images/Pokemon Sword (Europe)-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Pokemon Sword (Europe)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Pokemon Sword (Europe)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Pokemon Sword (Europe)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Pokemon Sword (Europe)-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Pokemon Sword (Europe)-boxback.png</boxback>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>20191115T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games / Action RPG</genre>
		<family>Pokémon</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074053" />
	</game>
	<game id="196001">
		<path>./Games/Portal Knights.xci</path>
		<name>Portal Knights</name>
		<desc>Prove yourself a Portal Knight by levelling up your character, crafting epic weapons, and vanquishing foes in real-time in this cooperative, 3D sandbox action RPG.

Explore dozens of randomly-generated islands! Build almost anything! In a world torn apart by the Fracture and terrorized by the Hollow King, you and your friends are its only hope!</desc>
		<image>./images/Portal Knights-image.jpg</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Portal Knights-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>20171123T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Keen Games</developer>
		<publisher>505 Games</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074055" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Professional Farmer.xci</path>
		<name>Professional Farmer</name>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074057" />
	</game>
	<game id="198059">
		<path>./Games/Q.U.B.E. 2.xci</path>
		<name>Q.u.b.e. 2</name>
		<desc>Q.U.B.E. 2 is the sequel to the hit first-person puzzle game Q.U.B.E. You are Amelia Cross, a stranded archaeologist who has awoken among the ruins of an ancient alien landscape. With the distant help of another survivor you must solve the puzzles of this mysterious world and find a way back home.Features- Master eleven puzzle areas and solve over 80 individual puzzles- Explore diverse environments that expand the Q.U.B.E. world- Experience an all new adventure and brand new characters- Interact with new and improved game mechanics- Original musical score composed by BAFTA nominated composer, David Housden- Full colourblind support, using symbols as a colour aid</desc>
		<marquee>./images/Q.U.B.E. 2-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Q.U.B.E. 2-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/Q.U.B.E. 2-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20190221T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Toxic Games</developer>
		<publisher>Trapped Nerve Games</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074100" />
	</game>
	<game id="198067">
		<path>./Games/Rad Rodgers Radical Edition.xci</path>
		<name>Rad Rodgers Radical Edition</name>
		<desc>Rad is a rambunctious but spirited young boy who maybe plays too many video games. After dozing off at the tail end of a long night of gaming, Rad awakens to find his dusty old console has turned itself back on. Suddenly a vortex emerges and he's sucked into his TV, where he finds himself the star in his very own video game adventure.
Dusty is Rad's good-hearted but foul-mouthed, now-sentient game console. His clock speed isn't what it used to be, but what he lacks for in megahertz he makes up for with experience and attitude!
Rad &amp; Dusty's adventure takes them through many dangerous stages of action-packed, humor-filled, hardcore platforming fun. This decaying jungle world has been infected by a fierce corruption, and it's up to the unlikely buddy-duo Rad and Dusty to save the jungle's inhabitants and restore the Elder Tree as guardian of the land.</desc>
		<marquee>./images/Rad Rodgers Radical Edition-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Rad Rodgers Radical Edition-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Rad Rodgers Radical Edition-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Rad Rodgers Radical Edition-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20190226T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Slipgate Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Handygames</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074102" />
	</game>
	<game id="195855">
		<path>./Games/Rayman Legends - Definitive Edition.xci</path>
		<name>Rayman Legends: Definitive Edition</name>
		<desc>Rayman, Globox, and the Teensies are off wandering through an enchanted forest when they discover a mysterious tent filled with a series of captivating paintings. As they look more closely, they notice each painting seems to tell the story of a mythical world. While focusing on a painting that shows a medieval land, they are suddenly sucked into the painting, entering the world, and the adventure begins. The gang must run, jump, and fight their way through each world to save the day and discover the secrets of every legendary painting.</desc>
		<image>./images/Rayman Legends - Definitive Edition-image.jpg</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Rayman Legends - Definitive Edition-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Rayman Legends - Definitive Edition-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Rayman Legends - Definitive Edition-boxback.png</boxback>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20170912T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<family>Rayman</family>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074104" />
	</game>
	<game id="196281">
		<path>./Games/RBI Baseball 18.xci</path>
		<name>R.B.I. Baseball 18</name>
		<desc>It's a whole new ballgame with R.B.I. Baseball 18! R.B.I. 18 takes a significant leap delivering all-new Franchise Mode, Home Run Derby Mode, brand new detailed player models, hundreds of new animations, high fidelity MLB ballparks, revamped crowd system, more dynamic camera angles and a stunning UI presentation. This MLB season get the baseball game that will have you wanting to PLAY IT AGAIN!</desc>
		<thumbnail>./images/RBI Baseball 18-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/RBI Baseball 18-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20180614T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>MLB</developer>
		<publisher>MLB.com</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Baseball</genre>
		<family>R.B.I. Baseball</family>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074109" />
	</game>
	<game id="198099">
		<path>./Games/RBI Baseball 19.xci</path>
		<name>R.b.i. Baseball 19</name>
		<desc>R.B.I. Baseball 19 takes the field delivering heightened authenticity for a genuine MLB experience. We've added hundreds of new animations, updated player models, every official 2019 uniform, more player gear, improved ball physics and environments, and more!</desc>
		<thumbnail>./images/RBI Baseball 19-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/RBI Baseball 19-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20190305T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>MLB</developer>
		<publisher>MLB Advanced Media</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Baseball</genre>
		<family>R.B.I. Baseball</family>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074115" />
	</game>
	<game id="195875">
		<path>./Games/RBI Baseball 2017 (USA).xci</path>
		<name>R.b.i. Baseball 17</name>
		<desc>Your breakout MLB season is on Nintendo Switch! R.B.I. Baseball 17 returns in the fourth edition of the classic franchise, developed by MLB.com. Fun, fast paced, high-octane baseball action bring back R.B.I's pick-up-and-play roots. Take control of your game with reactive pitching and batting systems that allow for in-the-moment decisions. R.B.I. 17 is packed with 30 authentic ballparks, advanced stat tracking, season game sims and roster updates throughout the season. R.B.I. Baseball is back, you gotta come ready to play!</desc>
		<releasedate>20170905T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>MLB Advanced Media</developer>
		<publisher>MLB Advanced Media</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Baseball</genre>
		<family>R.B.I. Baseball</family>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074117" />
	</game>
	<game id="195941">
		<path>./Games/Resident Evil Revelations.xci</path>
		<name>Resident Evil Revelations</name>
		<desc>Resident Evil Revelations features series favorites Jill Valentine and Chris Redfield, plus their respective BSAA partners - Parker Luciani and Jessica Sherawat. The action begins on board a supposedly abandoned cruise ship, the 'Queen Zenobia', where horrors lurk around every corner, before players head for the mainland and the devastated city of Terragrigia. With limited ammo and weapons available, the race is on to survive the horror of Resident Evil Revelations.</desc>
		<image>./images/Resident Evil Revelations-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Resident Evil Revelations-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Resident Evil Revelations-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Resident Evil Revelations-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<releasedate>20171128T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure / Survival Horror</genre>
		<family>Resident Evil</family>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074120" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/RICO.xci</path>
		<name>RICO</name>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074121" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Rime.xci</path>
		<name>Rime</name>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074123" />
	</game>
	<game id="195897">
		<path>./Games/Rocket League.xci</path>
		<name>Rocket League Collector's Edition</name>
		<desc>Compete in the high-octane hybrid of arcade-style soccer and vehicular mayhem! Unlock items in Rocket Pass, climb the Competitive Ranks, compete in Competitive Tournaments, complete Challenges, enjoy cross-platform progression and more! The field is waiting. Take your shot!</desc>
		<image>./images/Rocket League-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Rocket League-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Rocket League-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Rocket League-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Rocket League-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20171114T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Psyonix</developer>
		<publisher>Psyonix</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Soccer</genre>
		<players>1-8</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074126" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Secret Neighbor.nsp</path>
		<name>Secret Neighbor</name>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074128" />
	</game>
	<game id="196045">
		<path>./Games/Shaq Fu - A Legend Reborn.xci</path>
		<name>Shaq Fu - A Legend Reborn</name>
		<desc>A vessel floating down a river contains an orphaned baby boy. He is found and adopted. As he grows, he learns of his true identity and destiny of greatness. Thus is the premise of two of the greatest stories of our time, but that is where the similarities end.</desc>
		<image>./images/Shaq Fu - A Legend Reborn-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Shaq Fu - A Legend Reborn-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Shaq Fu - A Legend Reborn-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Shaq Fu - A Legend Reborn-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Shaq Fu - A Legend Reborn-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Shaq Fu - A Legend Reborn-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20180605T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Saber Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<family>Shaq Fu</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074131" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Shelter Generations EUR.xci</path>
		<name>Shelter Generations EUR</name>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074132" />
	</game>
	<game id="196195">
		<path>./Games/Shining Resonance Refrain.xci</path>
		<name>Shining Resonance Refrain</name>
		<desc>Play as Yuma Ilvern and stop the Empire from exploiting the power of the ancient dragons, including the soul of the Shining Dragon within you. With the help of your friends, realize your destiny, save Astoria, and unleash the strength you've always had locked away.

Dragons were long thought to be extinct, and because Yuma holds the ability to transform into the Shining Dragon, he was taken as a captive of the Empire. With the help of the Dragoneers, Sonia, princess of Astoria, pleads with Yuma to aid them in their fight to save their land from the Empire's dominion. Typically timid, will Yuma find the courage to realize the strength he has within him?</desc>
		<image>./images/Shining Resonance Refrain-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Shining Resonance Refrain-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Shining Resonance Refrain-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>20180710T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074134" />
	</game>
	<game id="197877">
		<path>./Games/Sid Meiers Civilization VI.xci</path>
		<name>Sid Meiers Civilization 6</name>
		<desc>Explore a new land, research technology, conquer your enemies, and go head-to-head with history's most renowned leaders as you attempt to build the greatest civilization the world has ever known.</desc>
		<marquee>./images/Sid Meiers Civilization VI-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Sid Meiers Civilization VI-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Sid Meiers Civilization VI-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<releasedate>20181116T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Aspyr</developer>
		<publisher>2K Games</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation / Build And Management</genre>
		<family>Civilization</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074137" />
	</game>
	<game id="198153">
		<path>./Games/Silence.xci</path>
		<name>Silence</name>
		<desc>War rages on. During an air raid, 16 year old Noah and his little sister Renie seek shelter in a bunker. There, not only are they protected from the deadly bombardment, but are also at the crossroads of a world between life and death: Silence. When Noah's sister gets lost in Silence, he is forced to venture into this idyllic yet threatening world to find her.

Join Noah and Renie on their exciting journey through Silence where an emotionally gripping story of contrasts between serenity and danger unfolds. Meet fascinating and likeable characters like Spot, the magical caterpillar who helps Noah and Renie on their way through Silence. And witness when the siblings discover that the only thing that can save them is their love for each other.</desc>
		<thumbnail>./images/Silence-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/Silence-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20190411T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Daedalic Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Daedalic Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074143" />
	</game>
	<game id="195883">
		<path>./Games/Skylanders - Imaginators.xci</path>
		<name>Skylanders Imaginators</name>
		<desc>Kaos has discovered the ancient power of Mind Magic and is using it to create an unstoppable army of Doomlanders! Eon is calling upon all Portal Masters and Skylands' greatest mystic warriors, the Senseis, to stop Kaos and his minions. Now, you must use the power of your imagination to create your own Skylanders to battle in the ultimate adventure alongside the almighty Senseis to save Skylands.Now with Skylanders Imaginators on the Nintendo Switch™, Embark on an Epic New Adventure on-the-goUse the Digital Library for easy on-the-go access to your Skylanders toy collectionUse the Imaginite Creation Crystals to Create Your Own SkylandersSensei Skylanders are the Ultimate Masters of the Almighty Sky-Chi PowersBattle to Save Skylands with the Sensei and Imaginator SkylandersUse 10 Different Battle Class Types to Defeat Kaos and his MinionsConquer All-New Side quests &amp; Mini-games</desc>
		<image>./images/Skylanders - Imaginators-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Skylanders - Imaginators-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Skylanders - Imaginators-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/Skylanders - Imaginators-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20170303T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Toys For Bob</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<family>Skylanders</family>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074146" />
	</game>
	<game id="196975">
		<path>./Games/Snake Pass.xci</path>
		<name>Snake Pass</name>
		<desc>THINK LIKE A SNAKE! When the tranquility of Haven Tor is interrupted by a mysterious interloper only the unlikeliest of heroes can save the day! Meet Noodle the Snake and his hyperactive best friend, Doodle the Hummingbird, who together must re-unite the missing Keystones with the magical gates that give Haven Tor its mythical power.

A unique, physics based puzzle platform game, Snake Pass challenges players to 'think like a snake' as they tackle precarious puzzles as only a snake can.</desc>
		<image>./images/Snake Pass-image.jpg</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Snake Pass-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/Snake Pass-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20170328T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sumo Digital</developer>
		<publisher>Curve Digital Games</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074148" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Snipperclips.xci</path>
		<name>Snipperclips</name>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074150" />
	</game>
	<game id="197395">
		<path>./Games/SNK Heroines Tag Team Frenzy.xci</path>
		<name>Snk Heroines - Tag Team Frenzy</name>
		<image>./images/SNK Heroines Tag Team Frenzy-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/SNK Heroines Tag Team Frenzy-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/SNK Heroines Tag Team Frenzy-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/SNK Heroines Tag Team Frenzy-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/SNK Heroines Tag Team Frenzy-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20180907T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Abstraction Games</developer>
		<publisher>NIS America</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-8</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074152" />
	</game>
	<game id="195899">
		<path>./Games/Sonic Forces.xci</path>
		<name>Sonic Forces</name>
		<desc>In SONIC FORCES, the evil Dr. Eggman has conquered much of the world with help from a powerful and mysterious new villain named Infinite. Now, you must assist Sonic and build an army to reclaim the world as they fight against chaos and destruction.

Defeat enemies with blazing speed as Modern Sonic, catapult past perilous platforms as Classic Sonic, and create your very own Custom Hero Character equipped with a variety of powerful gadgets. Experience fast-paced action with these three unique gameplay styles.</desc>
		<image>./images/Sonic Forces-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Sonic Forces-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Sonic Forces-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Sonic Forces-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Sonic Forces-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20171107T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sonic Team</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074154" />
	</game>
	<game id="196211">
		<path>./Games/Sonic Mania Plus (World) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It,Zh).xci</path>
		<name>ZZZ(notgame):Sonic Mania Plus</name>
		<desc>Welcome to the next level for the world’s fastest blue hedgehog. Welcome to Sonic Mania, available anytime, anywhere on Nintendo Switch.Relive the classic 2D Sonic games of the past in this all-new adventure!Enjoy exciting twists on iconic Zones, as well as brand new Zones and Acts!Play as Sonic, Tails and Knuckles, and use their abilities to defeat Dr. Eggman’s evil robot army!Go head-to-head in Competition Mode or team up in Co-Op Mode!</desc>
		<image>./images/Sonic Mania Plus (World) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It,Zh)-image.png</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Sonic Mania Plus (World) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It,Zh)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/Sonic Mania Plus (World) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It,Zh)-boxback.png</boxback>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<hidden>true</hidden>
		<lang>de,en,jp,es,fr,it</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074156" />
	</game>
	<game id="196003">
		<path>./Games/South Park The Fractured But Whole.xci</path>
		<name>South Park - The Fractured But Whole</name>
		<desc>From the creators of South Park, Trey Parker and Matt Stone, comes South Park: The Fractured But Whole, a sequel to 2014's award-winning South Park: The Stick of Truth. Players will once again assume the role of the New Kid and join South Park favorites Stan, Kyle, Kenny and Cartman in a new hilarious and outrageous RPG adventure.

In South Park: The Fractured But Whole, players will delve into the crime-ridden underbelly of South Park with Coon and Friends. This dedicated group of crime fighters was formed by Eric Cartman whose superhero alter-ego, The Coon, is half man, half raccoon. As the New Kid, players will join Mysterion, Toolshed, Human Kite and a host of others to battle the forces of evil while Coon strives to make his team the most beloved superheroes in history.</desc>
		<image>./images/South Park The Fractured But Whole-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/South Park The Fractured But Whole-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/South Park The Fractured But Whole-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/South Park The Fractured But Whole-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/South Park The Fractured But Whole-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20180424T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074158" />
	</game>
	<game id="195815">
		<path>./Games/Splatoon 2.xci</path>
		<name>Splatoon 2</name>
		<desc>Splatoon 2 on Switch is a third-person shooter played in massive multiplayer. The particularity of the title is that your different weapons project paint and not bullets. Scramble through environments with friends, splash paint on yourselves and turn into squids to hide in the colored puddles.</desc>
		<image>./images/Splatoon 2-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Splatoon 2-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Splatoon 2-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Splatoon 2-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Splatoon 2-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Splatoon 2-boxback.png</boxback>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>20170721T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-8</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074201" />
	</game>
	<game id="198467">
		<path>./Games/Spyro Reignited Trilogy (USA).xci</path>
		<name>Spyro Reignited Trilogy</name>
		<desc>Explore the expansive realms, re-encounter the fiery personalities and relive the adventure in fully remastered glory. Because when there's a realm that needs saving, there's only one dragon to call.</desc>
		<marquee>./images/Spyro Reignited Trilogy (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Spyro Reignited Trilogy (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Spyro Reignited Trilogy (USA)-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Spyro Reignited Trilogy (USA)-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20190903T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Toys For Bob</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<family>Spyro</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074203" />
	</game>
	<game id="197749">
		<path>./Games/Starlink Battle For Atlas.xci</path>
		<name>Starlink - Battle For Atlas</name>
		<desc>In Starlink - Battle for Atlas, you are part of a group of heroic interstellar pilots, dedicated to free the Atlas Star System from Grax and the Forgotten Legion.</desc>
		<image>./images/Starlink Battle For Atlas-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Starlink Battle For Atlas-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Starlink Battle For Atlas-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/Starlink Battle For Atlas-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20181016T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft Toronto</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074206" />
	</game>
	<game id="196299">
		<path>./Games/State of Mind.xci</path>
		<name>State of Mind</name>
		<desc>Berlin, 2048 – The world is on the brink. Lack of resources, illnesses caused by polluted air and water, crime on the rise, war. Governments and companies promise remedies through technological progress. Drones and humanoid robots replace humans in the public sector, everything is interconnected, surveillance has become omnipresent.

Richard Nolan is one of the few journalists openly criticizing this development. When he wakes up in hospital after an explosion and finds that his wife and son have mysteriously vanished, Richard realizes: he and his family have become more than just bystanders in a storm of rivaling ideas pertaining humankind's salvation between dystopian reality and digital utopia. Instead, they find themselves right at the center of it.</desc>
		<image>./images/State of Mind-image.jpg</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/State of Mind-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/State of Mind-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20180815T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Daedalic Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Daedalic Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074208" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Steins Gate Elite.xci</path>
		<name>Steins Gate Elite</name>
		<marquee>./images/Steins Gate Elite-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Steins Gate Elite-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/Steins Gate Elite-boxback.jpg</boxback>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074210" />
	</game>
	<game id="196037">
		<path>./Games/Street Fighter - 30th Anniversary Collection.xci</path>
		<name>Street Fighter 30th Anniversary Collection</name>
		<desc>Celebrate Street Fighter's historic legacy with the Street Fighter 30th Anniversary Collection. In this massive collection of 12 Street Fighter titles, which encompass the Street Fighter I, Street Fighter II, Street Fighter III and Street Fighter Alpha series, perfect arcade balance makes it to consoles for the first time ever. Hop online and relive the arcade experience through the online Arcade Mode or play with friends in the online lobby within four of the most definitive Street Fighter titles in the collection.The celebration continues in the Museum, where fans and historians alike can follow the timeline of how Street Fighter has evolved over the past 30 years. Learn more about the Street Fighter cast, view key animation sprites in the character viewer and take a behind-the-scenes look at the design documents that helped solidify the franchise that produced generations of World Warriors!</desc>
		<image>./images/Street Fighter - 30th Anniversary Collection-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Street Fighter - 30th Anniversary Collection-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Street Fighter - 30th Anniversary Collection-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Street Fighter - 30th Anniversary Collection-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Street Fighter - 30th Anniversary Collection-boxback.png</boxback>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20180529T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Digital Eclipse</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<family>Street Fighter</family>
		<players>1-8</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074212" />
	</game>
	<game id="198165">
		<path>./Games/Super Dragon Ball Heroes World Mission.xci</path>
		<name>Super Dragon Ball Heroes - World Mission</name>
		<desc>SUPER DRAGON BALL HEROES WORLD MISSION is a Tactical-Card game packed with exhilarating confrontation, deep card game strategy and a thrilling storyline taking place in the wide Dragon Ball Heroes universe!

Welcome to Hero Town, an alternate reality where Dragon Ball Heroes card game is the most popular form of entertainment. Create your own avatar and follow his journey to become the world champion of Super Dragon Ball Heroes. However, when the antagonists from the virtual game world appear in Hero Town and start wreaking havoc, you have to jump into the game world and team up with famous Dragon Ball characters to restore peace in the real world.</desc>
		<marquee>./images/Super Dragon Ball Heroes World Mission-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Super Dragon Ball Heroes World Mission-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Super Dragon Ball Heroes World Mission-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Super Dragon Ball Heroes World Mission-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20190405T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Bandai Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1-6</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074215" />
	</game>
	<game id="359425">
		<path>./Games/Super Mario 3D All-Stars (World).xci</path>
		<name>Super Mario 3D All-Stars</name>
		<desc>Play three of Mario's greatest 3D platforming adventures, all in one pack! Jump through boards in Super Mario 64, clean up paint residue in Super Mario Sunshine, and fly from planet to planet in Super Mario Galaxy!
Mario's moves are smoother than ever with HD resolution for each game, while retaining the look and feel of the originals.</desc>
		<image>./images/Super Mario 3D All-Stars (World)-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Super Mario 3D All-Stars (World)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Super Mario 3D All-Stars (World)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Super Mario 3D All-Stars (World)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Super Mario 3D All-Stars (World)-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Super Mario 3D All-Stars (World)-boxback.png</boxback>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<developer>1-Up Studio</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>wr</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074218" />
	</game>
	<game id="198345">
		<path>./Games/Super Mario Maker 2 (USA).xci</path>
		<name>Super Mario Maker 2</name>
		<desc>Play Everywhere. Create Anywhere.Let your imagination run wild with new tools, course parts, and features as you create the Super Mario courses of your dreams. This sequel to Super Mario Maker launches exclusively on Nintendo Switch.</desc>
		<image>./images/Super Mario Maker 2 (USA)-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Super Mario Maker 2 (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Super Mario Maker 2 (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Super Mario Maker 2 (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Super Mario Maker 2 (USA)-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Super Mario Maker 2 (USA)-boxback.png</boxback>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>20190628T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074221" />
	</game>
	<game id="195863">
		<path>./Games/Super Mario Odyssey.xci</path>
		<name>Super Mario Odyssey</name>
		<desc>Explore incredible places far from the Mushroom Kingdom as you join Mario and his new ally Cappy on a massive, globe-trotting 3D adventure. Use amazing new abilities—like the power to capture and control objects, animals, and enemies—to collect Power Moons so you can power up the Odyssey airship and save Princess Peach from Bowser's wedding plans!Thanks to heroic, hat-shaped Cappy, Mario's got new moves that'll make you rethink his traditional run-and-jump gameplay—like cap jump, cap throw, and capture. Use captured cohorts such as enemies, objects, and animals to progress through the game and uncover loads of hidden collectibles. And if you feel like playing with a friend, just pass them a Joy-Con™ controller! Player 1 controls Mario while Player 2 controls Cappy. This sandbox-style 3D Mario adventure—the first since 1996's beloved Super Mario 64™ and 2002's Nintendo GameCube™ classic Super Mario Sunshine™—is packed with secrets and surprises, plus exciting new kingdoms to explore.</desc>
		<image>./images/Super Mario Odyssey-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Super Mario Odyssey-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Super Mario Odyssey-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Super Mario Odyssey-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Super Mario Odyssey-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Super Mario Odyssey-boxback.png</boxback>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>20171027T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074223" />
	</game>
	<game id="197733">
		<path>./Games/Super Mario Party (World).xci</path>
		<name>Super Mario Party</name>
		<desc>The original 4-player Mario Party series board game mode that fans love is back, and your friends and family are invited to the party! Freely walk the board: choose where to move, which Dice Block to roll, and how to win the most Stars in skill-based minigames. Wait till you see the 2 vs 2 mode with grid-based maps, the creative uses of the console, and the series’ first online minigame mode!Test your skills in sets of five minigames with the new mode, Mariothon, and see how you stack up against players across the globe in Online Mariothon*. Whether you’re pedaling tricycles, flipping meat, or who knows what else, you’ll use Joy-Con™ controllers in clever ways across 80 new minigames; some are all-out free-for-alls, others are 2 vs 2, or even 1 vs 3! Toad’s Rec Room lets you pair up two Nintendo Switch™ systems**, which you’ll lay side-by-side on a flat surface like a real tabletop game. That way you can play a mini baseball game, battle tanks in custom arenas, or even see who can match the most bananas by repositioning the systems however you see fit!</desc>
		<image>./images/Super Mario Party (World)-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Super Mario Party (World)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Super Mario Party (World)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Super Mario Party (World)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Super Mario Party (World)-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Super Mario Party (World)-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20181005T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Board game</genre>
		<family>Mario Party</family>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>wr</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074226" />
	</game>
	<game id="198139">
		<path>./Games/Super Robot Wars T.xci</path>
		<name>Super Robot Wars T</name>
		<desc>Super Robot Wars T is a Tactical RPG game with story elements derived from Visual Novels and utilizes the same graphics engine seen in 3rd Super Robot Wars Z, but with an inclusion of a 3d isometric map unlike its predecessor. Like other games, it follows the same basic structure: when a stage begins, the character receives introductory dialogue between playable characters, leading to the scenario on the battlefield. To complete a scenario, the player must accomplish scenario objectives. Some scenarios are longer, with multi-part missions or have new objectives added as the story unfolds. On battlefield, the player and enemy take turns to order their units with commands available, such as movement, attacking, forming squads and casting "Spirit Commands", a set of magic-like spells unique to each pilot. Once the scenario is cleared, more dialogue is exchanged between characters before the player is taken to an intermission menu. Here, units can be upgraded or optional parts installed, characters' stats and skills can be changed or upgraded, and other maintenance actions can be performed before the player continues on with the game.Gameplay elements from previous games return, including the Skill Route and Skill Program function introduced in Super Robot Wars V, as well as the Tac Management system and Hard Mode settings as they appeared in Super Robot Wars X. New elements in the game is included in the form of the Support Command, which grants special commands through Supporters. Supporter Spirits Points, needed to use Supporter Commands, are shared between all Supporters characters. The game also uses the sub-order system, first introduced in 2nd Super Robot Wars Z</desc>
		<marquee>./images/Super Robot Wars T-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Super Robot Wars T-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/Super Robot Wars T-boxback.png</boxback>
		<publisher>Bandai Namco Games</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074228" />
	</game>
	<game id="197929">
		<path>./Games/Super Smash Bros Ultimate.xci</path>
		<name>Super Smash Bros. Ultimate</name>
		<desc>Gaming icons clash in the ultimate brawl you can play anytime, anywhere! Smash rivals off the stage as new characters Simon Belmont and King K. Rool join Inkling, Ridley, and every fighter in Super Smash Bros. history. Enjoy enhanced speed and combat at new stages based on the Castlevania series, Super Mario Odyssey, and more!Having trouble choosing a stage? Then select the Stage Morph option to transform one stage into another while battling—a series first! Plus, new echo fighters Dark Samus, Richter Belmont, and Chrom join the battle. Whether you play locally or online, savor the faster combat, new attacks, and new defensive options, like a perfect shield. Jam out to 900 different music compositions and go 1-on-1 with a friend, hold a 4-player free-for-all, kick it up to 8-player battles and more! Feel free to bust out your GameCube controllers—legendary couch competitions await—or play together anytime, anywhere!</desc>
		<image>./images/Super Smash Bros Ultimate-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Super Smash Bros Ultimate-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Super Smash Bros Ultimate-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Super Smash Bros Ultimate-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Super Smash Bros Ultimate-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Super Smash Bros Ultimate-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20181207T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-8</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074231" />
	</game>
	<game id="195901">
		<path>./Games/Superbeat Xonic.xci</path>
		<name>Superbeat - Xonic</name>
		<desc>Experience SUPERBEAT: XONiC, the new music game sensation! Play your way through 68 unique songs and unlocks tons of hidden rewards and items!</desc>
		<image>./images/Superbeat Xonic-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20171121T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>PM Studios</publisher>
		<genre>Music and Dance</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074234" />
	</game>
	<game id="196213">
		<path>./Games/Sushi Striker - The Way of Sushido.xci</path>
		<name>Choukaiten Sushi Striker - The Way of Sushido</name>
		<desc>Learn the Way of SushidoSwitch_SushiStriker_description-charHelp Musashi end the Empire's tyrannical monopoly of the world's sushi supply by becoming a Sushi Striker! Devour conveyor-belt sushi, matching plates and sushi types to defeat any enemy or boss who stands between you and victory. Befriend Sushi Sprites and use their powerful skills in battle. Deliciously strategic action-RPG-puzzle battles await!</desc>
		<image>./images/Sushi Striker - The Way of Sushido-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Sushi Striker - The Way of Sushido-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Sushi Striker - The Way of Sushido-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/Sushi Striker - The Way of Sushido-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20180608T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074237" />
	</game>
	<game id="197773">
		<path>./Games/Syberia 3.xci</path>
		<name>Syberia 3</name>
		<desc>Enter the enchanting world of Benoit SokalKate Walker is found dying on the banks of a river by the Youkol tribe, a nomadic people accompanying their migrating snow ostriches. Together, stuck and imprisoned in the town of Valsembor, they must find a way to continue their journey in a race against their enemies and unexpected obstacles. Not to mention Kate's past, which catches up with her...A world filled out with exceptional story-telling, imagined and drawn by Benoit Sokal, with music by Inon Zur.Discover an enchanting world full of mystery and life, that you can completely explore in 3D.Immerse yourself in the story, original puzzles, and mysteries of the fabulous adventure of an unforgettable heroine</desc>
		<marquee>./images/Syberia 3-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Syberia 3-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/Syberia 3-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20181018T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Microïds</developer>
		<publisher>Microïds</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<family>Syberia</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074242" />
	</game>
	<game id="197983">
		<path>./Games/Tales of Vesperia Definitive Edition.xci</path>
		<name>Tales Of Vesperia - Definitive Edition</name>
		<desc>A power struggle begins in a civilization dependent on an ancient technology, the blastia, and the Empire that controls it. The fates of two friends traveling separate paths intertwine in an epic adventure that threatens the existence of all.</desc>
		<thumbnail>./images/Tales of Vesperia Definitive Edition-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/Tales of Vesperia Definitive Edition-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20190111T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Bandai Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<family>Tales Of</family>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074247" />
	</game>
	<game id="196187">
		<path>./Games/Tennis World Tour (Europe).xci</path>
		<name>Tennis World Tour</name>
		<desc>THE BIGGEST STARS IN TENNIS• Play as one of the 30 best tennis players in the world: Roger Federer, Angelique Kerber, Stan Wawrinka and many of the sport's legends.PERFECTLY REPRODUCED MOVEMENT• Realistic animations, carefully reproduced in the game using motion capture technology, help you learn all of the shots used in modern tennis: the slice, lob, top spin, etc.EVERY PLAYING SURFACE• 18 types of courts: hard, clay, grass, carpet and even hardwood. Each surface affects the playing conditions.A COMPLETE CAREER MODE• Create your player and experience a career worthy of a professional: training, tournaments, staff management, equipment purchases, etc.AN UNEQUALLED TACTICAL DIMENSION• Decide what strategy to adopt for each match and use your skill cards to defeat your opponents.</desc>
		<marquee>./images/Tennis World Tour (Europe)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Tennis World Tour (Europe)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Tennis World Tour (Europe)-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Tennis World Tour (Europe)-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20180619T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Breakpoint</developer>
		<publisher>Nacon</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Tennis</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074249" />
	</game>
	<game id="198033">
		<path>./Games/The Book Of Unwritten Tales 2.xci</path>
		<name>Book Of Unwritten Tales 2, The</name>
		<desc>Legend foretold it. Prophecies predicted it. Chosen ones chose to believe in it. Now the fantasy spoof adventure saga continues. Join Wilbur, Ivo, Nate and Critter in another classic point-and-click adventure in the wicked world of Aventasia. Help them fulfill their destiny. A destiny as yet unwritten.</desc>
		<marquee>./images/The Book Of Unwritten Tales 2-marquee.png</marquee>
		<fanart>./images/The Book Of Unwritten Tales 2-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<releasedate>20190205T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>King Art</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074252" />
	</game>
	<game id="198105">
		<path>./Games/The Caligula Effect Overdose.xci</path>
		<name>Caligula Effect - Overdose, The</name>
		<desc>Something's amiss in the seemingly perfect world of Mobius. Escape from the false paradise and return to reality, or risk losing more than just your identity!</desc>
		<releasedate>20190312T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>NIS America</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074254" />
	</game>
	<game id="195915">
		<path>./Games/The Elder Scrolls V Skyrim.xci</path>
		<name>Elder Scrolls V - Skyrim, The</name>
		<desc>Take down enemies with the Master Sword, protect yourself with the Hylian Shield or look heroic in the Champion's Tunic. The legendary freedom of choice and adventure of Skyrim is realized like never before. Dragons, long lost to the passages of the Elder Scrolls, have returned and the future of Skyrim hangs in the balance. As Dragonborn, the prophesized hero born with the power of The Voice, you are the only one who can stand amongst them.</desc>
		<image>./images/The Elder Scrolls V Skyrim-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/The Elder Scrolls V Skyrim-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/The Elder Scrolls V Skyrim-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/The Elder Scrolls V Skyrim-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20171117T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bethesda Softworks</developer>
		<publisher>Bethesda Softworks</publisher>
		<family>The Elder Scrolls</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074257" />
	</game>
	<game id="359978">
		<path>./Games/The Great Ace Attorney Chronicles.xci</path>
		<name>The Great Ace Attorney Chronicles</name>
		<marquee>./images/The Great Ace Attorney Chronicles-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/The Great Ace Attorney Chronicles-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/The Great Ace Attorney Chronicles-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/The Great Ace Attorney Chronicles-boxback.png</boxback>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<family>Ace Attorney</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074259" />
	</game>
	<game id="198483">
		<path>./Games/The Legend of Zelda - Link's Awakening.xci</path>
		<name>The Legend Of Zelda : Link's Awakening</name>
		<desc>As Link, you awaken in a strange land away from Hyrule, where animals talk and monsters roam. To uncover the truth behind your whereabouts and rouse the legendary Wind Fish, explore Koholint Island and all its trap-ridden dungeons, reimagined in stunning detail for this new release of one of the most beloved The Legend of Zelda games. Along the way, you'll meet a hilarious assortment of charming characters to which you'll never want to say goodbye.</desc>
		<image>./images/The Legend of Zelda - Link's Awakening-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/The Legend of Zelda - Link's Awakening-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/The Legend of Zelda - Link's Awakening-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/The Legend of Zelda - Link's Awakening-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/The Legend of Zelda - Link's Awakening-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/The Legend of Zelda - Link's Awakening-boxback.png</boxback>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20190920T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action / Adventure</genre>
		<family>The Legend of Zelda</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074301" />
	</game>
	<game id="195745">
		<path>./Games/The Legend of Zelda Breath of the Wild.xci</path>
		<name>The Legend of Zelda: Breath of the Wild</name>
		<desc>Forget everything you know about The Legend of Zelda games. Step into a world of discovery, exploration, and adventure in The Legend of Zelda: Breath of the Wild, a boundary-breaking new game in the acclaimed series. Travel across vast fields, through forests, and to mountain peaks as you discover what has become of the kingdom of Hyrule in this stunning Open-Air Adventure. Now on Nintendo Switch, your journey is freer and more open than ever. Take your system anywhere, and adventure as Link any way you like.</desc>
		<image>./images/The Legend of Zelda Breath of the Wild-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/The Legend of Zelda Breath of the Wild-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/The Legend of Zelda Breath of the Wild-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/The Legend of Zelda Breath of the Wild-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/The Legend of Zelda Breath of the Wild-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/The Legend of Zelda Breath of the Wild-boxback.png</boxback>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>20170303T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<family>The Legend of Zelda</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074304" />
	</game>
	<game id="198091">
		<path>./Games/The LEGO Movie 2 Videogame.xci</path>
		<name>Lego Movie 2 Videogame, The</name>
		<desc>The alien monster invaders have left Bricksburg in ruins and taken Emmet's friends! It is now up to Emmet and a host of heroic characters to go beyond their world and save their friends from the strange inhabitants of the Systar System. Journey into outer space, discover new worlds, and test your Master Building skills.</desc>
		<releasedate>20190226T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>TT Games</developer>
		<publisher>Warner Bros. Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<family>LEGO</family>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074308" />
	</game>
	<game id="195929">
		<path>./Games/The LEGO NINJAGO Movie Video Game.xci</path>
		<name>Lego Ninjago Movie Videogame, The</name>
		<desc>Play as your favorite ninjas, Lloyd, Jay, Kai, Cole, Zane, Nya and Master Wu to defend their home island of Ninjago from the evil Lord Garmadon and his Shark Army.</desc>
		<releasedate>20170922T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>TT Games</developer>
		<publisher>Warner Bros. Interactive</publisher>
		<family>LEGO</family>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074310" />
	</game>
	<game id="197999">
		<path>./Games/The Raven Remastered.xci</path>
		<name>Raven Remastered, The</name>
		<desc>London, 1964. An ancient ruby is stolen from the British Museum. At the crime scene: a raven feather. Is somebody trying to follow in the footsteps of The Raven, the legendary master thief who disappeared years before?

Constable Anton Jakob Zellner finds himself in the middle of the kind of murder mystery he so far only knew from reading his favourite crime novels. Nothing is what it seems. Everyone has something to hide. And the Raven is always one step ahead...</desc>
		<releasedate>20190122T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>King Art</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074313" />
	</game>
	<game id="196253">
		<path>./Games/Titan Quest.xci</path>
		<name>Titan Quest</name>
		<desc>From Age of Empires co-creator Brian Sullivan and Braveheart writer Randall Wallace comes an innovative action role playing game set in ancient Greece, Egypt and Asia. The Titans have escaped their eternal prison, wreaking havoc upon the earth. The gods seek a hero who can turn the tide in an epic struggle that will determine the fate of both men and gods. Are you ready for the quest?Explore the Ancient World - Unlock arcane mysteries as you journey to legendary locationsConquer Monsters of Legend - Battle mythical beasts in a story-driven campaign that will determine the fate of all existenceHighly Customizable Characters - Build and customize your characters with 28 classes and over 1000 pieces of unique and legendary items to create the ultimate championOnline Multiplayer Gameplay - Challenge others to experience the story in fast-action, 2-6 player online cooperative gameplayConsole controls &amp; UI – Tailor made UI and controls for a perfect ARPG experience using a gamepad</desc>
		<image>./images/Titan Quest-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Titan Quest-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Titan Quest-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/Titan Quest-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20180731T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1-6</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074318" />
	</game>
	<game id="197995">
		<path>./Games/Travis Strikes Again No More Heroes.xci</path>
		<name>Travis Strikes Again - No More Heroes</name>
		<desc>Several years after No More Heroes 2... This time, the setting is a small town in the middle of nowhere in the American South. Badman shows up at the trailer Travis has been living in to exact revenge for the murder of his daughter, Bad Girl, and things go horribly wrong. As they battle it out, the two are sucked into the game world of the legendary game console, the Death Drive MkⅡ. Developed by Dr. Juvenile, the Death Drive MkⅡ has six games contained on Death Balls. It’s said that collecting all six and then beating each game allows the player to have one wish granted. Travis and Badman team up to use the Death Balls to bring Bad Girl back to life.In the Adventure Part, you can search for Death Balls (game software) and enjoy hilarious interactions between characters.Pass a Joy-Con™ to a friend and team up anytime, anywhere! By performing simultaneous Charge Attacks during co-op play, you can unleash the super-powerful co-op attack Choco Banana with Caramel Ice Cream.Collaborations with various indie games! You just may find your own favorite character!Features lots of laughs and iconic gags from the NMH series, such as saving your game on the toilet, etc.!DLC scheduled to make fan favorites playable! Stages also to be added!Hit the road in an all new adventure with gaming's most hardcore otaku assassin.Beam Katana in hand, Travis Strikes Again!</desc>
		<marquee>./images/Travis Strikes Again No More Heroes-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Travis Strikes Again No More Heroes-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Travis Strikes Again No More Heroes-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Travis Strikes Again No More Heroes-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20190118T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>grasshopper manufacture inc.</developer>
		<publisher>grasshopper manufacture inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074320" />
	</game>
	<game id="198057">
		<path>./Games/Trials Rising.xci</path>
		<name>Trials Rising</name>
		<desc>Explore over-the-top action and physics-bending motorcycle racing in the latest entry in the Trials franchise. With over 125 new tracks, Trials® Rising is easy to pick up and play, challenging to master, and offers the best multiplayer racing experience ever.Experience the most challenging tracks around the world – from the Great Wall of China to the Eiffel Tower.Test your friendships with the new Tandem mode that allows two players to control one bike. Hilarity is guaranteed!Create and share unique levels in Track Central with over 8,000 items available. The fun and possibilities are endless!From your local backyard to worldwide stadiums, defeat all your opponents online and rise to glory.</desc>
		<thumbnail>./images/Trials Rising-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/Trials Rising-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20190226T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074327" />
	</game>
	<game id="198179">
		<path>./Games/Truberbrook.xci</path>
		<name>Truberbrook</name>
		<desc>Trüberbrook is a thrilling mystery-sci-fi adventure game. Enjoy an adventurous vacation to a 1960's parallel universe! A Sci-Fi-Mystery Adventure Game with handmade scenery. Imagine yourself on a vacation to Europe in the late sixties. Now, picture yourself as a young American scientist; Hans Tannhauser. While you're at it, think of Trüberbrook, a remote village in rural Germany. Because, that's where you end up after hitting the continent. But who cares, you won the trip in a lottery! Or at least, that's how it seems. But don't fear, instead of getting some rest, you could find yourself having to save the world...</desc>
		<thumbnail>./images/Truberbrook-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/Truberbrook-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20190417T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>btf</developer>
		<publisher>Headup Games</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074335" />
	</game>
	<game id="195829">
		<path>./Games/Ultra Street Fighter II - The Final Challengers.xci</path>
		<name>Ultra Street Fighter II: The Final Challengers</name>
		<desc>The newest iteration of SFII in nearly 10 years, Ultra Street Fighter II features all of the classic characters, a host of new single player and multiplayer features, as well as two new fighters: Evil Ryu and Violent Ken! Nintendo Switch TV, Tabletop and Handheld modes allow you to play Ultra Street Fighter II at home or on-the-go!</desc>
		<image>./images/Ultra Street Fighter II - The Final Challengers-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Ultra Street Fighter II - The Final Challengers-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Ultra Street Fighter II - The Final Challengers-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Ultra Street Fighter II - The Final Challengers-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Ultra Street Fighter II - The Final Challengers-boxback.png</boxback>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20170526T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / 2D</genre>
		<family>Street Fighter</family>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074337" />
	</game>
	<game id="195911">
		<path>./Games/Unbox - Newbies Adventure.xci</path>
		<name>Unbox - Newbies Adventure</name>
		<desc>The ultimate postal service has arrived - self-delivering cardboard boxes! Unbox: Newbie's Adventure is a unique physics-platformer. Enjoy an epic single player adventure or grab up to four friends for local multiplayer races, battles and challenges!

The Global Postal Service is nearing bankruptcy! To save themselves, they have created self-delivering boxes. Play as the GPS' latest cardboard creation, Newbie, as you attempt to save the day. Dress to impress with a massive range of over 40,000 combinations of hats, clothes accessories and funny faces. Explore huge worlds full of challenges, collectibles and boxy boss battles as you compete against the dastardly Wild Cards!

Don't be a square! Think outside the box and create your very own cool cube!</desc>
		<image>./images/Unbox - Newbies Adventure-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Unbox - Newbies Adventure-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Unbox - Newbies Adventure-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Unbox - Newbies Adventure-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<releasedate>20171012T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Prospect Games</developer>
		<publisher>Merge Games</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074340" />
	</game>
	<game id="197941">
		<path>./Games/V Rally 4.xci</path>
		<name>V-rally 4</name>
		<desc>The legendary off-road racing game returns! Enjoy an extreme experience while becoming an expert in a demanding simulation. Take on the challenges of rallies, rallycross, drifts, buggies and hill climbs, and set off on a spectacular journey across every continent.
Dominate dangerous roads, hostile conditions, and environments, constantly striving for more speed. Let adrenaline boost your reflexes at the wheel of the most legendary off-road vehicles in each category, and take on the most difficult routes in fabulous surroundings.
V-Rally 4 features over 50 car models, including the most famous in rallying and extreme motor sports, for you to test drive, collect, upgrade, customize and, above all, master!</desc>
		<marquee>./images/V Rally 4-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/V Rally 4-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/V Rally 4-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/V Rally 4-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20190306T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Kylotonn Racing Games</developer>
		<publisher>Nacon</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074342" />
	</game>
	<game id="197707">
		<path>./Games/Valkyria Chronicles 4.xci</path>
		<name>Valkyria Chronicles 4</name>
		<desc>Valkyria Chronicles 4 takes place in the same timeframe as the original Valkyria Chronicles, but focuses on Squad E of the Federation. Commander Claude Wallace and his childhood friends set out to fight for freedom in this desperate war, but bone-chilling blizzards, waves of imperial soldiers, and the godlike powers of the Valkyria stand between them and victory.</desc>
		<image>./images/Valkyria Chronicles 4-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Valkyria Chronicles 4-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Valkyria Chronicles 4-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Valkyria Chronicles 4-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Valkyria Chronicles 4-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20180925T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074344" />
	</game>
	<game id="197759">
		<path>./Games/Warriors Orochi 4.xci</path>
		<name>Warriors Orochi 4</name>
		<desc>Features of WARRIORS OROCHI 4:・A dream collaboration starring heroes from DYNASTY WARRIORS and SAMURAI WARRIORS!・A roster of 170 playable characters! Five new characters - Zeus, Athena, Ares, Perseus, and Odin join the battle!・Introducing "Magic" to the series, you can now experience even more thrilling and intense Musou Action!・An online multiplayer mode is included for the first time ever in the series!For details about the game, please visit the official website.www.koeitecmoamerica.com/wo4/Pre-order Bonuses- Bonus Mount "Pegasus"- Bonus Mount "Unicorn"- Bonus Cosutme for "Wang Yi"- Bonus Costume for "Xingcai"- Bonus Costume for "Takatora Todo"Purchase before November 12, 2018 and receive a bonus costume.Early Purchase Bonus - Bonus Costumes for "Xu Shu", "Mitsunari Ishida", and "Da Ji"- Bonus Cosutme for "Wang Yuanji"- Bonus Cosutme for "Lady Hayakawa"- Bonus Cosutme for "Guo Jia"- Bonus Cosutme for "Yoshitsugu Otani"</desc>
		<image>./images/Warriors Orochi 4-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Warriors Orochi 4-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Warriors Orochi 4-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Warriors Orochi 4-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Warriors Orochi 4-boxback.png</boxback>
		<publisher>Koei Tecmo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<family>Warriors Orochi</family>
		<players>1-6</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074347" />
	</game>
	<game id="196163">
		<path>./Games/Wolfenstein II - The New Colossus.xci</path>
		<name>Wolfenstein 2 - The New Colossus</name>
		<desc>As BJ Blazkowicz, experience an unforgettable action-packed story brought to life by extraordinary characters. Reunite with your friends and fellow freedom fighters as you take on the evil Frau Engel and her Nazi army. Wage the second American Revolution your way – at home or on the go. And, for the perfect blend of immersion and accuracy, utilize the Nintendo Switch's unique motion controls to stop the Nazi threat.</desc>
		<image>./images/Wolfenstein II - The New Colossus-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Wolfenstein II - The New Colossus-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Wolfenstein II - The New Colossus-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/Wolfenstein II - The New Colossus-boxback.png</boxback>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20180629T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>MachineGames</developer>
		<publisher>Bethesda Softworks</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<family>Wolfenstein</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074351" />
	</game>
	<game id="198141">
		<path>./Games/World of Final Fantasy Maxima.xci</path>
		<name>World Of Final Fantasy Maxima</name>
		<desc>Originally released in October 2016, WORLD OF FINAL FANTASY is now available on Nintendo Switch™ as the powered-up FINAL FANTASY Maxima! Beloved characters from FF lore (Champions) and a multitude of capturable monsters (Mirages) appear in this fun and exciting adventure. This new and enhanced version of WORLD OF FINAL FANTASY also features the Avatar Change system, which allows the protagonists, Reynn and Lann, to fight as Champions. Fight your way through exhilarating battles as legendary FINAL FANTASY heroes</desc>
		<releasedate>20181106T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<family>Final Fantasy</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074354" />
	</game>
	<game id="195947">
		<path>./Games/WWE 2K18.xci</path>
		<name>WWE 2K18</name>
		<desc>ATTENTION: a microSD card (sold separately) with free storage space of minimum 32GB is required to download this game, plus 1GB on the system memory. You must have your microSD card inserted before beginning the download.Finally, WWE video games are back on Nintendo platforms with WWE 2K18, available for the first time EVER on Nintendo Switch™! Featuring cover Superstar Seth Rollins, WWE 2K18 promises to bring you closer to the ring than ever before with hard-hitting action, drama, excitement, new game modes, additional match types, deep creation capabilities, and everything you’ve come to love from WWE 2K. The best part is, the action never stops on Nintendo Switch, and you can enjoy WWE 2K18 at home, on-the-go, anywhere!Most Realistic WWE Video Game Ever!The most realistic WWE video game experience just became more intense with the addition of a new grapple carry system, new weight detection, thousands of new animations and a massive backstage area, bringing the drama of WWE to life like never before!MyCAREERA new MyCAREER experience puts you on the path to greatness as you journey along on the road to WrestleMania. Explore WWE like never before through free-roaming backstage, conversing with WWE Superstars, forming alliances, making enemies, seeking out quests, and strategizing for upcoming matches.Road to GloryCan your MyPlayer make it to the WWE Hall of Fame? Introducing the all-new Road to Glory! Compete with opponents online to improve your MyPlayer by earning unlockables, boosts and upgrades all while securing your entry into special events that are held alongside real-life WWE special events, such as pay-per-views.Dynamic Creation SuiteCustomize WWE like never before with an even deeper set of customization tools and the new Custom Match option! The robust Creation Suite also offers even more detailed features for Create-a-Superstar, Create-a-Video and Create-an-Arena.Seriously, THE BIGGEST ROSTER EVER!Dominate the ring with TONS of your favorite WWE, NXT and legendary Superstars! We’re not kidding, WWE 2K18 offers the most complete roster of the biggest and brightest WWE and NXT Superstars and Legends to ever grace a WWE ring!</desc>
		<image>./images/WWE 2K18-image.png</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/WWE 2K18-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/WWE 2K18-boxback.png</boxback>
		<developer>Yuke's</developer>
		<publisher>2K Games</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<family>WWE 2K</family>
		<players>6</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074356" />
	</game>
	<game id="195865">
		<path>./Games/Xenoblade Chronicles 2.xci</path>
		<name>Xenoblade Chronicles 2</name>
		<desc>Lost in a sea of clouds, entire civilizations rest on the backs of Titans. As the giant beasts march toward death, the last hope is a scavenger named Rex—and Pyra, a living weapon known as a Blade. Can you find the fabled paradise she calls home? Command a group of Blades and lead them to countless strategic victories before the world ends. Each Titan hosts its own distinct cultures, wildlife, and diverse regions to explore. Search the vast open areas and labyrinthine corridors for treasure, secret paths, and creatures to battle and index.

During these escapades you'll get to know a large cast of eclectic characters, including the weaponized life forms known as Blades. Gather these allies, bond with them to increase their power, and utilize their special ARTS to devastate enemies. But to save the world of Alrest, you must first demystify its cloudy past.</desc>
		<image>./images/Xenoblade Chronicles 2-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Xenoblade Chronicles 2-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Xenoblade Chronicles 2-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Xenoblade Chronicles 2-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Xenoblade Chronicles 2-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Xenoblade Chronicles 2-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20171201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Monolith Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<family>Xenoblade</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074358" />
	</game>
	<game id="198143">
		<path>./Games/Xenon Racer.xci</path>
		<name>Xenon Racer</name>
		<desc>In the near future, the official racing federation has ordered a seasons pause from racing, to allow teams to ease into the transition to flying vehicles. To bridge this gap, top hybrid car manufacturers host a rogue championship for rookie drivers on the streets of cities worldwide. Their advanced cars drive on electricity and Xenon gas, resulting in crazy speeds. Get behind the wheel, keep your adrenaline in check and drift through the streets. Boost to absurd speeds and become the ultimate Xenon Racer! Features:Race at top speeds in electric vehicles boosted by Xenon gasDrift through the streets of cities like Tokyo and Dubai in 2030Triumph in singleplayer, split-screen &amp; online multiplayer championshipsCustomize your car with tons of parts to create the ultimate racing vehicle</desc>
		<marquee>./images/Xenon Racer-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Xenon Racer-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/Xenon Racer-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20190326T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>3DClouds.it</developer>
		<publisher>Soedesco</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>8</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074401" />
	</game>
	<game id="359287">
		<path>./Games/Yo-kai Watch 4 PuraPura (Jpn).xci</path>
		<name>Yo-kai Watch 4 PuraPura</name>
		<desc>Yo-kai Watch 4++ is an updated version of Yo-kai Watch 4 with new content for the game, there will be new areas like "Blossom Heights" and “Cauldron-Boiled Hell”, a new Yo-kai to befriend, a new boss and a new multiplayer mode.</desc>
		<marquee>./images/Yo-kai Watch 4 PuraPura (Jpn)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Yo-kai Watch 4 PuraPura (Jpn)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/Yo-kai Watch 4 PuraPura (Jpn)-boxback.png</boxback>
		<genre>Role playing games / Action RPG</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074404" />
	</game>
	<game id="195963">
		<path>./Games/Yooka-Laylee.xci</path>
		<name>Yooka-laylee</name>
		<desc>Explore huge, beautiful worlds, meet (and beat) an unforgettable cast of characters and horde a vault-load of shiny collectibles as buddy-duo Yooka (the green one) and Laylee (the wisecracking bat with the big nose) embark on an epic adventure to thwart corporate creep Capital B and his devious scheme to absorb all the world's books... and convert them into pure profit!

Using their arsenal of special moves, our heroes will tackle a huge variety of puzzles and platforming challenges in their search for Pagies, the golden bounty used to unlock — and expand — stunning new worlds, each jammed to the gills with oddball characters, hulking bosses, minecart challenges, arcade games, quiz shows, multiplayer games... and much more!</desc>
		<image>./images/Yooka-Laylee-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Yooka-Laylee-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Yooka-Laylee-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Yooka-Laylee-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Yooka-Laylee-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20171214T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Playtonic Games</developer>
		<publisher>Team17</publisher>
		<genre>Action / Adventure</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074407" />
	</game>
	<game id="198155">
		<path>./Games/Yoshis Crafted World.xci</path>
		<name>Yoshis Crafted World</name>
		<desc>ump into a new Yoshi adventure in a world made of everyday objects—like boxes and paper cups! As Yoshi, you'll leap up high, gulp down enemies, and set out on a treasure hunt to find all the different collectables. On the flip side, stages can be played backwards, providing new perspectives to explore and new ways to locate some of the more craftily hidden items!

It all started when Kamek and Baby Bowser set out to steal a gem-set stone. Legend has it that this fabled artifact can grant the bearer their wildest dreams! But when the artifact's gems are sent flying, it falls upon Yoshi and friends to find them. Luckily, saving the day can be cooperative and challenging. Pass a Joy-Con™ controller to a friend to team up as fellow Yoshis. Also, Mellow mode gives Yoshi wings for a breezier experience, which may come in handy! Finding all the flowers, coins, and Poochy Pups is no small feat! For extra protection, suit up in one of the handicraft costumes you can unlock in-game or by tapping select amiibo™ figures!</desc>
		<image>./images/Yoshis Crafted World-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Yoshis Crafted World-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Yoshis Crafted World-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Yoshis Crafted World-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Yoshis Crafted World-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Yoshis Crafted World-boxback.png</boxback>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20190329T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Good-Feel</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074409" />
	</game>
	<game id="196147">
		<path>./Games/Ys VIII Lacrimosa of DANA.xci</path>
		<name>Ys VIII: Lacrimosa of DANA</name>
		<desc>Ys returns with a brand new adventure for the first time in 8 years! Adol awakens shipwrecked and stranded on a cursed island. There, he and the other shipwrecked passengers he rescues form a village to challenge fearsome beasts and mysterious ruins on the isolated island. Amidst this, Adol begins to dream of a mysterious blue-haired maiden living in a unknown world. Join Adol as he unravels the riddle of the cursed isle and the blue-haired maiden Dana in Ys VIII: Lacrimosa of Dana!</desc>
		<image>./images/Ys VIII Lacrimosa of DANA-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Ys VIII Lacrimosa of DANA-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Ys VIII Lacrimosa of DANA-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Ys VIII Lacrimosa of DANA-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/Ys VIII Lacrimosa of DANA-boxback.png</boxback>
		<releasedate>20180626T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nihon Falcom</developer>
		<publisher>NIS America</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<family>Ys</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074411" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/ARMS.xci</path>
		<name>ARMS</name>
		<marquee>./images/ARMS-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/ARMS-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/ARMS-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T073327" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Sword Art Online Hollow Realization.xci</path>
		<name>Sword Art Online Hollow Realization</name>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20230301T222557</lastplayed>
		<gametime>47</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074239" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/The Legend of Zelda Skyward Sword HD.xci</path>
		<name>The Legend of Zelda Skyward Sword HD</name>
		<image>./images/The Legend of Zelda Skyward Sword HD-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/The Legend of Zelda Skyward Sword HD-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/The Legend of Zelda Skyward Sword HD-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/The Legend of Zelda Skyward Sword HD-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/The Legend of Zelda Skyward Sword HD-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<boxback>./images/The Legend of Zelda Skyward Sword HD-boxback.png</boxback>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074305" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Timothy vs the Aliens.xci</path>
		<name>Timothy vs the Aliens</name>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074315" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Troll and I PROPER.xci</path>
		<name>Troll and I PROPER</name>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074329" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Windstorm The Game Gold Edition.xci</path>
		<name>Windstorm The Game Gold Edition</name>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20230216T074349" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/13 Sentinels Aegis Rim [01003FC01670C000][v0].nsp</path>
		<name>13 Sentinels Aegis Rim [01003FC01670C000][v0]</name>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T191849" />
	</game>
	<game id="430583">
		<path>./Games/Advance Wars 1 plus 2 Re-Boot Camp [0100300012F2A000][v0][US](nsw2u.com).nsp</path>
		<name>Advance Wars 1+2: Re-Boot Camp</name>
		<desc>Each CO affects your units in different ways, and they each possess a unique ability that can turn the tide of battle. Do you like to go toe-to-toe, or engage from a distance? Choose the CO that best complements your playstyle!</desc>
		<image>./images/Advance Wars 1 plus 2 Re-Boot Camp [0100300012F2A000][v0][US](nsw2u.com)-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Advance Wars 1 plus 2 Re-Boot Camp [0100300012F2A000][v0][US](nsw2u.com)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Advance Wars 1 plus 2 Re-Boot Camp [0100300012F2A000][v0][US](nsw2u.com)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Advance Wars 1 plus 2 Re-Boot Camp [0100300012F2A000][v0][US](nsw2u.com)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Advance Wars 1 plus 2 Re-Boot Camp [0100300012F2A000][v0][US](nsw2u.com)-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20230421T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Wayforward</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<family>Advance Wars</family>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T191920" />
	</game>
	<game id="198229">
		<path>./Games/Assassins Creed III Remastered [NSP + XCI + DLC + Language Packs + Update 1.0.1].xci</path>
		<name>Assassin's Creed 3 Remastered</name>
		<desc>Fight for freedom! As the American Colonies are about to revolt, secure liberty for your people and your nation.</desc>
		<marquee>./images/Assassins Creed III Remastered [NSP + XCI + DLC + Language Packs + Update 1.0.1]-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Assassins Creed III Remastered [NSP + XCI + DLC + Language Packs + Update 1.0.1]-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Assassins Creed III Remastered [NSP + XCI + DLC + Language Packs + Update 1.0.1]-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<releasedate>20190521T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure / RealTime 3D</genre>
		<family>Assassin's Creed</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T191938" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Asterix and Obelix XXL Romastered/Asterix and Obelix XXL Romastered [0100F46011B50800][v196608].nsp</path>
		<name>Asterix and Obelix XXL Romastered [0100F46011B50800][v196608]</name>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T191940" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Asterix and Obelix XXL Romastered [0100F46011B50000][v0].nsp</path>
		<name>Asterix and Obelix XXL Romastered [0100F46011B50000][v0]</name>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T191941" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Astral Chain + Update [NSP]/ASTRAL CHAIN Update [v1.0.1].nsp</path>
		<name>ASTRAL CHAIN Update [v1.0.1]</name>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T191942" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Bayonetta 3.xci</path>
		<name>Bayonetta 3</name>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T191944" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Bubble Bobble 4 Friends (EUR).xci</path>
		<name>Bubble Bobble 4 Friends (EUR)</name>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T191945" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Cats On Streets [0100FA601D2F2000].nsp</path>
		<name>Cats On Streets [0100FA601D2F2000]</name>
		<md5>634a6fd831bec851dc74e5c01f8fe094</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T191949" />
	</game>
	<game id="198331">
		<path>./Games/Crash Team Racing Nitro-Fueled [0100F9F00C696000][v0].xci</path>
		<name>Crash Team Racing Nitro-Fueled</name>
		<desc>Crash is back in the driver's seat! Get ready to go fur-throttle with Crash™ Team Racing Nitro-Fueled. It's the authentic CTR experience plus a whole lot more, now fully-remastered and revved up to the max</desc>
		<image>./images/Crash Team Racing Nitro-Fueled [0100F9F00C696000][v0]-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Crash Team Racing Nitro-Fueled [0100F9F00C696000][v0]-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Crash Team Racing Nitro-Fueled [0100F9F00C696000][v0]-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Crash Team Racing Nitro-Fueled [0100F9F00C696000][v0]-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Crash Team Racing Nitro-Fueled [0100F9F00C696000][v0]-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20190621T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Beenox Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<family>Crash Bandicoot</family>
		<players>1-8</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192021" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Crash Team Racing Nitro-Fueled [NSP + XCI + DLCs + Update 1.0.13]/DLCs/0100f9f00c697001.nsp</path>
		<name>0100f9f00c697001</name>
		<md5>7fb2fb8a6040c5e021ab113e35ed81ce</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192022" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Crash Team Racing Nitro-Fueled [NSP + XCI + DLCs + Update 1.0.13]/DLCs/0100f9f00c697002.nsp</path>
		<name>0100f9f00c697002</name>
		<md5>e693e94dd69c475a39bffcbc7c5b8fdf</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192023" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Crash Team Racing Nitro-Fueled [NSP + XCI + DLCs + Update 1.0.13]/DLCs/0100f9f00c697003.nsp</path>
		<name>0100f9f00c697003</name>
		<md5>f9e9ae56af27a1b2715e740f49f912b7</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192024" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Crash_Bandicoot_4_Its_About_Time_NSW-VENOM/Crash_Bandicoot_4_Its_About_Time_NSW-VENOM totally_tubular_skins_dlc_010073401175f001.nsp</path>
		<name>Crash_Bandicoot_4_Its_About_Time_NSW-VENOM totally_tubular_skins_dlc_010073401175f001</name>
		<md5>2830757712e5fcf3e26a6ad1f420afc0</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192026" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Crash_Bandicoot_4_Its_About_Time_NSW-VENOM/Crash_Bandicoot_4_Its_About_Time_NSW-VENOM tubular_skins_dlc_010073401175f002.nsp</path>
		<name>Crash_Bandicoot_4_Its_About_Time_NSW-VENOM tubular_skins_dlc_010073401175f002</name>
		<md5>137f0376260ae0b1b4b99e6106e43ac3</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192027" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Crash_Bandicoot_4_Its_About_Time_NSW-VENOM/Crash_Bandicoot_4_Its_About_Time_NSW-VENOM Update v65536.nsp</path>
		<name>Crash_Bandicoot_4_Its_About_Time_NSW-VENOM Update v65536</name>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192028" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Crash_Bandicoot_4_Its_About_Time_NSW-VENOM.nsp</path>
		<name>Crash_Bandicoot_4_Its_About_Time_NSW-VENOM</name>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192029" />
	</game>
	<game id="359576">
		<path>./Games/Darksiders Genesis [NXP + XCI + Update 1.0.1]/Darksiders Genesis[0100F2300D4BA800][US][v65536][Non Patched][Req FW 9.1.0].nsp</path>
		<name>Darksiders: Genesis</name>
		<desc>DARKSIDERS GENESIS is an action/adventure that tears its way through Hell and back with guns blazing and swords swinging. Genesis gives players their first look at the world of DARKSIDERS before the events of the original game. Furthermore, it introduces the fourth and last horseman STRIFE, as well as Co-op gameplay for the first time in the history of the franchise.</desc>
		<image>./images/Darksiders Genesis[0100F2300D4BA800][US][v65536][Non Patched][Req FW 9.1.0]-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Darksiders Genesis[0100F2300D4BA800][US][v65536][Non Patched][Req FW 9.1.0]-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Darksiders Genesis[0100F2300D4BA800][US][v65536][Non Patched][Req FW 9.1.0]-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Darksiders Genesis[0100F2300D4BA800][US][v65536][Non Patched][Req FW 9.1.0]-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20200214T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Airship Syndicate</developer>
		<publisher>THQ Nordic</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure / RealTime 3D</genre>
		<family>Darksiders</family>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<md5>5551198a3c2ea087adec149235db4b9d</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192053" />
	</game>
	<game id="359576">
		<path>./Games/Darksiders Genesis [NXP + XCI + Update 1.0.1]/Darksiders Genesis[0100F2300D4BA800][US][v65536][Patched FW 9.0.1].nsp</path>
		<name>Darksiders: Genesis</name>
		<desc>DARKSIDERS GENESIS is an action/adventure that tears its way through Hell and back with guns blazing and swords swinging. Genesis gives players their first look at the world of DARKSIDERS before the events of the original game. Furthermore, it introduces the fourth and last horseman STRIFE, as well as Co-op gameplay for the first time in the history of the franchise.</desc>
		<image>./images/Darksiders Genesis[0100F2300D4BA800][US][v65536][Patched FW 9.0.1]-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Darksiders Genesis[0100F2300D4BA800][US][v65536][Patched FW 9.0.1]-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Darksiders Genesis[0100F2300D4BA800][US][v65536][Patched FW 9.0.1]-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Darksiders Genesis[0100F2300D4BA800][US][v65536][Patched FW 9.0.1]-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20200214T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Airship Syndicate</developer>
		<publisher>THQ Nordic</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure / RealTime 3D</genre>
		<family>Darksiders</family>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<md5>40755007ebf849f56a0a2f9148b55070</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192119" />
	</game>
	<game id="359576">
		<path>./Games/Darksiders Genesis[0100F2300D4BA000][US][v0].xci</path>
		<name>Darksiders: Genesis</name>
		<desc>DARKSIDERS GENESIS is an action/adventure that tears its way through Hell and back with guns blazing and swords swinging. Genesis gives players their first look at the world of DARKSIDERS before the events of the original game. Furthermore, it introduces the fourth and last horseman STRIFE, as well as Co-op gameplay for the first time in the history of the franchise.</desc>
		<image>./images/Darksiders Genesis[0100F2300D4BA000][US][v0]-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Darksiders Genesis[0100F2300D4BA000][US][v0]-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Darksiders Genesis[0100F2300D4BA000][US][v0]-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Darksiders Genesis[0100F2300D4BA000][US][v0]-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20200214T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Airship Syndicate</developer>
		<publisher>THQ Nordic</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure / RealTime 3D</genre>
		<family>Darksiders</family>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192143" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/DEAD OR ALIVE Xtreme 3 Scarlet [NSP + Update +  XCI + DLCs]/All DLCs/01009cc00c97d001.nsp</path>
		<name>01009cc00c97d001</name>
		<md5>c793ab2ae1d71245e95055663d4468c8</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192145" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/DEAD OR ALIVE Xtreme 3 Scarlet [NSP + Update +  XCI + DLCs]/All DLCs/01009cc00c97d002.nsp</path>
		<name>01009cc00c97d002</name>
		<md5>e990b75bda6c8ba7f90e3f061506d152</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192147" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/DEAD OR ALIVE Xtreme 3 Scarlet [NSP + Update +  XCI + DLCs]/All DLCs/01009cc00c97d003.nsp</path>
		<name>01009cc00c97d003</name>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192148" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/DEAD OR ALIVE Xtreme 3 Scarlet [NSP + Update +  XCI + DLCs]/All DLCs/01009cc00c97d004.nsp</path>
		<name>01009cc00c97d004</name>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192149" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/DEAD OR ALIVE Xtreme 3 Scarlet [NSP + Update +  XCI + DLCs]/All DLCs/01009cc00c97d005.nsp</path>
		<name>01009cc00c97d005</name>
		<md5>3e6b2f1bb6f4b55936e05c779e8429f9</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192151" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/DEAD OR ALIVE Xtreme 3 Scarlet [NSP + Update +  XCI + DLCs]/All DLCs/01009cc00c97d006.nsp</path>
		<name>01009cc00c97d006</name>
		<md5>6dce163dca3b72015646e64d8d7f192b</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192152" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/DEAD OR ALIVE Xtreme 3 Scarlet [NSP + Update +  XCI + DLCs]/All DLCs/01009cc00c97d007.nsp</path>
		<name>01009cc00c97d007</name>
		<md5>1a6c2aed7e05268bd1f5a1d8e8eef34a</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192154" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/DEAD OR ALIVE Xtreme 3 Scarlet [NSP + Update +  XCI + DLCs]/All DLCs/01009cc00c97d008.nsp</path>
		<name>01009cc00c97d008</name>
		<md5>c826a94789d952572dee55475ab9926d</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192155" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/DEAD OR ALIVE Xtreme 3 Scarlet [NSP + Update +  XCI + DLCs]/All DLCs/01009cc00c97d009.nsp</path>
		<name>01009cc00c97d009</name>
		<md5>99c5c0444132aeb310a3e34d25de5118</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192156" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/DEAD OR ALIVE Xtreme 3 Scarlet [NSP + Update +  XCI + DLCs]/All DLCs/01009cc00c97d00a.nsp</path>
		<name>01009cc00c97d00a</name>
		<md5>a4a85b9658b53db4805e38a271c869ff</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192158" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/DEAD OR ALIVE Xtreme 3 Scarlet [NSP + Update +  XCI + DLCs]/All DLCs/01009cc00c97d00b.nsp</path>
		<name>01009cc00c97d00b</name>
		<md5>6bb584886a54145161aaaa3857232ace</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192159" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/DEAD OR ALIVE Xtreme 3 Scarlet [NSP + Update +  XCI + DLCs]/All DLCs/01009cc00c97d00c.nsp</path>
		<name>01009cc00c97d00c</name>
		<md5>d0330b4ef55e79372de6b285b5091c00</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192201" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/DEAD OR ALIVE Xtreme 3 Scarlet [NSP + Update +  XCI + DLCs]/All DLCs/01009cc00c97d00d.nsp</path>
		<name>01009cc00c97d00d</name>
		<md5>bcdbdfd01cd51e625e97e15d0bbf5f3b</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192202" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/DEAD OR ALIVE Xtreme 3 Scarlet [NSP + Update +  XCI + DLCs]/All DLCs/01009cc00c97d010.nsp</path>
		<name>01009cc00c97d010</name>
		<md5>d67383d5918a646a4319c1e349130a45</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192204" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/DEAD OR ALIVE Xtreme 3 Scarlet [NSP + Update +  XCI + DLCs]/All DLCs/01009cc00c97d011.nsp</path>
		<name>01009cc00c97d011</name>
		<md5>b49eea733a8b99de5b6b914a998efaa7</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192205" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/DEAD OR ALIVE Xtreme 3 Scarlet [NSP + Update +  XCI + DLCs]/All DLCs/01009cc00c97d012.nsp</path>
		<name>01009cc00c97d012</name>
		<md5>608eac1455c454b09a695f25212ce9b4</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192207" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/DEAD OR ALIVE Xtreme 3 Scarlet [NSP + Update +  XCI + DLCs]/All DLCs/01009cc00c97d013.nsp</path>
		<name>01009cc00c97d013</name>
		<md5>f8a20c2383565cd29315d4664a083e74</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192209" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/DEAD OR ALIVE Xtreme 3 Scarlet [NSP + Update +  XCI + DLCs]/All DLCs/01009cc00c97d014.nsp</path>
		<name>01009cc00c97d014</name>
		<md5>227969e5a96fbc91094e2ab6a81a1950</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192210" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/DEAD OR ALIVE Xtreme 3 Scarlet [NSP + Update +  XCI + DLCs]/All DLCs/01009cc00c97d015.nsp</path>
		<name>01009cc00c97d015</name>
		<md5>f68ea0021436aa6acc17513365e4b9aa</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192212" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/DEAD OR ALIVE Xtreme 3 Scarlet [NSP + Update +  XCI + DLCs]/All DLCs/01009cc00c97d016.nsp</path>
		<name>01009cc00c97d016</name>
		<md5>e9d51dd4cb0df99135e5708380cddfaf</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192213" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/DEAD OR ALIVE Xtreme 3 Scarlet [NSP + Update +  XCI + DLCs]/All DLCs/01009cc00c97d017.nsp</path>
		<name>01009cc00c97d017</name>
		<md5>4c7c96aa5614d97c542fa2287283d392</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192215" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/DEAD OR ALIVE Xtreme 3 Scarlet [NSP + Update +  XCI + DLCs]/All DLCs/01009cc00c97d018.nsp</path>
		<name>01009cc00c97d018</name>
		<md5>608f97e7a7148504e6bbdedf57fff537</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192216" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/DEAD OR ALIVE Xtreme 3 Scarlet [NSP + Update +  XCI + DLCs]/All DLCs/01009cc00c97d019.nsp</path>
		<name>01009cc00c97d019</name>
		<md5>b5c0c8ab16ba5fe4ba563076c219a78b</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192218" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/DEAD OR ALIVE Xtreme 3 Scarlet [NSP + Update +  XCI + DLCs]/All DLCs/01009cc00c97d01a.nsp</path>
		<name>01009cc00c97d01a</name>
		<md5>f7d4032597a0e70fc6cea4c8273142eb</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192220" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/DEAD OR ALIVE Xtreme 3 Scarlet [NSP + Update +  XCI + DLCs]/All DLCs/01009cc00c97d01b.nsp</path>
		<name>01009cc00c97d01b</name>
		<md5>32c6a95abf4c4fd19b7e917bd8d93f8f</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192221" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/DEAD OR ALIVE Xtreme 3 Scarlet [NSP + Update +  XCI + DLCs]/All DLCs/01009cc00c97d01c.nsp</path>
		<name>01009cc00c97d01c</name>
		<md5>1a2f313b9a1a8387cebbebc161fc99ec</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192223" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/DEAD OR ALIVE Xtreme 3 Scarlet [NSP + Update +  XCI + DLCs]/All DLCs/01009cc00c97d01d.nsp</path>
		<name>01009cc00c97d01d</name>
		<md5>73f1bc8c1a35d56a67fe7ebbbe9c31f7</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192224" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/DEAD OR ALIVE Xtreme 3 Scarlet [NSP + Update +  XCI + DLCs]/All DLCs/01009cc00c97d01e.nsp</path>
		<name>01009cc00c97d01e</name>
		<md5>77e3455ea6ccb1d8d187af54e887b507</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192225" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/DEAD OR ALIVE Xtreme 3 Scarlet [NSP + Update +  XCI + DLCs]/All DLCs/01009cc00c97d01f.nsp</path>
		<name>01009cc00c97d01f</name>
		<md5>c8548060d9d091ada92b76195a66ea78</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192226" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/DEAD OR ALIVE Xtreme 3 Scarlet [NSP + Update +  XCI + DLCs]/All DLCs/01009cc00c97d020.nsp</path>
		<name>01009cc00c97d020</name>
		<md5>d06ce2dc6cc23a05c2bbc66399c99166</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192228" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/DEAD OR ALIVE Xtreme 3 Scarlet [NSP + Update +  XCI + DLCs]/All DLCs/01009cc00c97d021.nsp</path>
		<name>01009cc00c97d021</name>
		<md5>06a23551a51015576569066ce79f966e</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192229" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/DEAD OR ALIVE Xtreme 3 Scarlet [NSP + Update +  XCI + DLCs]/All DLCs/01009cc00c97d022.nsp</path>
		<name>01009cc00c97d022</name>
		<md5>e114995191b43dc5e0ef1893dc969f49</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192231" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/DEAD OR ALIVE Xtreme 3 Scarlet [NSP + Update +  XCI + DLCs]/All DLCs/01009cc00c97d023.nsp</path>
		<name>01009cc00c97d023</name>
		<md5>c9d7710f451a87efcdfdb52e383183fa</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192232" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/DEAD OR ALIVE Xtreme 3 Scarlet [NSP + Update +  XCI + DLCs]/All DLCs/01009cc00c97d024.nsp</path>
		<name>01009cc00c97d024</name>
		<md5>3e67f4d2b81cd562fd15e42cb64fd303</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192234" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/DEAD OR ALIVE Xtreme 3 Scarlet [NSP + Update +  XCI + DLCs]/All DLCs/01009cc00c97d025.nsp</path>
		<name>01009cc00c97d025</name>
		<md5>dda7fa5b61f4abcd749f9827896d6708</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192235" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/DEAD OR ALIVE Xtreme 3 Scarlet [NSP + Update +  XCI + DLCs]/All DLCs/01009cc00c97d02f.nsp</path>
		<name>01009cc00c97d02f</name>
		<md5>ec1140e6a07e82154a1a39669ab1c31c</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192237" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/DEAD OR ALIVE Xtreme 3 Scarlet [NSP + Update +  XCI + DLCs]/All DLCs/01009cc00c97d030.nsp</path>
		<name>01009cc00c97d030</name>
		<md5>4548531e518847a98e255a3d99cd847f</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192238" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/DEAD OR ALIVE Xtreme 3 Scarlet [NSP + Update +  XCI + DLCs]/All DLCs/01009cc00c97d031.nsp</path>
		<name>01009cc00c97d031</name>
		<md5>53add93aac580615b7cd891d2b0aa9e9</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192239" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/DEAD OR ALIVE Xtreme 3 Scarlet [NSP + Update +  XCI + DLCs]/All DLCs/01009cc00c97d032.nsp</path>
		<name>01009cc00c97d032</name>
		<md5>d2df98037340045a94d5806af0fc1142</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192241" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/DEAD OR ALIVE Xtreme 3 Scarlet [NSP + Update +  XCI + DLCs]/All DLCs/01009cc00c97d033.nsp</path>
		<name>01009cc00c97d033</name>
		<md5>3072a6ef4c58ae74a25cfd1e3b6399b2</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192242" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/DEAD OR ALIVE Xtreme 3 Scarlet [NSP + Update +  XCI + DLCs]/All DLCs/01009cc00c97d034.nsp</path>
		<name>01009cc00c97d034</name>
		<md5>aeaba77c34862634afdfbce1be08e4a7</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192244" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/DEAD OR ALIVE Xtreme 3 Scarlet [NSP + Update +  XCI + DLCs]/All DLCs/01009cc00c97d035.nsp</path>
		<name>01009cc00c97d035</name>
		<md5>afe1708c2b3da987e278d052d6926591</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192245" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/DEAD OR ALIVE Xtreme 3 Scarlet [NSP + Update +  XCI + DLCs]/All DLCs/01009cc00c97d036.nsp</path>
		<name>01009cc00c97d036</name>
		<md5>5e13f31bffbf16dce4726cde77356d93</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192247" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/DEAD OR ALIVE Xtreme 3 Scarlet [NSP + Update +  XCI + DLCs]/All DLCs/01009cc00c97d037.nsp</path>
		<name>01009cc00c97d037</name>
		<md5>12a5913cee9ee56f1a8f512e067fde65</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192248" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/DEAD OR ALIVE Xtreme 3 Scarlet 基本無料版[01009CC00C97C800].xci</path>
		<name>DEAD OR ALIVE Xtreme 3 Scarlet 基本無料版[01009CC00C97C800]</name>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192250" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Highway Moto Racing Rush 2023 - Simulator [01002F801BEA8000].nsp</path>
		<name>Highway Moto Racing Rush 2023 - Simulator [01002F801BEA8000]</name>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192251" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Little Nightmares Complete Edition [NSP + Update 1.0.2 + 2 DLCs]/Little Nightmares Complete Edition [Little Nightmares - Fox Mask] [01002FC00412D001][v0].nsp</path>
		<name>Little Nightmares Complete Edition [Little Nightmares - Fox Mask] [01002FC00412D001][v0]</name>
		<md5>147ceee2582e5a207c3beea33c11e8cc</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192253" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Little Nightmares Complete Edition [NSP + Update 1.0.2 + 2 DLCs]/Little Nightmares Complete Edition [Little Nightmares - Tengu Mask] [01002FC00412D002][v0].nsp</path>
		<name>Little Nightmares Complete Edition [Little Nightmares - Tengu Mask] [01002FC00412D002][v0]</name>
		<md5>83d0e8c23d52a3b807c1f3033b4232f8</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192255" />
	</game>
	<game id="198375">
		<path>./Games/MARVEL ULTIMATE ALLIANCE 3 The Black Order [010060700AC50000][v262144] (1G+1U+1D).xci</path>
		<name>Marvel Ultimate Alliance 3 The Black Order</name>
		<desc>In this new storyline, heroes and villains unite in a race across the Marvel Universe to find the Infinity Stones before Thanos and The Black Order use them to unleash cosmic chaos. From Avengers Tower to the X-Mansion and beyond, every stop on the dangerous quest to thwart Thanos results in unexpected collisions of fan-favorite characters and iconic locations.</desc>
		<image>./images/MARVEL ULTIMATE ALLIANCE 3 The Black Order [010060700AC50000][v262144] (1G+1U+1D)-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/MARVEL ULTIMATE ALLIANCE 3 The Black Order [010060700AC50000][v262144] (1G+1U+1D)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/MARVEL ULTIMATE ALLIANCE 3 The Black Order [010060700AC50000][v262144] (1G+1U+1D)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/MARVEL ULTIMATE ALLIANCE 3 The Black Order [010060700AC50000][v262144] (1G+1U+1D)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/MARVEL ULTIMATE ALLIANCE 3 The Black Order [010060700AC50000][v262144] (1G+1U+1D)-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20190719T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Koei</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<family>Marvel</family>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192326" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Mega Man Zero ZX - Legacy Collection (USA) [XCI + UPDATE]/v-mega_man_zero_zx_legacy_collection_v196608.nsp</path>
		<name>v-mega_man_zero_zx_legacy_collection_v196608</name>
		<md5>dba9fc5483b301e1c994890a767d490c</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192331" />
	</game>
	<game id="359774">
		<path>./Games/Mega Man Zero ZX - Legacy Collection (USA).xci</path>
		<name>Mega Man Zero/ZX Legacy Collection</name>
		<desc>Mega Man Zero/ZX Legacy Collection brings together six classic titles in one game: Mega Man Zero 1, 2, 3, and 4, as well as Mega Man ZX and ZX Advent.In addition to the original games, Casual Scenario Mode and a Save-Assist feature are available for those who would like to enjoy the story at their own pace. Players can also try their hand at the new leaderboard-based Z Chaser Mode, an exclusive new mode created just for this set of games</desc>
		<image>./images/Mega Man Zero ZX - Legacy Collection (USA)-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Mega Man Zero ZX - Legacy Collection (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Mega Man Zero ZX - Legacy Collection (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Mega Man Zero ZX - Legacy Collection (USA)-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20200225T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Compilation</genre>
		<family>Mega Man</family>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192355" />
	</game>
	<game id="359773">
		<path>./Games/Metro Redux (EUR) [XCI].xci</path>
		<name>Metro Redux</name>
		<desc>In 2013 the world was devastated by an apocalyptic event, annihilating almost all mankind and turning the earth’s surface into a poisonous wasteland. A handful of survivors took refuge in the depths of the Moscow underground, and human civilization entered a new Dark Age.The year is 2033. An entire generation has been born and raised underground, and their besieged Metro Station-Cities struggle for survival, with each other, and the mutant horrors that await outside.You are Artyom, born in the last days before the fire, but raised underground. Having never ventured beyond the city limits, one fateful event sparks a desperate mission to the heart of the Metro system, to warn the remnants of mankind of a terrible impending threat.But will they even listen? Rather than stand united, the factions of the Metro are locked in a struggle for the ultimate power, a doomsday device from the military vaults of D6. A civil war is stirring that could wipe humanity from the face of the earth forever.Including the epic single-player campaigns of both Metro 2033 and Metro: Last Light, Metro Redux takes you on a journey from the forgotten catacombs beneath the subway to the desolate wastelands above, where your actions will determine the fate of mankind.Metro Redux is the ultimate double game collection, including the definitive versions of both Metro 2033 and Metro: Last Light, now available on Nintendo Switch™Newcomers to the series will get the chance to experience two of the finest story-driven shooters of all time in one vast package; an epic adventure combining gripping survival horror, exploration and tactical combat and stealth.Those who favoured the more survival-horror oriented gameplay of ‘Metro 2033’ can play both campaigns in the ‘Survival’ Play-Style, a fraught, slow burn fight for survival. Those who enjoyed the more action-oriented gameplay of ‘Metro: Last Light’ can try the ‘Spartan’ Play-Style, providing Artyom with a powerful set of combat skills.With the legendary Ranger Mode included to offer an extra layer of challenge and immersion, and all previous released DLC, Metro Redux offers 50+ hours of AAA FPS gameplay for an incredible price.</desc>
		<image>./images/Metro Redux (EUR) [XCI]-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Metro Redux (EUR) [XCI]-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Metro Redux (EUR) [XCI]-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>20200228T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>4A Games</developer>
		<publisher>Deep Silver</publisher>
		<genre>Compilation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192414" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/MONSTER_HUNTER_RISE_NSW-VENOM/v-monster_hunter_rise_v131072.nsp</path>
		<name>v-monster_hunter_rise_v131072</name>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192415" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/MONSTER_HUNTER_RISE_NSW-VENOM.xci</path>
		<name>MONSTER_HUNTER_RISE_NSW-VENOM</name>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192416" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Overcooked_All_You_Can_Eat_NSW-NiiNTENDO/n-overcookedayce_v131072.nsp</path>
		<name>n-overcookedayce_v131072</name>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192417" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Overcooked_All_You_Can_Eat_NSW-NiiNTENDO.xci</path>
		<name>Overcooked_All_You_Can_Eat_NSW-NiiNTENDO</name>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192419" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Party Party Time (JPN) (En,Ja,Ko,Cht) [0100C6A019C84000]/Party Party Time (JPN) (En,Ja,Ko,Cht) (DLC - Thrilling Party Pack) [0100C6A019C85008]/hr-bd8qh-tpp-dlc.nsp</path>
		<name>hr-bd8qh-tpp-dlc</name>
		<md5>e06be56264a507b1b2069c57d1a8104c</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192421" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Party Party Time (JPN) (En,Ja,Ko,Cht) [0100C6A019C84000]/Party Party Time (JPN) (En,Ja,Ko,Cht) (Update v1.0.13) [0100C6A019C84800]/hr-bd8qhv851968.nsp</path>
		<name>hr-bd8qhv851968</name>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192423" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Party Party Time (JPN) (En,Ja,Ko,Cht) [0100C6A019C84000].xci</path>
		<name>Party Party Time (JPN) (En,Ja,Ko,Cht) [0100C6A019C84000]</name>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192424" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Plants_vs._Zombies_Battle_for_Neighborville_Complete_Edition_NSW-HR/hr-axb3av131072.nsp</path>
		<name>hr-axb3av131072</name>
		<md5>84520d8a1c5e8b49a4faeb3c28a63d5b</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192427" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Plants_vs._Zombies_Battle_for_Neighborville_Complete_Edition_NSW-HR.xci</path>
		<name>Plants_vs._Zombies_Battle_for_Neighborville_Complete_Edition_NSW-HR</name>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192428" />
	</game>
	<game id="359653">
		<path>./Games/Pokemon Mystery Dungeon Rescue Team DX + Update [NSP]/Pokemon Mystery Dungeon Rescue Team DX[01003D200BAA2800][US][v65536].nsp</path>
		<name>Pokémon Mystery Dungeon: Rescue Team DX</name>
		<desc>What if you woke up one day, and you were a Pokémon? You can meet and recruit Pokémon in a dungeon-crawling adventure within their world! Build a rescue team to take on mysterious, changing dungeons and strategically plan your moves as you venture forth to make the Pokémon world a safer place…and uncover your true purpose along the way.As you recruit Pokémon, these trusty teammates will need somewhere to stay, so build rescue team camps to house, manage, and strengthen your Pokémon friends. Think hard about who is right for the job and how to approach each mysterious dungeon as you prepare a rescue team. You’ll move a single square at a time or use Auto mode to speed up movement until you engage other Pokémon in turn-based battles—but don’t forget about Pokémon strengths, weaknesses and potential rare qualities! This version adds Mega Evolved Pokémon, gorgeous watercolor-inspired graphics, and more! Get comfortable in your Pokémon form, there’s a lot of work to do.</desc>
		<image>./images/Pokemon Mystery Dungeon Rescue Team DX[01003D200BAA2800][US][v65536]-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Pokemon Mystery Dungeon Rescue Team DX[01003D200BAA2800][US][v65536]-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Pokemon Mystery Dungeon Rescue Team DX[01003D200BAA2800][US][v65536]-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Pokemon Mystery Dungeon Rescue Team DX[01003D200BAA2800][US][v65536]-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20200306T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<family>Pokémon</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>9362b50915b1027e2e64d3dca09887ed</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192455" />
	</game>
	<game id="359649">
		<path>./Games/Pokemon Shield [World] [En,Fr,It,Pt,De,Es,Zh,Tw] [01008DB008C2C000][v0].xci</path>
		<name>Pokémon Shield</name>
		<desc>A new generation of Pokémon is coming to the Nintendo Switch™ system. Begin your adventure as a Pokémon Trainer by choosing one of three new partner Pokémon: Grookey, Scorbunny, or Sobble. Then embark on a journey in the new Galar region, where you'll challenge the troublemakers of Team Yell, while unraveling the mystery behind the Legendary Pokémon Zacian and Zamazenta! Explore the Wild Area, a vast expanse of land where the player can freely control the camera.</desc>
		<image>./images/Pokemon Shield [World] [En,Fr,It,Pt,De,Es,Zh,Tw] [01008DB008C2C000][v0]-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Pokemon Shield [World] [En,Fr,It,Pt,De,Es,Zh,Tw] [01008DB008C2C000][v0]-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Pokemon Shield [World] [En,Fr,It,Pt,De,Es,Zh,Tw] [01008DB008C2C000][v0]-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Pokemon Shield [World] [En,Fr,It,Pt,De,Es,Zh,Tw] [01008DB008C2C000][v0]-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Pokemon Shield [World] [En,Fr,It,Pt,De,Es,Zh,Tw] [01008DB008C2C000][v0]-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20191115T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games / Action RPG</genre>
		<family>Pokémon</family>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>de,en,es,pt,fr,it,cn</lang>
		<region>cn</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192524" />
	</game>
	<game id="359559">
		<path>./Games/SAMURAI SHODOWN [Japan] [En,Ja,Zh] [01008FC00D964000].xci</path>
		<name>Samurai Shodown</name>
		<desc>SAMURAI SHODOWN has enjoyed worldwide success as a blade-wielding fighting game series since its first release in 1993. 11 years have passed since the last series installment, and it is now time for SAMURAI SHODOWN to return in a brand-new game featuring high-end visuals and gameplay! Faithfully reproducing the game mechanics and atmosphere that contributed to the success of the series, SAMURAI SHODOWN includes a revolutionary feature that learns players' game actions and patterns in order to create CPU-controlled “ghost” characters. With its story set one year before the very first installment, warriors and combatants from various backgrounds and with their own goals are about to battle to fulfill their destinies!</desc>
		<image>./images/SAMURAI SHODOWN [Japan] [En,Ja,Zh] [01008FC00D964000]-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/SAMURAI SHODOWN [Japan] [En,Ja,Zh] [01008FC00D964000]-video.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail>./images/SAMURAI SHODOWN [Japan] [En,Ja,Zh] [01008FC00D964000]-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/SAMURAI SHODOWN [Japan] [En,Ja,Zh] [01008FC00D964000]-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20200225T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / Versus</genre>
		<family>Samurai Shodown</family>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>jp,en</lang>
		<region>jp</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192549" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/SEGA Mega Drive Classics (EUR) [XCI + UPDATES x 2]/v-segamdc_v131072.nsp</path>
		<name>v-segamdc_v131072</name>
		<md5>d538eb0c747576642b66e8061eac75cf</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192551" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/SEGA Mega Drive Classics (EUR) [XCI + UPDATES x 2]/v-segamdc_v65536.nsp</path>
		<name>v-segamdc_v65536</name>
		<md5>02d8eb6ef1486f6f7ca652c187ec4244</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192554" />
	</game>
	<game id="197923">
		<path>./Games/SEGA Mega Drive Classics (EUR).xci</path>
		<name>Sega Mega Drive Classics</name>
		<desc>Including over 50 titles across all genres, from all-time classics like Sonic and Streets of Rage 2 to deep RPGs like the Phantasy Star series; arcade action, shooters, beat'm ups, puzzles, old favorites and hidden gems. There is a classic title for every player to enjoy!

New features also bring modern convenience to the classics. Save your game at any time, rewind those slip-ups, or customize your controls. Earn bragging rights with online multiplayer and achievements.</desc>
		<image>./images/SEGA Mega Drive Classics (EUR)-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/SEGA Mega Drive Classics (EUR)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/SEGA Mega Drive Classics (EUR)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/SEGA Mega Drive Classics (EUR)-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<releasedate>20181207T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192618" />
	</game>
	<game id="427892">
		<path>./Games/STAR WARS Jedi Knight II Jedi Outcast [0100BB500EACA000][v131072] (1G+1U).xci</path>
		<name>Star Wars Jedi Knight II: Jedi Outcast</name>
		<thumbnail>./images/STAR WARS Jedi Knight II Jedi Outcast [0100BB500EACA000][v131072] (1G+1U)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>20201110T000000</releasedate>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192625" />
	</game>
	<game id="359426">
		<path>./Games/Super Mario 3D World + Bowsers Fury [Rev 1.0.0] (USA) (Update_v1.1.0).nsp</path>
		<name>Super Mario 3D World + Bowser's Fury</name>
		<desc>Power up, team up, one up to save the Sprixie Kingdom! Pounce and climb through dozens of colorful courses! Mario (and his friends) can use a variety of power-ups like the Super Bell, which grants catlike abilities like climbing and scratching. Team up with up to three other players locally* or online** to reach the goal and see who can get a high score. Explore a seamless feline world in the new Bowser's Fury adventure: Free-roaming Super Mario gameplay makes a return in this brand-new adventure. Bowser has become gargantuan and lost all control! Explore Lake Lapcat and its islands, complete objectives to collect Cat Shines, and team up with Bowser Jr. to bring his big, bad dad back to normal. Just watch out for Bowser's island-wide attacks.</desc>
		<image>./images/Super Mario 3D World + Bowsers Fury [Rev 1.0.0] (USA) (Update_v1.1.0)-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Super Mario 3D World + Bowsers Fury [Rev 1.0.0] (USA) (Update_v1.1.0)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Super Mario 3D World + Bowsers Fury [Rev 1.0.0] (USA) (Update_v1.1.0)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Super Mario 3D World + Bowsers Fury [Rev 1.0.0] (USA) (Update_v1.1.0)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20210212T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action / Adventure</genre>
		<family>Super Mario Bros</family>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<md5>220c94d4c03cd1b4fc6429da8d67f459</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192651" />
	</game>
	<game id="433543">
		<path>./Games/Super Mario Bros. Wonder [010015100B514000][v0][US].xci</path>
		<name>Super Mario Bros. Wonder</name>
		<desc>Find wonder in the next evolution of Mario funClassic Mario side-scrolling gameplay is turned on its head with the addition of Wonder Flowers. These game-changing items trigger spectacular moments you have to see to believe...Witness pipes coming alive, wreak havoc as a giant spiky ball, and see even more unexpected events called Wonder Effects.Pick from heroic Super Mario™ characters and Power-UpsChoose from familiar characters including Mario, Luigi, Peach, Daisy, Yoshi and Toad. Transform into Elephant Mario to use your trunk to trounce enemies with a surprising new Power-Up!Share the wonder with friends and Mario fansTeam up with up to three friends locally* and gather around one Nintendo Switch™ system to experience the game-bending Wonder Effects together as you tackle courses as a team and help each other on your way to the goal.</desc>
		<image>./images/Super Mario Bros. Wonder [010015100B514000][v0][US]-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Super Mario Bros. Wonder [010015100B514000][v0][US]-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Super Mario Bros. Wonder [010015100B514000][v0][US]-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Super Mario Bros. Wonder [010015100B514000][v0][US]-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Super Mario Bros. Wonder [010015100B514000][v0][US]-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<releasedate>20231020T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform / Run Jump</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192722" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Super Mario RPG [0100BC0018138000][v0].nsp</path>
		<name>Super Mario RPG [0100BC0018138000][v0]</name>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192723" />
	</game>
	<game id="359421">
		<path>./Games/Super Robot Wars X [Asia] [Ja,En,Ko,Tw] [010026800E304000].xci</path>
		<name>Super Robot Wars X</name>
		<desc>The fates of warriors X-cross once again in a new world.

The latest in the Super Robot Wars series! Super Robot Wars X tells the story of super robots who get sucked into a strange new world. This scenario-based story concludes within this game.

In addition to titles making their debut in the Super Robot Wars series like Gundam Reconguista in G, Buddy Complex, and Mashin Hero Wataru, titles that surpass the mecha genre like Nadia: The Secret of Blue Water also make an appearance.

Witness the battles unfold in this dazzling new world!</desc>
		<image>./images/Super Robot Wars X [Asia] [Ja,En,Ko,Tw] [010026800E304000]-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Super Robot Wars X [Asia] [Ja,En,Ko,Tw] [010026800E304000]-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Super Robot Wars X [Asia] [Ja,En,Ko,Tw] [010026800E304000]-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Super Robot Wars X [Asia] [Ja,En,Ko,Tw] [010026800E304000]-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20200110T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>B.B. Studio</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<family>Super Robot Wars</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>jp,en,cn</lang>
		<region>cn</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192747" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Super_Smash_Bros_Ultimate/Super_Smash_Bros_Ultimate_Update_v11.0.0_NSW-VENOM.nsp</path>
		<name>Super_Smash_Bros_Ultimate_Update_v11.0.0_NSW-VENOM</name>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192748" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Super_Smash_Bros_Ultimate/v-ssbu_arthur_01006a800016f048.nsp</path>
		<name>v-ssbu_arthur_01006a800016f048</name>
		<md5>f0fa305ac6560bee49cfc68386fad92c</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192750" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Super_Smash_Bros_Ultimate/v-ssbu_felyne_01006a800016f049.nsp</path>
		<name>v-ssbu_felyne_01006a800016f049</name>
		<md5>44822116b9852c84456dbd766d579c93</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192751" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Super_Smash_Bros_Ultimate/v-ssbu_hunters_01006a800016f04a.nsp</path>
		<name>v-ssbu_hunters_01006a800016f04a</name>
		<md5>7f481c8cac9167840e158c221f04dbfd</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192753" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Super_Smash_Bros_Ultimate/v-ssbu_rathalos_01006a800016f04b.nsp</path>
		<name>v-ssbu_rathalos_01006a800016f04b</name>
		<md5>affea66addb54d7f85f2a5e17d5dfa91</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192754" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Super_Smash_Bros_Ultimate/v-ssbu_ultimate_spirits_set_01006a800016f083.nsp</path>
		<name>v-ssbu_ultimate_spirits_set_01006a800016f083</name>
		<md5>dbe5e0c39d8e479473ed662cfb64dcfc</md5>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192756" />
	</game>
	<game id="359405">
		<path>./Games/Taxi Chaos[0100B76011DAA000][v0].nsp</path>
		<name>Taxi Chaos</name>
		<marquee>./images/Taxi Chaos[0100B76011DAA000][v0]-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Taxi Chaos[0100B76011DAA000][v0]-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>20210223T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Lion Castle</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192809" />
	</game>
	<game id="198483">
		<path>./Games/The Legend of Zelda Link's Awakening [World] [Ja,En,Es,Fr,De,It,Nl,Ru,Ko,Zh] [01006BB00C6F0000] (1).xci</path>
		<name>The Legend Of Zelda : Link's Awakening</name>
		<desc>As Link, you awaken in a strange land away from Hyrule, where animals talk and monsters roam. To uncover the truth behind your whereabouts and rouse the legendary Wind Fish, explore Koholint Island and all its trap-ridden dungeons, reimagined in stunning detail for this new release of one of the most beloved The Legend of Zelda games. Along the way, you'll meet a hilarious assortment of charming characters to which you'll never want to say goodbye.</desc>
		<image>./images/The Legend of Zelda Link's Awakening [World] [Ja,En,Es,Fr,De,It,Nl,Ru,Ko,Zh] [01006BB00C6F0000] (1)-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/The Legend of Zelda Link's Awakening [World] [Ja,En,Es,Fr,De,It,Nl,Ru,Ko,Zh] [01006BB00C6F0000] (1)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/The Legend of Zelda Link's Awakening [World] [Ja,En,Es,Fr,De,It,Nl,Ru,Ko,Zh] [01006BB00C6F0000] (1)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/The Legend of Zelda Link's Awakening [World] [Ja,En,Es,Fr,De,It,Nl,Ru,Ko,Zh] [01006BB00C6F0000] (1)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/The Legend of Zelda Link's Awakening [World] [Ja,En,Es,Fr,De,It,Nl,Ru,Ko,Zh] [01006BB00C6F0000] (1)-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20190920T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action / Adventure</genre>
		<family>The Legend of Zelda</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>de,en,nl,jp,fr,es,ru,it</lang>
		<region>ru</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192839" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/The Legend of Zelda Tears of the Kingdom [0100F2C0115B6000][v0].xci</path>
		<name>The Legend of Zelda Tears of the Kingdom [0100F2C0115B6000][v0]</name>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192840" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/The Witcher 3 - Wild Hunt [Complete Edition] (JPN) (ja,en) [XCI].xci</path>
		<name>The Witcher 3 - Wild Hunt [Complete Edition] (JPN) (ja,en) [XCI]</name>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192841" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Turbo Shell [0100A0A01BEB4000].nsp</path>
		<name>Turbo Shell [0100A0A01BEB4000]</name>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192842" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/Turok 3 - Shadow of Oblivion Remastered [010013D019CF4000].nsp</path>
		<name>Turok 3 - Shadow of Oblivion Remastered [010013D019CF4000]</name>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192843" />
	</game>
	<game id="198309">
		<path>./Games/Windjammers [USA] [En,Fr,It,De,Es] [010048800B638000].xci</path>
		<name>Windjammers</name>
		<desc>Windjammers is a fast-paced head-to-head arcade game where two players face off on a court, and throw discs at the opponent's goal zone to score points. Incredibly fun and intensely addictive, Windjammers is the adrenaline rush you're looking for!</desc>
		<image>./images/Windjammers [USA] [En,Fr,It,De,Es] [010048800B638000]-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Windjammers [USA] [En,Fr,It,De,Es] [010048800B638000]-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Windjammers [USA] [En,Fr,It,De,Es] [010048800B638000]-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Windjammers [USA] [En,Fr,It,De,Es] [010048800B638000]-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Windjammers [USA] [En,Fr,It,De,Es] [010048800B638000]-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<releasedate>20181023T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>DotEmu</developer>
		<publisher>DotEmu</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<family>Windjammers</family>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>de,en,es,fr,it</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192910" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Games/WRC_9_The_Official_Game_NSW-NiiNTENDO.nsp</path>
		<name>WRC_9_The_Official_Game_NSW-NiiNTENDO</name>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192911" />
	</game>
	<game id="359302">
		<path>./Games/XCOM 2 Collection [0100D0B00FB74000].xci</path>
		<name>XCOM 2 Collection</name>
		<desc>The XCOM 2 Collection includes the award-winning strategy game XCOM 2, four DLC packs (Resistance Warrior Pack, Anarchy's Children, Alien Hunters, Shen's Last Gift) and the War of the Chosen expansion all in one package. Activate any of the additional content (DLCs and the Expansion) or just play the base game. 
 
XCOM 2:
Aliens rule Earth, promising a brilliant future for mankind while secretly hiding a sinister agenda. As the leader of a guerrilla force facing impossible odds, you must ignite a global resistance to eliminate the alien threat and save the hum race from extinction.</desc>
		<image>./images/XCOM 2 Collection [0100D0B00FB74000]-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/XCOM 2 Collection [0100D0B00FB74000]-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/XCOM 2 Collection [0100D0B00FB74000]-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/XCOM 2 Collection [0100D0B00FB74000]-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<releasedate>20200529T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>2K Games</publisher>
		<genre>Compilation</genre>
		<family>X-Com</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20231125T192936" />
	</game>
</gameList>
